three
one two three
oh
one two three one two three
whoa come to thredup under three threesome
okay i'm saying that to you guys
of course welcome to say it to
you well thank you for having me
three i'm really excited to be getting
today you don't see guys i me
today that's right it's all about you
just an interview how lauren got started
or and i'm doing this for you
so where did you do improv or
worrying i'm talking about
ah did you hate tell you always
knew you were funny don't you hate
that yeah i don't know why anyone
would ever listen to a podcast where
it was a real interview someone i
know it's like forty five minutes you
can't there's nothing to talk about in
forty five minutes other than the stuff
that's been endlessly i just don't really
i sometimes i find it interesting to
hear
her someone's like origin story or whatever
you're bitten by a radioactive spider sure
that's interesting i mean right there huh
most doctor ran or belted by gamma
rays you could really google most things
and just kinda yes exactly this is
the show where he's also advice to
interviewers i know guitar know that's how
they come up with their questions what
have you already said let's try not
to try to get you to say
it again this is the show where
we don't do that this is
the show where me lauren lacus and
my friends ah paul f tompkins scott
ackerman we are just friends and we
just talk about things were of us
here he called himself lauren and now
oh i thought was the comedy that
was being brought five c it was
spewing for
yeah it was the comedy that was
oozing out i hadn't fucking disgusting dreams
or oh tell me here we go
it was about someone we know and
in the dream i was going to
have sex with this person hell yeah
but then their penis had
like it was like it was stopped
up with something green oh
oh so it had like i'm sorry
it's so raw and i was really
nasty you know and i was like
oh no and i got really scared
and then i we didn't do it
but then i was like oh no
do i have whatever that is now
and then like i'm gonna get in
trouble because i'm married and like yeah
losing this whole fucked up dream dreams
where you've killed p
people i find that i have those
i'm just like well i'm a murderer
now killing know i have way more
sex dreams than anything and this and
by the way i'm killing people with
my
do you well when you have a
dream about someone do you like when
you see them on in-person or on
instagram after that are you like oh
no they're kinda like that i haven't
when i was working at the affirmation
tension i know it's you one of
the one of the other waitresses
said to me like oh did you
work at in two years the stories
you have from that time it's true
i'm a lot happened i mean there's
you show a lot of people yes
that's the show um then i was
calling jaw
epic cardiology jar jar binks giorni alley
which i refer to as macaroni grill
me cobiella i can never remember the
name so i think it's like well
it's no longer with us apparent louie
calendars i e marie calendar's of course
i was there for years marie calendar
i was an air square marine here
i always wear had the best fra
chicken tenders and fries food bar and
when you see get stoned probably are
just that particular one i really yeah
much like when well whatever one you
are because you're saying qualities of an
extent frantoio can you also allow brown
x that i was in high school
okay yeah my maybe my palate wasn't
as quite
you also say that maybe you didn't
do a good job baking these chicken
tenders
um what was i talking about oh
chin chin cares oh yeah so one
of the wages is just like i
had a dream where you and i
had sex last night and i think
there's only one reason to say that
to so if you want one actually
if you currently want to have sex
with him but she was treated like
it was disgusting like a curious phenomenon
yeah you only say
if you want to have sex that
person and you could even make up
that you had a dream where you
had sex if you want to die
too i was like oh i was
put off because she was not ever
didn't never had expressed any kind of
interest in your dream we had sex
you were really into it made me
think you were hot for a second
you said you were so happy but
it kinda made me go oh well
is she interested but then she was
acting like it was so gross and
it was just like what is the
purpose of this conversation just to make
you uncomfortable i don't know why she
did that she invited me to a
party once and i didn't go i
had i want that at all in
a very strange dream it was one
of like a really entertaining dream and
mary holland was in it and i
texted her the next day
and i said yeah you are my
dream i sign this what was happening
and blah blah blah and she said
this never occurred to me to say
before she said thank you for dreaming
of me
hey she's on your mind that's great
yes great to be planted since she
said it i said wow i'd never
occurred to me do that she said
well it's very flattering i was like
you know what you're right i guess
it's sort of like that quote about
how in my what does it in
my twenties i was worried whatever one
thought of me in my thirties
what is it you're right nobody thought
of you well but but then in
my forties i realised no one was
ever thinking of me yeah which is
like yeah that's kind of what it
is like i know that's not true
people think about me a lot they're
all really thinking oh yeah oh i
live rent free and a lot of
people say i'm so fucking sick of
that receipts for that oh i've kept
the receipt so good
cause you write that off
i dreamt of weird last night that
we were hanging out and and we
saw a kid wearing an edith t-shirt
and i said hey man you still
got it
was like okay that's weird i had
a dream where weird out took a
child to court really yeah for unauthorized
merchandise
does that really happen
i think it's literally because i saw
someone eating earlier in the day i
saw i was reading a website of
like popular songs from nineteen eighty four
and yes this is my life in
quarantine and ah and though a year
by year i was listed on it
i was just seeing if ever heard
of m nineteen twelve the ginger ale
polka
were you trying to get ready for
to watch wonder woman and you were
like what songs might be in the
movie we did by the way why
would it be prepared we watched in
order to prepare for wonder woman nine
nineteen hundred and eighty four we watched
wonder woman nine teen hundred and seventy
seven the third season premiere which we
didn't realize was an hour and a
half movie which
is more time than we want to
commit to with lynda carter with lynda
carter but it's the craziest fucking plot
first of all i did i i
watched this when i was a kid
but i guess i didn't realize the
first two seasons of wonder woman are
set during world war two yeah and
then this third season is set in
the seventies so i was like i
wonder how they did that so i
watched it and they
i'd just basically like at the top
she sees steve trevor her love interest
she goes that looks a lot like
steve trevor and to son ooh yeah
and then she's like this guy i
used to know i'm like for those
two years that were invested in you
then suddenly like in-between forty years or
thirty years has gone by
and you just basically forgot about him
anyway it's a weird way away but
then does the son becomes a love
interest again yeah it's really weird that's
fucked up yeah and then jessica walters
in it which is really funny she's
acting she's young she's like thirty probably
but acting just like jessica walter which
is really funny
like the same whole like arrested development
yeah the same whole side glances and
caddy things she says but she's like
yeah she says the banana from the
theme right but it's a crazy ass
fucking plot of this thing i wanna
watch that i remember watching that show
when i was a kid i don't
have like a lot of memories of
it i mean obviously linda carter super
hot
ott of a litter of a little
boy who was like i like this
lady i like this slade oh she
is buxom oh my god let's talk
about hot girls shit this is making
me amorous
learn to do that as tits and
l
ah lauren do you talk about ella
handsome guys around mike like if you
see a handsome guy on tv yeah
i would just say wow handsome guys
and attractive women will just go and
attract yeah he's really pretty oh he's
hot you know some guys and attractive
women a life watching television you can't
help but comment on these yeah absolutely
jamie i always discovered yoshi by accessing
covered by axis
i mean let it fit the meter
no
you discover them by accident like you
find her scrapbook where she's cut all
the lady yeah exactly but on your
show everyone she'll say she'll say something
like the way i found out she
had a thing for um all shit
he was in no country for old
men choo choo what's his name sugar
or whatever yes
why can i think it was dude
dude from ah bond dude from bond
yes i don't know droopy god damn
it what's his name he's low t
we need to load
i really love that movie theory we
had about droopy dog and rewatch that
cause i don't remember a lot of
times you were around to know his
name oh no country for old men
it was children of menace the movie
i'm thinking oh yeah i'm clive oh
my lights children of men um ok
no shy for old men i'm looking
at you
yeah i'm javier bardem vieira bar yeah
yes and she said like she was
talking about somebody and she's she said
i mean he's only he's javier bardem
and i was like oh wow what
is accepted by all of humanity yes
like most attractive first came out of
nowhere and i was like whoa okay
like that
yeah that's how i felt it's it's
always been like a weird like a
thing that she like david tennant was
one where she just kept she would
just keep saying like she just bring
him like if something was on she's
like well just have david tennant i
guess we could watch that and after
after like a few
times i was like do you have
a thing for him she's like maybe
wow who's viewed that the guidance sweetgreen
thought i was i walked into sweetgreen
he goes oh you're you're famous right
ago not really were we there no
no but i feel like i've talked
about it i just don't want to
incur the wrath of wrong path
this may have been is just a
phrase now i know but but i
said no effect yeah exactly good for
you to be here with a spanking
man that's his only like fortunately wear
a mask at least it's only dude
just died of coders because of that
yes god we're saying we did and
it's because of this um wow very
far apart
we're super far away yeah there are
people who are doing podcasts in indoors
in the same routes yeah um but
ah he was like you're famous right
i go ah yes absolutely he goes
your i think he i think it
was david attenborough because you're david attenborough
what am i go what does he
look like eighty year old guy aren't
you final barry
i mean
because oh you're not i go no
i think you're thinking to someone else
and then the next time i came
in he goes oh i know who
you are no i don't know why
i thought you were david i'm sorry
that person is yes yeah streamlight oh
it's insanity he's ninety four yeah i
hear to pick up my order sweet
green
yeah as ago this was grassland
to be said i want they lose
out it was the weirdest fucking that's
bananas yeah oh my god it made
me really like insulted but also really
loud funny it makes me wonder who
does he think david edinburgh is yeah
can't think it's
the sale because start going is he
thinking to the dude from jurassic park
because even that's insulting that alone can't
but that guy was old and nineteen
ninety three or is he thinking or
is it did he see a movie
of david attenborough was in in the
sixties and think that it was made
the other day there's no plausible explanation
before meet
i didn't know who david attenborough he
don't know but that's weird maybe you
were david cross
even worse you know like when people
don't really know and they kind of
just like mix people up like that
yeah yeah yeah yeah i don't know
i do think it's weird though when
like people get recognized
as someone else but there but that
person also is famous like it's weird
to be like like you to have
someone approach you and think you're somebody
else but they could know who you
are like is there something about how
people look
do what i mean like jump tow
like like ok my friend got ah
um recognized as being someone else but
he also is famous right so it's
like no i i think what happens
is people see someone triggers something in
their brain it used to happen to
me where i would see reality show
people around town and i i
if they were my friend yeah i
go hey how's it going then i'd
realize oh i'm just talking to someone
i saw and really hey what's going
on meanie meanie yeah a flavor flav
it's only a bus
anyway why is it but it's only
one ie both times that's what it
is i do the whip i apologize
you the ne to nini leaks um
was already to watch me whip watch
me naini i'm sorry you should watch
me do watch me whip watch me
meaning it's a song written by four-year-old
but i think it triggers something as
cool
i think there's something in people's brains
of like now she didn't do women
she does naini i whip my hair
back and forth i whip my head
where are you were you think you
will smith when you said it was
written by a foiled wow no i'd
say you'd like the the idea of
a of a song it's like watch
me do this watch me do that
much me oh i was thinking what
my hair back and forth which by
willow smith who was like mine
when she did co-op's nephew would dance
to watch me whip and watch me
nay when her sister got married so
it was like his favorite song that
summer and he would he would do
this particular choreograph dance this is the
shoe cleaning entrepreneur gets me so she's
still like cleaning jews dude hey i
saw on the day his hair is
crazy if you're listening chi your hair
or is nuts i think i saw
something on instagram of them recently yeah
it's nuts um but everyone's hair is
not that i'm sick i know sos
mine i've only given myself two haircuts
i've only had one haircut during this
whole year and it was in july
and now my hair is really likes
long but at least you can do
stuff you can like you use
put it up yeah i mean right
now i have it on my butt
but like it's getting really like thick
in a way that i don't like
i want to be sure yeah yeah
yeah um why were we talking about
whipping nanay oh yeah but i think
it's he's like you see someone famous
you've seen on things before trigger something
your brain
and then like that used to happen
with my friend where people go oh
my god i love you hello drew
carey and be like what yeah it's
really weird like but i but i
also wonder if the if it's like
if that happens people who aren't in
entertainment at all and arguably like you
see someone and you've you've seen them
like i feel like it's chrome
right it's like nobody like it's common
with please go to a hardware store
hey you're in the bank
that's thanks
it's commonly new actors and famous guy
for the bank because you're like no
i'm actually from the supermarket
so you know what it's funny
no it's quote unquote funny oh it's
funny people like let it go and
let people wanting to let it go
on no i just think it's i
think there's something about like if you're
a familiar face or something then people
are like oh yeah something then they
just put the wrong person on it
or yeah for sure i've definitely had
that experience many times where it's like
i know that purse
listen and then you realize you just
recognize them from a tv show yeah
and it's really it's like you're trying
to place them like did we work
together on something did i go to
school with them and i hit that
did i hit the ah
wow that were his catchphrase how different
that show oh watch me whip watch
me ne
lorna talk about red table talk so
well gee me i just think she's
really cool and i feel like she
got raised right even though she's exorbitantly
wealthy she feels like she's really down
to earth and she is interest she's
an interesting person with a lot of
interest and she i was looking at
her instagram and she has like a
singing duo with this woman and it's
really cool and it's like kind of
earthy in this way it's not like
any of the music shit before and
as a singing about dirt i don't
know what they sing about but i
did watch a little bit and i
thought it was really good and i
just think she's interesting and i think
it must be really hard to be
to grow up not it's not hard
to grow up really rich and everything
but hard to be grounded in that
and to be kind of northshore yeah
what about jane and when you think
about jayden now i have i have
less i will say about shoah i
don't really know i don't know much
about jayden because i watched red table
talk a lot and she's on that
show so i hear her appt
minions
and what's her opinion on back to
the future she thinks it's really well
done but like the part
ah actually just watch the dealer now
to get i love that movie ah
so good don't stop or we'll die
i haven't seen in a really long
time now but it's from that's a
lot of people mishear the old couple
who are freaked out by ah marty
going back in time and
or driving in there like a lot
of people mishear what she screams at
him as don't stop or we'll die
it's when does she say i forget
exactly what she says my name that's
why they named their band oh summer
well this is our friend's band don't
stop or we'll go inside new the
high fun now with the podcast every
week where they do a news yeah
well this or that instead of this
i've seen
in the clips on instagram they all
very catchy bands are having podcast now
sloppy boy oh we should just start
a band which has a cocktail podcast
what does that mean they talk about
cocktails do you get it now yeah
i guess so jesus guys i started
banging though because then we can be
working on their side of the street
and that way we'll have covered what
i want
play has a fucking podcast yeah so
we should have a band because no
one pays and i'll play the kazoo
oh i like that do you not
play any musical instruments i play the
clarinet yeah but that was when i
was fourteen just that was just a
lord dads
i started learning what are you wearing
that oh my god it's early and
piano during the quarantine but i told
you this that oh yeah then i
kind of stopped and i completely forgot
everything but i really want to do
it again i just you know it's
one of those things i'll be sitting
there right next to it and i'll
think what i was doing that right
now and then i just don't get
it you don't just like transfer your
buddies over to them like i let
l think
it'd be so much better if i
was trying to learn piano right now
you know how comfortable is the chair
you're in when you when you're thinking
those great that's probably i wanna run
the piano yeah so okay the couch
goes in front of you it's just
a signet and i'm just like nah
you know you don't play anything i
play guitar
like what like what like what what
can you play like what's a guitar
six strings was getting you play anything
anything if i said anything i said
play this didn't do
do it ok here we go don't
you don't fuck he did it
can you play from listening ah some
yeah i can sort of pick out
stuff but i will say david wayne
asked me to play on you know
those covers he was doing of like
where everyone records their part at home
and yeah put some together so he
asked me to play this rpm song
and i sort of picked it out
by ear
and i was like it didn't sound
exactly right and then he's like oh
there's this website where a guide teaches
you how to play against myth any
of those songs that dan guy new
york you guitar dan smith cheese it's
like it's like a flyer that was
everywhere oh wow anyway so i watched
this and it was fascinating and it
was like so
so interesting to learn the the slight
differences in the chords that you are
picking up a year of like and
like oh well this one needs a
different tuning you know stuff that you
wouldn't even know anyway he's learning guitar
right now oh we should jam yeah
he can play two chords which two
yeah he only needs one more hear
them a lot i don't know what
they are
all you really need is you need
c d and g
well then he'll be he'll be flying
in no time
he's got at least two of those
our friend is teaching him on zoom
oh really that's fun so is it
annoying to have to hear him practicing
a lot i went out with a
girl once and she had the guitar
like she'd bought this really awesome love
is my favorite set of effort there's
an annoying lesson of practice i went
out with a girl once ah but
she had this awesome guitar that
had an amp in the actual guitar
so yeah that's plugged into anything it
was really cool and she bought it
and she could barely play so then
i would play on it and she
would get so annoyed with me playing
the same song over and over it's
like well that's how you get good
so that's kind of the annoying thing
about learning piano because it's like everyone
has to hear me fucking long dong
i know and it's like i mess
up and i'm also with my app
that
i use i have it in my
headphones so i can hear like the
rest of the song while i'm playing
the notes and here's my notes oh
it here's the notes you're playing yeah
see if you're right oh interesting so
cool by sorta sorta like wrong wrong
actually i'll tell everyone what it's called
because someone told me and i that's
how i learned about um but it
is i find it um it's not
particularly annoying
ng when he's learning um but i'm
sure he knows when i think he's
good at well no because he plays
sometimes i'm watching tv and then i'm
like can you not do that right
now i'm watching tv yeah but i
don't really but i also don't want
to discourage it because it's like i
don't want to be annoying um it's
called simply piano if anyone cares but
and i play on a keyboard and
it's like where do you get
keyboard my cat he likes to learn
things oh how good does he get
at the things before he decides to
learn some guy the same question um
it's after a separate certain things he
gets really obsessed with like with chess
he's oh yeah he's very deep in
and he's like his but then like
he with like piano i he
and do he can do much more
than i can but he doesn't care
about it now but i mean he
gets very into things um i'm trying
to think of what else he's like
gotten really good at he like is
really good at making clothing you yeah
he's gonna making clay heads really like
to do oh shoot allow
he was younger but then got back
into any mail my dad and it's
really good so he just made it
like look just like yeah does he
look at the person or yoda the
person or nothing
he wasn't looking at anything i think
he actually started making and then decided
it looks like my dad and then
went with that oh wow do it
like the lady from the hello video
i don't know that she wasn't looking
at anything she's blind in the hello
hello yeah it makes the weirdest clay
richa anirudh yeah um no he was
looking at it and then he gave
me a ball and work with and
i made like a piece of shit
fish and i was like i don't
like
by the way i read behind the
scenes thing about the hello video yeah
and so lionel richie gets to set
and the reveal of the head and
he goes what looks like a chip
this he goes this doesn't really look
that much like me and then the
person telling the story says like so
so i said to lionel like ah
lionel she's blind like but the whole
point of the video is supposed to
be bad is that it's supposed to
be good and yet when yes not
that she's guessing what he told the
person telling the story is fake is
like acting like lionel richie is an
idiot for not
getting that she's blind and can't that's
crazy otherwise he would just be impressionistic
but like yeah just enough like him
and it's so off that he looks
like a monster so that's so fun
have you ever been offended by a
drawing of you ah have i ever
i don't know how you i'm did
you do you want to start why
do you have yeah yeah you just
didn't like sitting there sketching well i've
been talking
when i was in theater school i
would draw
i was i used to be pretty
good at drawing so i would draw
like ah my teachers or whoever was
talking to asked me to stop at
a certain point they're like you're not
like you have to stop drawing in
class yeah they were really good i
mean like they know they were really
good i would know they were in
the louvre
wood after the classico here i drew
this and that you have any now
i threw everything away what the book
so you can't prove it yeah no
but i was glad quality yeah no
i want to be an artist when
i was young i want to yeah
yeah i want to be a cartoonist
never thought i had that i never
got better at tuning in
high school the tigers know we took
we add a cartooning plus and i
liked it was class for lexical signs
are elective oh wow i really liked
it um and we made comic strips
i told you that oh um and
i was okay at that but it's
i can only draw very specific animals
like which ones lists like in a
comic you weigh like i can draw
a mouse and years buck teeth whiskers
got it yeah but i can only
do it from the side and i
think you decide front
really tried from the side the front
side
i know my my skills are very
limited i always you know what else
ah adult i have one dog that
draws very sound good and then i
have i used to tell myself as
like a cartoon and that one was
like what i typically did in high
school i had a cartoon character that
created called irving and i would draw
oh boy i would draw strips i
really want to be like a garfield
kerr like delbert like i really want
to be so scott adams type cavalry
well yeah jack which is great yeah
jacks yeah from your mind like his
right arm is like really huge
check it off on dry little boys
your arm is you draw a picture
it's a really heavy pin
brother was good at drawing growing up
and oh really he always drew releasing
jam
i had i almost i don't know
okay here's my thought process right now
yeah is like i when you said
you had your irving comic strip i
was i drew comic strips too and
then for a second i was like
i'm not gonna add this why am
i going to talk about hey i
don't know it's all we have to
talk about is whatever you say so
like are here also add another thing
i had this cat this day my
day were feeling yeah i know it's
just i even talk about anything anything
on this show
i have this day-by-day calendar of cats
it was just like um musical it
was honestly just pictures of caveats nothing
about that was interesting right i just
liked cats sure and then i would
cut them out and make a comic
under them and so that was an
under them like i would write it
i would write a new yorker type
line under the picture
like you cut out the pictures and
then hasten your fly
were they as slave as the new
york all the cats are going with
psychiatry i was hey too so probably
they were better than than europe oh
new yorker slams shots fired but it
was ah enjoyable and i what do
you want to brave sold them for
ten cents um no i don't remember
any
remember that you know you'd take the
picture then you just kind of yeah
write something stupid under you you'd sell
them to your mom and dad yeah
that's seldom oh that sounds horrible new
issue of the cats got out i
loved making newspapers and think yeah oh
yeah i mean at high school i
made a newspaper like a monthly newspaper
monthly yeah texas
lyrical newspaper getting you work yeah i
worked in the newspaper but you made
one that you handed out i did
it ah yeah i didn't weekly and
here's the thing i would make i
would hand make the copies so i
would make like five of them and
they'd circulate yes yeah and that was
really exciting on that wow it was
some people liked it it was not
like honestly
wide sensation but i always loved that
kind of thing in high school like
ooh it's that like i love when
the onion came out yeah i would
get really excited like to crying oh
craig's knees feel so good i i
lived my first apartment building in l
a ah the house ah yes of
course with the photo of i don't
wanna say
hey there i'm talking about my anderson
lee yeah
um
there was a little coffee table in
the lobby ah where people would leave
magazines and stuff for other people take
a magazine leave him yes one person
left scientology pamphlets and it was like
who is it i wonder but i
i at the time had a subscription
to the paper edition of the onion
oh and so
i one time put out a stack
of onions on the table and the
super of the building knocked on my
journey was angry at me because he
thought i was leaving trash on the
tape trash like dude this is the
best and i was like i couldn't
mix open your mind i couldn't explain
lane to him like these are not
like old like who oh yeah over
cents old newspapers yeah it's it's kind
of a satirical magazine but there was
like a language barrier and i just
i couldn't he was like furious with
me another thing to be furious it
was terrible
are you okay
are you okay right now
thank you for asking me
i guess i'm not i e don't
tell you about did i tell you
about when i was thirteen and made
yeah the nixon news
what well so my aches a new
you only wrote about what nixon was
up to well
my
the ah you know how to get
into this lie
so well i were damn easy
i saw mix it over there and
it's a newspaper guy yeah was
i don't want i don't want to
take all the credit but i also
don't want to get too into it
but yeah
so my friend i'll just say my
friend my friend did it to she
was really into politics key okay so
it was my girlfriend at the time
no it's cool that you didn't have
twenty girlfriends ah she she was really
into politics and um with su
super liberal and jane fonda did you
like that are you like a bitch
i liked it but we we thought
it would be really funny to to
save it nixon was making a comeback
and make like a fake newspaper all
about nixon making a comeback and being
the greatest president of all time and
anyway so we made like a pretty
funny with
like and i drew cartoon i get
it yeah anyway so we did we
had all these satirical stories in it
all that yeah i don't get it
at all
i don't understand what nixon did watergate
he you got it yeah yeah you
did it you nailed it we paid
he paid a bunch of people to
investigate his opponents to break into their
hotel room why the watergate is going
to sound um why is it
that every other president has to deal
with the consequences we don't have of
what they do like when they do
something oh and it's like no one
ever has to deal with consequences really
yeah nixon only he was the last
one impeached yeah but nothing ever happened
to him um what do you mean
it will
it's like it was marring it was
but that's about it you know what
i mean donald trump was impeached like
so if anyone was not was bill
clinton's impeachment the same is donald trump's
where he just kept going i mean
the president yeah yeah i didn't understand
and nixon resigned to avoid am sorry
to everyone thinks i'm dumb i don't
i don't know about president so nick
nixon was going to get impeached
they end and all of the people
said hey you're going to get removed
if we impeach you yes everyone has
turned against you because essentially the bad
thing that he did was bad but
then he went and lied under oath
about it the cover up was coming
and covered it up and so once
everything came out and and then he
taped himself
talking about it and incriminating and xone
two he taped all of his conversations
say and once they found that out
they're like well we want to hear
these conversations and then he kept saying
like oh no you don't get to
hear him and essentially they subpoenaed them
and and and and he was like
tell you what i'll just give you
the pertinent tapes like
like i'll give you the tapes that
i think you may want to hear
and they're like no we need to
hear them all such a bold wow
hey i'll give you the ones that
i figure yeah yeah so eventually they
heard all the tapes of him just
like confessing to everything and they said
hey you're gonna get removed ah if
you get impeached and so he left
office okay and then forward pardon
for him when he came out the
door he was way out the door
because it would be to the nation
already been damaged enough and this would
be like because their their faith was
shaken in the presidency now we know
everyone had always just like idolized each
president or whatever the last thing people
want now as consequences for someone's actions
yeah so i'm gonna let him
go and then ever since then nobody
has to deal with anything i see
i always kinda thought other people had
a worse um punishment than let no
no no george w bush gets he
gets minced from michelle obama yeah she
gets to hang out with l and
mince pies
but in any case so why i
thought i thought you know we thought
it was really funny to do this
like five page and now that he
has a context pretty funny right i
think it's hilarious and i what i
love about it is so let's all
the ways that lampoons yeah really inspired
by the lampoon so
it's wonderful the harvard lab yes of
course no but it was it was
probably not funny or whatever but it
was funny to us in eighth grade
that we were like talking about nixon
making a comeback and doing all these
satirical articles anyway so we pass it
out to everyone ever wanted to school
made xeroxes of it and i got
called into the principal's office
and the confidence to pass it on
to everyone yeah who knows and i
think they liked it or they probably
threw it away some people kept it
because i think someone likes photocopy it
incentives to me wow um i keep
a lot of stuff like that i
probably have like weird shit like that
in a box somewhere that you got
weird shit in a box i remember
the principal was always like he was
like
well i gotta say this is really
funny really clever very smart and i
was like hey thanks i'm sure it
sucked but he's like but the kicking
out of school but we have an
official newspaper and we these need to
be illegal because these need to be
against not illegal but against the rules
yeah because we have
an official newspaper and people i forget
what the like bend over backwards to
say like i'm not going to punish
you because you didn't know that these
were were against the rules or whatever
but you can't ever do this again
you know but like other places have
more than one who's like cities have
more than one yeah it's and nous
yeah i don't yeah more cities were
this guy's a he's out of his
mind a lunatic he's an idiot he's
a child
it's a fucking child grow up teacher
um we need to take a break
our first break wow first break of
yeah oh twenty twenty one we'll be
right back
welcome back slim into a slap g
slap into the slim slam you know
what i'm sick of wow it's dive
for lord's favorite department know what i'm
sick of covert yeah but from that
the
we all joke setup if you blank
you don't need to worry about the
vaccine if you yeah it was funny
the first thing i never was really
funny it was
a picture of like dirty pillows yeah
like like yellowed pillow i understand it
was like if your pillows like this
don't wear the vaccine but that was
really funny that was my favourite i
think i read it today for the
first time like if you thought brie
larson was terrible and captain marvel you
don't have to that's why rats that
one's crazy well you know how there's
a bunch of like terrible people out
there yeah like don't like
brie larson because she's no i don't
say a planet to the vaccine why
don't they like vaccine bhima because she
happened to say she thinks more women
and people of color should work behind
the scenes and that is
i was like wait what's wrong with
that as i say i yeah that's
it's a merit based system my god
okay like everything like everything is yeah
benefiting white man um and sorry oh
yeah if you don't like what we're
saying anyway so i understand what you're
saying if you don't like what we're
saying about that and you don't like
this show yeah like you don't like
talking about people
yeah there's like the like but yeah
both ways people so weird that there's
people that are fans of like star
trek which is which of the i
yeah utopian society where we've put aside
you know all these stupid bickering things
that we have when we all work
together now yeah and it's like i
don't
like politics it's very similar with comic
books where there you know there's all
these people who are like hey stop
trying to make heroes that are they're
black or women you know it's like
you know stuff trying to pander it's
like all these people who've grown up
reading these moral stories about people trying
to do the right thing but then
you realize there
only into the power fantasy exactly and
that's what the star trek thing is
like they like they like the lasers
and yeah and the imperialism and the
the fighting and feeling like well what
if i were a good fighter you
know but star wars to to a
certain degree because it's the same thing
with star wars yeah yeah star wars
has like so many strong female catholic
princes
giulia is a stronger female character than
you remember in the first movie like
he's absolutely like not in distress she
is she doesn't need to be rescued
she's like very much tougher than i
than i remembered as a kid but
because she's not the focus of the
movie in the way that the guy
yeah she's on his journey and everything
yeah yeah but
so like you know like oh you
but put the put a woman in
this just to do it because people
asked i don't know it's like what
did you think people what did you
think you were watching yeah i hate
everyone in any case so you don't
like this so it's i'm getting first
because everyone's doing it like it's those
things are fun for like a second
it's like why can't a joke just
be a good joke why do you
have to do your
her spin on yeah now the joke
is like if you if you wear
shoes in your house you enjoy by
vaccine if you if you if you
jive yeah this type of cry and
worry about the exam yeah if you
you know i just don't care yeah
then rent living rent free in my
mind is now one of the well
this is this is a twitter problem
i mean because if i wasn't unimportant
or i wouldn't know when yes and
i wouldn't give a fuck did not
really ruins jokes and runs them into
the ground i think i really i
i here's the problem i connect with
friends through twitter yes so i do
feel that i enjoy going on and
seeing oh what hanging away but i'm
for the retweeting part
out of it is has ruined twitter
because now you have to read what
other people say yeah i i don't
mind that so much because usually i
curate my twitter so that i have
a list of people that i enjoy
falling very low to very low wide
ranging lists so it's people that are
ah it's people that think like me
it's people that don't
think like me it's people that i
that i trust to retweet things that
i'm going to enjoy and that's how
i find other people that i like
to follow um but i the my
thing is and it's like i can't
it's like one of the things that
i can't be mad about but it's
like when people want to re
apply and they want to do their
own joke and a reply reply the
reply yeah just like that that's part
of it i feel guilty when i
retweet someone's joke and then bad replies
come and yes i've seen me yes
i'm mortified of course these losers would
want to add this joke now this
nice of sellers are losers i love
mine
i've only good followers
when you then i'm like oh i
i re-tweeted a joke of someone who's
doesn't have many followers now that to
deal with this fucking shit know why
couldn't they just enjoy their show possibility
though um so that is what lawrence
mad about this
i met about right now as i
opened my phone and saw one but
it's the only thing you you can
be mad about one thing a week
is this the thing that you want
to be mad about this wow no
no or do you want to be
mad about something oh i got an
email saying else can be what i
think really bad i talk to everybody
oh yes
once she opened the window you walk
past the window oh up in the
sash she did not throw open the
sash and throw up i think the
thing i'm mad about what you're gonna
and i know i'm gonna cry was
a new thing now yeah but no
i don't it's it's now that it's
february i'm sure i'm mad about something
else but i did see people that
i know traveling yeah
cavalierly with no quarantine and no nothing
yeah to their families it yeah i
did too jamie and i were talking
about that that it's you know any
word about this get that a lot
or is that just here i feel
like i get it a lot here
from me isn't say your own name
and context yeah yeah oh shit we
entered like a weird moment recently she
has lately started saying my name to
get my attention paul wow really instead
of like babe yeah yeah it's really
strange i finally had to say
like why are you always say that
i feel like something bad has happened
i don't like when my calls me
lauren yeah i've stopped we only we
only do it if it's like if
maybe if we're i'm trying to think
like this specific instances where we say
each other's names and it's not weird
well like in front of other people
like my yeah you're staying with us
so i'm not saying
ng babe or anything yeah it's like
that did to me it's like i
find that were sweet tush yeah we're
like second nuts
it's chock full of nuts i'll just
say mike but it's like yeah then
when we're alone i don't feel like
i'm either you embarrass like that you're
dead would think that you think he's
a big baby
she might mistake him for a baby
i just think my parents never called
each other be what they call each
other by their names mother five yes
their names i guess the one thing
that bother thinking it was just so
scared about my position not talking to
each other right
now especially oh
yeah
hey i'm in heaven okay i was
sorry about all that what a horrible
thing i like you stay married your
whole life yeah just waiting for death
yes so you can part company exactly
and then you're up in heaven because
you got married you're putting others have
the same last name
so you're thinking okay you're right em
um the one thing that bothers me
is when klopp calls me oxman around
other people because it's like like you
like your buds know it's she does
it it's like she call you that
in private no
hey ackerman what do you because it's
like it's it's still okay so this
is what i likened it to you
know how when you watch the bachelorette
or something yes nah i'll check out
any kind of reality show when someone's
call someone the kid yeah it bugs
me because it's a status thing yeah
where you're like
you know the kid just bugs me
like he's a good kid but he
what oh it's like what the gut
two guys would say but two guys
yeah the mathers that they're saying it
about each other like two competitors are
like this kid is like so if
you call anyone a kid yeah it's
like a status thing where you think
you're better than them yeah so that's
what it feels like when she's like
hey ocker men around
other people yeah huh it feels like
no just call me what you call
me at home which is smart reading
your
and so janie was calling you paul
yeah and i finally had to say
like don't call me off it really
it really makes me anxious because i
feel like you're about to say hey
paul they're gonna turn a daughter off
oh thank you for that they're going
to turn out
paul they're going to turn our water
off why is it so is that
a good example i just think it's
so funny like an emergency or to
happen turn our water up i mean
i would like a good reveal of
like but how has amazing the bill
for six months yeah yeah paul
you might have like your like so
someone's like the plumbers over your house
like don't you have to go a
pretty long time before they turn i've
i've missed bills and they don't turn
it off right away it's usually like
a five month thing trying to think
when i've gotten stuff shut off it
was like a while what what what
did you get a lot of times
in your life
you've had stuff yeah yeah yeah for
sure like what have you gotten shut
off the electricity okay electricity or so
were suddenly just like boosh and then
you when it's damaged i didn't pay
the bill ever ooh they found out
yeah it caught up i'm trying to
think of like yes stuff that's been
because usually like apartments i would live
in there will be a couple things
include
added but then there would be something
where it's like where you're on your
own for that we always stop there's
always some area i don't like that
i would just have like he's dead
stove in my house and no heat
when you are like it's fine i'm
a guy yeah i'm ah yeah this
is what guys do this extra eyes
zoo saturdays for not having he oh
that just reminded me of my
the power going out in the freezing
cold in chicago ah for some reason
our heat was turned off but i
think it might have been just it
was happening territory when our power went
out on labor day of the summer
can i just say that i was
so fucking cold and i was wearing
everything i owned and no framework
what happened on labor day well your
power went out yeah because my birthday
was september six and it was the
power went out on my birthday and
that right discipline we we heard it
was still fun we heard your power
went out so when ah and yours
got so we turned our power
in solidarity parody nobody you you texted
us that yours came back on after
two hours it was a heatwave yeah
so there's a heatwave going on oiling
outages liberty weekend rather so ours went
out at i remember i was i
was out here i'll never forget i'll
never forget i was high i'll never
forget that i was ready i want
to know and i was
thinking
se me um no i was i
was out here and i have the
the the the stereo on and the
music playing and suddenly just shut off
and it was fourth thirty or so
and you thought i thought oh no
i have to lay in the pool
with noma just got high ten minutes
ago oh no i dropped my bean
what am i going to do um
no but i thought oh okay so
it'll be back it'll be back on
it like six thirty which i think
at the time it was getting dark
at seven so i was like oh
yeah that's fine and then it was
so hot
and then just the hours kept going
by and going by and it didn't
get it wasn't like yours where it
came back on after two hours and
so at like nine o'clock suddenly all
of the air conditioning had worn off
and it was sweltering in the house
and we had none of the lights
were on and we were using flashlights
and we were like okay i guess
we should even though
though we don't feel really safe about
it we can't stay here because we
won't be able to sleep let's go
to a hotel than every hotel none
of them would take dogs and then
our show gone to hotel for dogs
that's true do you take humans
but then the other part that we
didn't know is we were we finally
were like can we just go over
to our friend tall john's house and
we're like can we stay at your
place even though like we haven't quarantined
or whatever like we just can't be
here but our gate our electric gate
wouldn't open so we couldn't drive oh
so i had to side to figure
out how to open the gate
which is like a huge deal anyway
so club go wow what a man
what a man want to bet you
made me hot and bothered but that
was as hot and bothered and i
was the one turning this power outage
that was the one time that we
went over to our friend's place where
we just kind of gave up we
were like life circumstances of life yeah
just
felt who cares if we get cold
that i can't see but hothouse haven't
gone to anyone's house i did one
time maybe why the ones september it
was my birthday september da xix day
was my birthday and we were going
to sit outside and it
when all the fires were happening and
so the air was unbelievable this is
around the same time we went yeah
it was around the same time so
we went inside and it felt very
illegal yeah i did go inside actually
was on my birthday um and i
felt such imprisonment for one other couple
and i felt um crazy
yeah but it was it wasn't it's
nice like the times even just seeing
people i feel like the times i've
seen people i'm like like loving it
yeah because i'm so sorry about baja
but um i really i just really
can't wait for that feeling to go
away when like you feel like when
you're finally just sixty so weird
yeah i'm like near you
it was afterwards we were you know
we had dinner we were you know
in a big room we were far
apart from each other but afterwards it
felt like
it was really i had i like
a really weird comedown because it felt
so normal yeah yeah felt so normal
it's back to the same old and
then it's back to the well this
cause that's why all those cheaters are
out there doing it and just yeah
getting together they should reboot cheaters about
people who are cheating cheaters yeah covert
cheaters look at this guy he thinks
he's gonna get
away with it i used to love
cheater oh i love cheater it was
a fun show it was crazy it
was so weird what a weird show
i told you about that the weirdest
episode of cheaters with the guy introducing
it in a tux producer and then
throwing it to the old host who
was in the studio know the new
host who's
like hi i'm the new host of
cheaters and joey greco or something i
think he was joey greco yeah but
then the footage they had had the
old host because the new host hadn't
done any footage yet so there were
three fucking notes of what episode
it was so funny
yeah it does feel weird to be
around people and that's when we went
over to my friend's house it was
kind of like we'd both gotten tested
recently so it was kind of like
you know anyway belt and neither of
us go anywhere so it was kind
of like it felt okay but it
was very weird to suddenly for the
first we ended up having to stay
there for two days because it finally
got turned back my two days later
date
a's and for the first two or
three hours we were pretty like aware
and trying to wear masks around each
other and that is a certain point
it was like this is impossible and
stupid we can't even do this but
it felt it did feel risky though
yeah yeah yeah it felt like to
me it felt like doing when you
would in world war two when you
were not you know rationing are you
aren't like pulling the blinds when you
are supposed to do it it felt
very it felt very much like a
you are not doing your part during
now yeah which is kind of illegal
feeling yeah like you're what would they
you would have to turn out the
lights when like they were bombing and
yeah like that so they couldn't see
like where the city was yeah that
exactly my god exists oh my god
oh my god you guys palm and
it's honestly horrible oh yeah my office
chilean people it's horrible yeah that sounds
fucking bad i mean you're just sitting
there waiting to get fucking hell this
is this is why it's so infuriating
this is lee i know it's there
you're being asked to do so little
i'm sorry we were during the break
we were watching a lady
yelling at people in the cbs for
having to wear a mask and it's
incarcerating kristen wiig character history just just
like what a bitch i i just
i can't say that but you i
can't imagine being in there and like
not telling her to fuck off like
get the fuck outta your idiot yeah
why do you need to be in
here and what's your fucking point and
you know you're
just doing it to be annoying like
so is this the thing you're mad
about yeah more mad about that okay
this is the thing okay this is
officially this is it ok anti massacres
who feel the need to fight you
on it just be an anti masker
and just don't go anywhere how about
these dumb dms who are doing like
little parades through a target wow it's
so late
mean it's mortifying i cannot i just
it's so imagining being their child humiliate
feel i just feel so empathetic to
these children oh speaking of things like
that yeah i've been watching this show
i don't know if i mentioned this
to called welcome to platteville we talked
about this
wow sounds familiar right it's fascinating what
is it a reality show yes and
the show is the plath family and
they live in yes huh yeah southern
georgia
and they um they live in the
middle of nowhere small town no will
parents have usa i don't know how
many kids there are like eight or
something there's a lot and
they are so sheltered but then these
kids the older ones are starting to
venture in the world so it's almost
like um breaking amish oh they really
don't know anything like they don't they
never had a coke they've never you
know gone to the movies they don't
have any like the typical experiences of
a
child growing up in america because they
live in a small tunnel because the
parents are very strict until okay would
take like playstation no they don't have
a tv they would go to daily
listen to religious music they never heard
like pop music so then they start
venturing out and except for a baby
right yeah now one of them is
like an underwear model
he got like really small and he's
an undermount oh and the parents are
like the stick i've seen this guy
yeah your files
huh they're all the problem is they've
raised them show so strictly that now
they're all trying new things and it's
like very crazy to the parents even
though the things they're doing really are
team but like it's it's very very
interesting and it's also one girl paulo
family this girl moves out she's like
sixteen seventeen and she
gets her first kiss on the show
oh ha and then and then when
it happened she's like can we pray
and then she says like dear god
i just want to be able to
like handle this correctly with this guy
and she says it to him like
but to this guy and move it's
it's a really interesting show little boner
i did it a mormon girl
url
i did a mormon girl did you
date i don't know like he's like
oh we've got a girlfriend forever yeah
yeah yeah yeah he's like i wrote
a newspaper with my friend while she
was my girlfriend and i did this
mormon girl okay so when i was
nineteen or twenty it was a very
good year is december nineteen sixty three
umm no we i dated this mormon
girl for a while and i felt
really weird about it because a while
like a summer ooh the summer of
my mormon girl but i felt really
strange about it because she was very
the mormon i remember like on ah
what day can they tell you that's
how you're referring to her so i
mentioned so what day can they not
go out and do stuff is it
sunday october third saturday
you scared the devils de um but
i remember like her saying yea la
yeah we can hang out and be
going over to replace she had a
book of like because you can't pay
money for stuff is that what it
is why does this look more it
there's a certain thing where on sundays
i believe you can't spend money i
never heard ever because that is neither
you
i can't work and that's making someone
else work if you spend my see
i see so there she had a
book you can't work you have to
prevent other people from yes well you
can't encouraging anyone to work right so
she had a book of fun things
to do on a date that didn't
cost money or whatever and she's like
see we can do some of this
i was like this is lame but
number one
should have been have sex right well
that's what i mean my other friend
who was mormon he went on missionary
ah is that with someone they called
a mission you went on a mission
and he was a missionary he went
on a mission well that's what that's
what he was saying he's like all
of them were having sex you throughout
your sunday thing i am okay so
an ex
size and manual labor is best reserved
for the other six days of the
week as our exercise such as running
and other recreation but under what mormons
are allowed to do on sunday the
fact is that this commandment just like
all the others is for our benefit
not the lord's anyone who has faithfully
live the commandment of keeping the sabbath
holy can tell you that a strength
has come into his or her life
the soul needs rest and rejuvenation just
like
anybody who's done this can tell you
it's great it's great yeah they love
it they have to buy books how
to circumvented yeah here's a book about
how you can possibly have fun this
thing is great and it's boring as
shit here's a book
so i remember and i was always
very respectful of her like we would
make out and i was oh very
restored by you know you would listen
to her pray afterwards now but i
was respectful about not going far with
it even though it seemed like she
wanted me to oh she did but
i remember her asking me where this
was
going because i think i was going
way to to theater school after that
like after the summer and i was
like well no nowhere she's like then
why are then why do we get
together and do this i was like
well why do you think we are
she's like well if this isn't heading
towards marriage i was just like ah
i think you've got the wrong idea
about me baby
i'm a rambling
ah don't you know i have many
girlfriends i planned to date a lot
of people throughout the years including someone
marie calendar's
shame about me including someone wrote a
newspaper
in the past ah
come on it's not that many people
how many people have like a lot
ruins always have a girlfriend store and
we're gonna do a body count man
it's always a different world just always
like well my i had a girlfriend
i was doing some of them are
the same girl probably alright well then
we should get more specific team girl
i feel like i feel like everyone's
all i hear about one of the
muslim to your show soi one
i want to feel that ah what's
that i was singing the song same
girl
usher and ah what's the fucking name
why does they leave bye bye because
he's cancel usher who's cancelled oh chris
ray r kelly thank you wow they
had a song where they they are
taught they're sharing with each other this
new girl in their lives oh nice
each revenue growing their lives turns out
the same girl damn what a horrible
situation enemy sing
me about it they're comparing notes so
they found wintering georgia tech works a
tbl way yeah went to georgia tech
and works a tv yeah it was
in georgia yes interesting yeah wait that's
the lyrics choose yeah yeah i like
it song i think also she loves
some waffle house well that's anyone's sorry
works at tb
yeah it doesn't narrow down at all
is hilarious there now works at tv
yeah lifted it look it up they
know that you looked at it like
a very nice lady she says professional
yeah she's a great job in show
business i think it's disrespectful color girl
she and development i don't go into
that and this could be greenlight in
the room
ah alright we have to take a
break
and we're back it's time for three
shirts time for three true we always
do this we won't stop doing by
whom was this submitted well scott i'm
glad you asked this is submitted by
karate surfer thank you karate sir for
saying thank you so honestly karate server
er thank you so much hey chronic
surfer thanks man or or ma'am or
man or ma'am thanks for what you've
done
here's how movie merge go
one player combines the titles of two
different movies that share the first and
last word for example a few good
men in black or la la land
before time the other two pitch the
first player a movie with that title
that combines the plots of both original
movies as a sorry i had to
call
pardon me hey pardon a little fuck
out of me the other two bless
your silly ass to another to pitch
the first player move you that title
that combines the plots of both original
movies as crossover slash new concepts slash
reboot slash etc trying to get the
first player to greenlight their pit chael
yeah
let's do it okay polly do you
want to think of the first title
no i sure don't i just read
the thing how about ah how about
er you go so i'd put it
i'm thinking of the example and yes
this is the hard part of the
thing is thinking of these titles so
think of one movie then think of
a different movie then put them together
and remember we
to do this three times three times
okay oh i'll think of it too
and whoever thinks one first can and
then meanwhile paul you have to talk
yeah i have to say things to
keep the listener listening or else goodbye
podcast no one likes length okay of
quiet how about home alone is there
movies section alone
this is the hard part you have
to come up with it
but this is fun this is how
we get it going
ah ah alone again your coach on
here i got i got one okay
miracle on thirty fourth street car named
desire yeah yeah classic movie museum this
is okay so paulo i have to
pitch to see yes hey thank you
for seeing us thank you for signing
you mind if i lay down um
no i guess that's all right great
it's your office alright on the floor
i'm like um i'm gonna lay down
on my desk on your desk oh
that seems like a comfortable place fabulous
baker boys us as your desk made
out of pillows this looks so yes
this is made out of a few
pillows oh wow
um if you
okay can i ask can you green
light in the room i do have
that power i don't always use it
i'd say i'm a friend of work
cbs you can do that does you
want to test shoots georgia tech gun
um long story short i'm sleepy so
why don't we get to the quarterback
a deleon of what you're going to
say ok
well we have a great movie pitch
for you um and the title should
we start with the title yes it's
calling a title kind of grounds me
okay it's cody miracle on thirty fourth
street car named desire desires long it's
so light earns the title okay because
there's a lot of story
the that happens and i figured once
you're you've read to the end of
the title you're already in you know
at that's what you're i mean you're
not committed i'm like well what am
i going to turn it off now
i already read the okay exactly been
on and how do you guys know
each other we are brothers and sisters
okay and how long has that been
going on now
so became legally
kimberly eagle three hours ago two months
to three hours ago get your story
straight guys we do it we just
did we just you maybe we're landing
what's your favorite thing to do together
oh i bet anything doesn't cost money
on sunday so zoo we go through
monday to set on your saturday
every day and pay through saturday or
at the zoo because it costs money
sunday all we do is count money
that we're not spending yeah okay and
what's your favorite food to eat together
i got lady and the tramp style
ah spaghetti tacos spaghetti tacos have your
red spaghetti taco know just discussing what
you lose from getting right talking and
all those carbs with the pasta yeah
the taco shell taco shell here you
know right and oh my gosh chicken
heroes and you guys but it's all
an audio tag go to bed at
the same time yes we do yes
we do a a p n eighteen
oh yeah our yes so six o'clock
six o'clock pm yep we love it
and i guess my final question is
what you want to hear
this pitch
well my final questions for me final
question is what's the movie about ah
now i understand your methods very well
played well we open in new orleans
the big easy santa clauses hometown to
big easy santa clauses from dale santa
claus is we see have nine crocodiles
it has nine crocodiles and one has
a red nose i'm afraid i don't
get that riff but oh well because
of the rain you wrote this movie
and you don't get the reference i
didn't write this movie i'm pitching so
you're pitching it you don't get the
reference of why santa would have nine
so i don't know anything about santa
claus
i do luckily that's why we make
a great team exactly i know everything
about new orleans he knows everything santa
ca does bourbon street for instance santa
claus loves walking up and down berber
tree with a hurricane cup in his
hand just getting shit faced your kid
to me that's right no one's asking
you to but he's doing it
then every day except sunday december twenty
four that's when he has to fly
around new orleans and only new orleans
yelling and screaming for his wife to
let him inside okay now i like
this his life is a lot i
relate to this
my husband is always screaming outside of
our house right we feel like there's
a lot of people that this will
will yeah it's very little content there
was absolutely so his wife mrs claus
has this sister and she is a
damaged goods she is she's i mean
who brews the banana you know exactly
she wears
yellow all the tall the time and
her mascara is running yes she looks
like a damned foam yeah sorry something
came up um it's what happened i
you know another another meeting is being
scheduled oh things scheduled for very soon
wants to rush or slow down i
will i'm still listening to you i
wouldn't be able to do both of
these things so
so i just need that to be
known hey okay ceo let's keep going
the sister that with mascara she doesn't
believe that her ah sister's husband is
real and i'm so figment of her
imagination or a story told to children
ah chrome of beef ah said it's
just a shot as lusher so
so she takes her sister to court
to prove that the that her husband
is not real but the husband by
the way is a mailman know the
husband santa claus yeah the mailman of
gifts you got me
so
so this so the sister mrs claus
countersuits to prove that he is real
yeah and they and and that israel
is also real it should be recognized
as a nation yes this story takes
place in the uk i love it
okay so ultimately my feeling is i'm
going to greenlight it because i love
it well that's a great feeling that's
great ult
that feeling so i'd love for the
stream made now and i want it
to be how soon do you need
me during call shoes now during coven
you want to make during covert that's
gonna hijack the budge up a little
bit because she knows coven narrower passions
and no testing and i want it
done now you want no testing no
caution we can help passing that movie
now can we have doctors and nurses
there wearing the attire they would wear
in the hospital as long as they
are supposed
to be characters in the film we
just sent this in a hospital so
you want some scrubs i want some
scrubs a scrub is a guy who
can't get no covert from me
and see yeah
ah
sorry somebody just started doing something on
my phone that he needed to be
stopped a russian hacker
and then there are a lot of
spam texts lately oh yeah so they've
decided like okay you're not gonna pick
up our calls yeah absolutely text yeah
i forgot this number works two ways
i got one today um oh wow
you did yeah duh let's see today
yeah final day you can get a
concealed carry gun certificate permit
she downloaded here takes only fifteen minutes
oh just download it just just click
the link yeah um well i just
have a question of how much time
we have because i do have to
go soon oh look that can be
our only round quite honestly make the
rules here and i can't remember a
any third two movies and we we
can come back to that three or
another time
go back to another time thanks to
karate surfer like these guys are making
fun but honestly thank you so much
karate sir no honestly thank you so
much because without you we couldn't have
done that i wouldn't dine out whenever
you already know it sounds like i
was laughing and stuff but sincerely thank
you chris thank you so much alright
we'll be back again next week we'll
be back again
then as we can't be so read
um the broadcast
actually i will say goodbye
uh