three
oh yea nah i agree nah that's
the way ah three um
hi k c and the sunshine band
that's right wow
what casey stand for ah kick kentucky
chicken and turkey chicken yeah kentucky chicken
in the sunshine yeah it wasn't fried
now oh just to finish this he
lived a long time the front man
of casey and sunshine was a live
chicken from kentucky yes yes good thing
honestly that's probably a good idea yeah
i don't really get the new i
could really see that being fun welcome
to three to mine paul i'm lauren
i'm scott hello everyone and you have
a sore throat i have a sore
throat it's annoying and it feels like
i can't inhale without it hurting more
you could inhale i did not inhale
that woman ah
and i owe you for fans out
there but i think i have allergies
this new but my eyes were watering
and i'm like what are you allergic
to if i do well i did
an allergy test years did you where
they prick you with a pin and
then draw my poison yeah my whole
back they did a grid and then
they did you say
sure i did because it was i
didn't take it they uploaded to the
internet okay because my back was aflame
in december fetishists i'm sure there are
you know they're wrong you know there
are because you are one wow you're
trying to hide in plain sight everyone's
aware i've never done it
i haven't yeah it was it was
pretty cool it was very uncomfortable once
it actually happens because of course you're
what's comfortable oh because of the rock
and you only feel it in part
of yeah like whatever part is they
picked you with yeah they prick you
a different different thing just something do
the pricks hurt i don't know if
it's a prick which is a drop
of something i don't remember oh
oh right they're not like sticking with
a pin i don't think so
i hear make sense to not put
it in your body if you're allergic
to it huh yeah because there's always
find out if you die your alert
yeah right so i will urge you
to olive trees olive trees not offs
ah not olives and there is an
olive tree where i live what if
james bond always ordered his martinis
like eight olives
really go heavy on the island and
i'm i'm allergic to dust allergic allergic
to dust which i think that sucks
i just like suse not this is
i don't know do you feel like
los angeles is a dustier place than
any other place downtown yeah and i
think but by the way i think
that we didn't
i moved here there were no mosquitoes
yeah now there are mosquitoes the worst
and allergies are now more common here
why didn't we get lightning bugs instead
of mosquitoes i would know i'm going
to get a bug that's not from
here didn't you love that there were
no mosquitoes here it was so oh
so good it was like amazing to
move here and be like wow what
year did mm
mosquitoes come i think it was like
a couple of years after i moved
i moved here in two thousand and
january doesn't ten so it was probably
two thousand and thirteen that they came
around later than that public later later
yeah yeah yeah could've been just where
i lived but because when i moved
here yeah good for me because
lakers fan i was a good kid
i'm trying to talk very best on
this episode by the way
i want i want this episode only
be a half hour can we talk
fast yeah we still did the same
amount i still do yeah and then
back and slow down later yeah yeah
exactly listen to everyone talking really guys
okay so to talk about like okay
like the story we told before okay
so we're sorry every told before that
we want to tell this look into
this just the day we trust was
walkable districts you were walking down the
street just the other day
ah oh um but nickname least wait
so sorry are you allergic to anything
we don't know we haven't had it
done but you do know what they
do you are allergic to know i
know that i used to be allergic
to cats yeah cats i didn't realize
you grew it i outgrew it yeah
i realize i wasn't told that until
after tall enough and then you are
fine as a dad runs down breaking
news
okay this is bic fuck oh my
god i'm fired yeah paul
pack up your office
it was back up your outfits pack
up your own fits your phillies you
fired that's a good accent you are
the weakest link good you're very generous
um what opened her ah the original
or gen robinson both she was the
weakest link she got fired but when
did she regenerate changing shit
dr stein we were going to do
that on bang bang when reggie left
the show but ah i couldn't figure
out how to do nerdy um so
i'm watching this movie air last yeah
you cannot pay me to watch that
movie really oh that was fun people
are now saying it's you don't oh
oh i know but people say a
lot of things fantastic that i disagree
that's true yeah so i'm watching air
and in the beginning of the movie
they have a guy was just shoes
it's nineteen eighty four was like how
am i going early ball
he is there at some point ah
it's nineteen eighty four and they're doing
it establishing montage they have wham they
have absolutely ah they they george orwell
they do a little bit of anachronistically
ah is that the word i'm searching
for where they have run dmc from
the following year yeah
yeah plus and there but but they
try to cover their ass by having
chris tucker say like run dmc are
coming out with a song called my
adidas next year on their next albums
like how how would he i'm sorry
there's breaking news that bikers in a
movie again why why did they have
to put in something that wasn't timeline
ides appropriate like y da to put
that well it's it's about shoes i
know so they're talking about why ideas
are cool and chris tucker says like
everyone loves adidas why even run dmc
instead of just saying write a song
about them and just like no one
knows was here like i do i
hope that kelly says everyone
because why run dmc themselves coming up
with the sonics yeah there's one you
gotta know did you just have the
word trying to figure out rhymes as
we speak but it wasn't weird choice
like what instead instead of offending me
the only person who would know like
oh my d just didn't come out
until ninety eight yeah ah they instead
cover there
harass and say like they're coming out
but why would chris tucker an executive
at a shoe company no right even
know about run dmc he keeps his
ear to the ground about shoe news
that's crazy but in any case i
was very very happy in this montage
to see one of our favorites featured
that's right one string clara peller he
original it was how is it that
brushy one string
clara peller was in the movie she's
in the movie she's the star there
it's a bit of a radio star
of air hopefully she was gone i
can't get up so no that's different
that's a different way to think they
were talking we don't know who that
what that lady's name is i follow
okay i don't even know why i
just did that by brick
i know what her fucking shit is
let's look we've talked about it so
i fucked that commercial was so funny
which when i fallen and can't get
up play flirt yeah oh that was
a crazy one that one in mir
the commercial for miracle ear yeah where
the old man's in the movie theater
i know i remember now he's in
various places and he's he
can't hear what people are saying and
he's constantly asking them to repeat themselves
and then at the end of the
there he's at the movie with his
family or whatever and everyone is the
movie is over and everybody's like getting
up there clearly moved by what just
happened at the old vagos what did
he say oh yes
or did he say he missed the
last movie i was so important i
wish he was like is it over
like yeah alright here's here's some of
you can't hear a movie jesus christ
miracle or two
the doctor yeah i have the opposite
problem i saw you could only also
fast and yesterday yeah movies when i'm
not there and it was too loud
yeah okay edith four
but edith for is e before i
never i think ketchup with you should
want for cyborg what are you talking
about edith fours the fallen and i
can't get it and i got up
she died in nineteen ninety seven but
we love her she is of course
an honorary piss oh
do you think and i don't and
i don't mean this in a disrespectful
way but do you think when she
died people said she finally followed yes
it's official god has lifted her up
ah
make gun full
yeah
she's up in making god falling back
but we love her an honorary piss
pig she died in nineteen ninety seven
yeah i've been made that i've been
meeting similar places pigs i gotta say
i met a few more so great
that one last night met one a
couple nights ago love our picks yeah
folk yeah oh by the way holmes
misses for now the cyborg began making
commercials after actually falling
and with blood dripping into her eyes
activating paramedic alerts
she preceded the commercial i guess so
i guess that's what they maybe hired
her she came into our dish and
i'm sorry that was like insist actually
happen to me so i maybe she
drew from real life i just say
i'm honored to be here no matter
what happens i'm through that i got
to be too because i felt i
couldn't yeah i think blood was dripping
tomorrow
i enjoy eyeball i could see the
red and then they were like she's
got it i felt the salt of
my own inside yahoo is i believe
that they first had her in commercials
giving testimonials about her rescue oh shit
yeah then maybe she segue into the
acting like i could do i don't
do it like a lay on the
ground yeah you wanna take
once for no blood dripping into your
eyes yeah for this commercial gave me
a helping it up would that have
been as successful a commercial if there
was just ripping i know it and
it would've been more today at least
do those capsules so if you're johnny
bells yeah actually know what a bit
better because watching it as a kid
you don't really see what's so
so serious about that she's like laying
by the tub and you're like sure
you're like hey i'd like to lay
down yeah but then if she was
bleeding in her eye i'd be like
oh no yeah yeah yeah her name
was edith for edith four f o
u r no unfortunately r r r
martin met a pirate
f o r e like the golf
ah for deal with cafo came through
her window hitter in the head yeah
knocked her down that's why she probably
and that was the last road she
heard she's like that's my last day
where you calling me when you announcing
the ball she she ran towards the
ball known around the world here i
just
yeah
a bonk on the way here i
was wondering about golf clothes okay i
had to say why are they what
they are why sorry they what they
are i have been talking about this
on stage recently hey the golfers don't
need special clothes wow i love the
overall this isn't the zeit guys so
so the the
polos that they were the golf shirt
something where are there because you need
because here's my guess you were supposed
to wear a collared shirts to be
classy probably wherever you went and so
they were like ok well let's make
it like a t-shirt but with a
collar yeah right but then i thought
okay do they want their arms to
be free so they
can make it smooth motion so sure
they wear long sleeve though yeah yeah
yeah that's a good point but then
it's like kind of just about the
look but what the witch cannot be
beat but i'm not totally against the
idea of seeing everyone on the golf
course kind of in a uniform i
don't hate the idea of it's better
than seeing people in sf
sweat scoffing do you know what i
would like first of all agreed but
if everybody like had to wear white
or something like that you know what
i mean if there was like a
standard thing that they all did and
i thought that would be kinda cool
the shoes in the nba had to
be fifty one percent
then nike paid all the fines and
legal trees in the skies were layered
up like crazy golfers yeah right they
had okay so they had the let's
let's see if we can name you
have like a name topside golf or
does you have like your sweater vest
what are the things they would like
hang off like little yarn balls or
something why you know
oh that was probably that was on
their club golf clubs and the other
wouldn't wear those anyway i thought they'd
take them off and put them on
their clubs to keep them warm they
were lab landers
yeah when these were early shoes
they represented all nations
so they have the best in the
polo vest vesta the polar their breaches
their knickers yeah belts of course bill
was really wrong soft sock software charts
your argyle socks yeah and then golf
shoes which have cleats i guess yes
yeah so that you don't slip when
you go bowling heavy have you ever
been interested in golfing i want i
liked
playing mario golf so much that for
my birthday my friend got me a
couple of clubs in a bag and
my friend who was a an experienced
golfer took us out to the los
feel is a practice course and i
could never hit the ball wow wow
if it wasn't shaped like mario's head
except
that's how you play mario golf use
glover with goku
you can worry me but was mario
golf with a controller or with a
we control club okay the most i've
ever like you know so those days
i'm just thinking that would be fun
yeah but we do it like that
but no you did those we right
right yeah it's hard i think it's
i mean people might be laughing at
me but yeah but but my friend
who is an experienced
golfers like yeah it's harder to hit
the balls and they tell you but
i'm sure i'd be terrible at it
because i couldn't hit the ball and
i can play baseball and hit the
ball coming towards me and stuff like
that but like but your little do
up you're like yeah you're not looking
right at the ball while me and
it's but you must no matter what
the sport is keep your eye on
the ball
all you must do no matter what
that is true i will find you
um the only interest of arizona golf
is golden tee yeah yeah just the
big arkady you just do a little
like yeah with a little ball yeah
it was fun everything should be a
video game every thing any voting yes
yeah i would love that i would
love that a lot
not what i would really love that
you know what let's like you know
ever like we were talking about the
strike before we started the show and
and how tiring it can be to
walk you know up and down it
is exhausting in a different way i
turned it into a video game we'd
all love that yeah if i was
going to do i played all day
yeah this is me this is like
i think war should be a video
game yes why are we sending our
young men and women to die when
we could just have a video games
and then we'll see world conflict see
who wins and then a bad especially
true in it yeah it is actually
true it's insane that there's still don't
know i know so crazy honestly that's
one of the things that drives me
like crazy as a purse
isn't it's just like why are we
doing this what is more fun yeah
like we're doing middle ages shit it's
just good wow you into it you
ready do it i just know scott
you love it but isn't it just
hearing that people are like we should
have a war let's kill a lot
of people no no i don't join
skaters yes that's crazy people who are
defending themselves i think which
is the definition of defending yourself is
it necessary but i'm saying why are
we where are we waging war yeah
maybe you are waging war yes yes
but you think it so it's always
like one side ah is attacking this
defending what about when frankie goes to
hollywood tells us the two tribes go
yeah that's a good point what about
mister kohinoor gets a third tribe
what about what about when right said
fred said he was too sexy for
his shirt he was doing do you
know that he's a huge like antivaccine
weirdo no no yes i'm too sexy
for the vaccine to save him and
his twin brother whatever and they're constantly
like and those tweeting wrong dead wrong
wrong said frog wrong
said fraud
wow it's just sad frightened for i
think i didn't know this then i
saw this it was a whole thing
yeah it was a whole thing with
you yeah in that respect so i'm
online on the internet isn't it funny
how it seems to be the most
washed up people that facts they love
to have a statement well they love
devastate
payment and they want to be out
with it yeah isn't about it okay
so you saw it online what if
you could not see anything online anymore
i think i'd be happy yeah why
didn't you have it i would love
if you saw it online there were
some things we figured out like what
have you could never see anything online
again when instagram was down yesterday i
was like yea yeah i thought
i'd be down forever of course slowing
down for five minutes know so yeah
it's like a relief when those things
i know yeah oh i can't do
this bullshit ever again because someone decided
for me yeah yeah getting off twitter
i am not having to post about
shows is like such a relief it
makes me feel of like when i
stopped doing comedy death ray about like
oh i
get to do whatever i want on
tuesday i know see i think that's
interesting with leaving twitter because i can't
leave graham the same way i could
leave twitter twitter became so vile instagram
doesn't bother me as much but i
waste a lot of time there and
be nice to not yes yes yes
yes yes i do the i try
to always remember to to hit the
following ah tab so
i'm not looking where you it will
give you the high line of people
follow rather than just a bunch i
always forget about that yeah i like
instagram because i get like five thousand
dollars every couple hours from people who
i just yeah oh yeah there's oh
that's love you just like type a
simple phrase back at them yeah and
you get a lot just be the
first one of the
first six hard times every thing yeah
i've gotten a lot i made like
three hundred k last year from doing
that yeah it's pretty good it is
obviously it's my favorite thing to do
it it was fun today think they're
doing what is the i love it
aloud is that scam work i think
someone was saying to me that it's
not a monetary scam
m someone someone wrote this it's an
emotional scam it it helps the algorithm
if people respond to a post or
something oh i don't want to do
that but what but their whole their
whole profile is just about like hey
i'm rich and i'm trying to help
people so what i don't get it
but i don't know i just want
you to know that little waste of
time but i but you know maybe
i'm na
i meant for this world i don't
understand these us like the song vincent
by don mclean yeah the way which
the world was ever meant for one
as beautiful as you who is it
about vincent van gogh vince van gaal
really and and like that right please
let me know when when fred said
he was too sexy for this and
there is maybe the world wasn't meant
for his world yeah hey
lorin i don't know i'm just thinking
about that song it's not because i
relate to everything he says politically it's
ah i swear not wacky bringing you
my swear i sway yeah wow moon
and the stars in the song is
that
for one offer one offer one um
one for all my dear boy speaking
of singing what have you ever seen
gina was watching this documentary about donna
summer oh yea just came out and
they have her appearance from family matters
in it
they may have a majority of the
doctor was in and out of the
room that's possible
but hey they show her performing like
when she was like just bursting on
the scene and love to love you
baby yeah and she's doing a real
orgasm during that yeah i've seen i
have no idea it was fucking yeah
it was it's she's like she's being
so sexual on stage yeah it was
a waffle
i was standalone it is well she's
a born again christian now so everything's
cool now she's dead oh that's right
yeah so she's jamie like oh they're
gonna cover christianity and she didn't know
about that and then like i came
in later and ah they're talking about
her in the past tits like this
like oh jesus you know she was
dead and i was like i don't
think i remembered that no
no i guess she died like in
like twenty seventeen or so thanks to
recent yeah she should have been dead
since the eighties
well still an honorary pittsburgh
dasara summer absolutely an honorary pipit oh
i have three christian have to say
something about before you do we have
to this is exciting anyway finger yeah
we can wait okay we're gonna take
ray colby reddick
okay okay we wanna know wanna know
we we stopped by the way now
stopped doing the episode and we all
went home yeah yeah for five days
and we've been so just bursting with
anticipation like the wink yeah yeah i
slept forty haven't either you've had forty
days yeah
okay um the thing was that um
it was brought to my attention that
you know when i was talking about
how when she's psycho and they had
like yeah and yeah i touched but
going to see jane and i was
like dad my burger exchange oh yeah
document rebel yeah dana live orchestra i
don't know why
philip glass tell me oh so extremely
justified yes and i didn't remember at
all because my memory is poor as
anyone who listens to the show will
know yeah and that makes me because
i always thought it was just like
incidental music but i remember it but
i was also i remember when i
now remember that i was like oh
yeah so i was really excited to
go
so i and i knew immediately afterwards
were like this yeah i know about
it i forgot about yes the relevant
lured you into the boys like that's
a cool hill i think he was
there yeah yeah yeah is that possible
yeah i saw him on stage with
jane little anyways whole thing but it
was really interesting anyways when we've we've
done so many interests that would be
the highlight of anyone's life
yeah yeah and for me no show
tuesday yeah go to a concert now
yeah um i speaking to philip klass
i remember watching battlestar galactica and discovery
original show the new one right and
discovering that show the philip glass album
solo piano which is a beautiful album
i don't believe there's a song in
that on that album that they use
in
the show to great effect you know
what song it is i think it's
it might be they're they're kind of
they're they are thematic i think it's
metamorphosis metamorphosis one yes maybe yeah
this is the fuck is this this
is just some idiot playing it i
don't wanna hear the idiot why would
anyone want to hear that okay i
think youtube should delete like five billion
per cent of its ah they should
just be the judge yeah just really
exist so you just say to them
you know which ones come on you
know just
just get rid of it
oh my god everyone's crying ooh ahh
i see it is haunting oh yes
ooh ooh
believe me starbuck does like a monologue
over this dramatic monologue about lottie's yeah
well you see how all the people
battlestar galactica die in there
his starbucks is starbucks sometimes six feet
yeah it's starbucks named after starbucks no
no no buddy starbuck is named after
starbuck okay in a way it is
because the modern battlestar galactica posits that
it's actually been back on it's very
yeah he's just right i thought
originally the past i thought they were
going for it and so they were
the inspirations starbuck apollo they were the
inspirations for yea i thought all this
spaceships are gonna we're gonna be like
start earth is that what they did
like now they're all earthlings years older
thanks sorry spoiler without the ending but
you can see it come
me from muddle way and then and
then everyone sort of bates is the
answer from the very beginning though i
don't think well yeah because you're too
busy like looking at those cylons going
think they're sexy oh no i want
to have suffered a robot old robot
i don't notice silos it's robot alright
it looks like a person a man
they didn't use to look
like a person yeah just like big
robots they were cool looking robots too
they were like a great design went
to ah universal studios back in the
day just for their big battlestar galactica
attraction where basically if some robotic cylons
with like point lasers your coming back
to that i would do that they
were
lauren do you know what they look
like
crazy to draw them all the time
do you ever see pictures of them
no i wonder if i could draw
on right now yeah try i'm gonna
try to do it from memory i'm
not looking at a p can't do
it i'm not looking at a ah
a picture
yeah it is not horrible no it's
empty worse but did try to do
it from memory i'm trying to remember
what there because they had sort of
an egyptian like mohawk yeah they doing
along with like a darth vader whoa
that's high and they had like a
ah red ah rarely lonely guy that
was good
oh that's right your head sorry really
cool and they had like a robotic
voice were like by your command that's
more like it but that's the worst
thing more like it so we're strong
if anything anyone's ever done for righteous
go back outside
oh boy battlestar galactica yeah that's that's
cool man that's really awesome if that
okay you know how how there's a
big debate and we're not gonna say
which i we lean on about okay
in this country and whether they might
whether they're they're really the greatest
but if they made laser guns like
they haven't star wars battlestar galactica yeah
you'd want one oh yeah i would
for sure yeah i wouldn't want one
you wouldn't want why because i wouldn't
want to have an accidental laser shooting
never happens never happened why and in
science you've never seen anything like that
in star wars where someone's like
in their tattooing hut or whatever moisture
farmer that thinks someone's breaking in and
then they accidentally shoot themselves yeah that
was actually never said should happen next
because that would be good maybe i
should be a soca i would liked
a white on a soca maybe maybe
sheikha that's the soca soca that's
the new shell stop saying it
you know the whole the whole i
don't know about your singing soca soca
yeah i don't think you get it
plea paul so what is it ah
so ah so soca no soca ah
so i don't saying oh like i
don't remember i'm saying a soca so
it's not a soca like a samba
soca right
is that like super awesome sounds like
a super soaker to play with their
friends in the street yeah it's not
a super soaker yeah yeah just go
to hydra is that this is a
chupa
two medusa is useful to the jupyter
for that oh that's a ratio remember
that what does it is when um
ah okay what's her name right now
do you remember yeah i'm looking up
as soon as soso to po and
she went on david letterman and she
was talking about a resourceful trooper oh
rosie
oh xyz is a trooper he goes
what's it going to zoos tapa yeah
this was a trooper i like rosie
play the clip ah taught us you
remember to tuck last was on your
show ah when it was comedy death
ray way back when on the improbable
radio version and he kept saying subaru
subaru
subaru i'm trying to get my mom
and subaru yeah i can't find it
i don't know all right well everyone
else people find their own time yeah
yeah i'm imagining yeah right it's just
like this
wait what are you saying please was
a trooper i can't understand jesus
a white bag is funny to chupa
the end what isn't is is a
trooper though it's a car yeah i
know but like is it good it's
great it's the right that's why you
haven't heard of it it's better than
every car it's but i still live
in azusa you live in zoos troop
i used to live in a car
i'm joel
she lets rosy presses birthday now twelve
sixty eight yeah because you think it's
nine twelve sixteen let's see how close
we don't get because i actually thought
it was my birthday but i'm like
why do i think that i'm guessing
it is my birthday that's fucking okay
i only because that was i don't
know anyone it wasn't sure okay just
oh wow you don't
i know okay come on why would
i know i know yours july two
yours is
i pick my mum no idea it's
also known as paul i think your
ah your september october or september hey
guys okay we know that mine is
the birthday it's the best birthday yeah
known as the birthday i have no
idea sorry okay my news september six
years september two were september eight i
mean six
and then what year do you think
because you were close
rosie yeah yeah rosie i think is
older than me so i think eighty
three maybe
ah no i think she's she's sixty
seven
sixty seven you know like nice some
sad oh wow okay
nineteen sixty seven yeah and you say
i'm gonna say she is
sixteen five nineteen sixty four sixty four
close arose not going over yeah um
but she was great on the flight
attendant which is great in ah harley
quinn at last harley quinn movie and
do the right thing an honorary piss
pig rosie perez waved
birthday twin okay yeah on respect yeah
ah who are your birthday twin scott
i don't know let's find out no
um no no there's my berlin's september
something come on twenty something he just
said it a bit ago when i
don't know i'm going to tell you
it's never gonna just yeah why would
i remember anything when it's in my
calendar
okay here it goes eventually was my
phone number because
oh my god
yeah the people who share a birthday
with you are it was marco opposite
of you as does mark hamill oh
hold on i haven't gotten there yet
there's a there's actually a lot like
i'll give you a yeah there's probably
a whole bunch of people who share
my birthday margot robbie oh lindsay lohan
yeah i've heard her yeah um jerry
the hall okay larry david
ooh
what was your jerry hall oppression
i'll root but i love you johnny
rear the ice skater
it's anywhere yeah i should add a
d to the editor and say you
wanted to know if mark hamilton
it's like hey why not hamill's birthday
september twenty fifth okay he's also a
september baby um lauren who are who
your other birthday twins um i believe
susie kurtz is one suppose you see
right shows a scene and we eagerly
should eat yourself but we got macy
gray rosie perez elbow jane addams jane
from back in the black and white
days um jane curtain that was a
good one jeff foxworthy you might be
mourn on september six yeah if you're
a redneck that's yeah he's reversing it
now yeah if you're a redneck you
might do this those are the main
cause the main okay let's do better
jokester i'm reinventing myself
and then september twelfth here's the ones
i know okay way are you september
eleventh know what the fuck is wrong
with i don't know i'm not listening
to you fame oh stemmer sniffs famous
birthdays of number twelve okay but here's
the ones i know what your twelfth
yes oh great i know george jones
i know maurice chevallier
oh yea your old friend from xii
has rice and unfortunately i know louis
c k but why does it say
mark hamill now hold on a second
mark hamill's more and i just looked
it up and it said he was
okay we got paul walker we got
sydney sweet young paul walker rocker emmy
rossum that paul walked jennifer hudson o
j
um george jones um a lot of
people i've never heard of they're like
are you here yeah i know are
you mad the j hud you got
it before you did barry white oh
no tall gay um i'm a little
bit i mean not mad but disappointed
myself yeah you could've tried harder yeah
louis c k yeah we
don't say it again hell yeah yeah
this i love it
ah oh my god so funny anyways
so yeah great so birthdays birthdays birthdays
oh man which birthday is it going
to be for you this year my
aunt will be thirty eight thirty eight
yeah good for you what are you
what are you planning on doing for
your fortieth you know for my fortieth
i don't know but i have two
friends who are returning forty
in early twenty twenty four and we're
talking about taking a girls trip really
i'm pretty excited i hope we can
make it happen it's fine ice came
out so yeah what and we want
to go either to disney world or
to um have these points very far
literally like your trout portland maine like
it could be anything really just kinda
really maine where we
we're just yeah we aug that's right
yeah well in maine yeah we did
the tour show there oh okay wow
well i might go there we could
tell you the hotel where there was
a pair of sweats
oh just lying there in my room
that's right what you got in i
did not know that because i immediately
went to sleep and then when i
got up there was wax like this
yeah we did that's honest but we
didn't talk about how fast he thought
he was thought he was in the
the leftovers yeah because e he thought
somebody cut
rapture oh yeah so i was fine
with someone being in my room not
sure he yeah exactly the thing yeah
sure man it's such a bard i
hope that's not gonna be true i
hope not because you enjoy although think
of all the rings and watches and
stuff you'd be able to pick up
and clothes yeah
it's true it'll be fun to just
like big clothes on the street trim
on i think it used to be
i think when the rapture was first
introduced as a concept they were like
it's going to be ninety percent of
the people who've gotten than the unlucky
ten but now i think it's flipped
where it's like for sure ten percent
of the people would be gone yeah
yeah yeah the righteous yes yeah sucks
yeah sucks so it doesn't
they can go okay i mean i
don't mind we're just gonna hang out
until the the antichrist cups sure don't
you have a good time what is
like it's like come on man i
was like i did i didn't even
get to die you know like i
do you didn't give me a heads
up yeah do some cool
death it's an experience you'll be robbed
of that life experience yeah that would
be really everyone all owed everyone gets
it yeah thug everyone i'd be really
hard yeah it would be the worst
part
thing
the idea of dying and being okay
with dying like at the end of
your life you're if you get to
if you get to be well i
guess any age if you know you're
going to die and you make peace
with it before you go to be
like well i'm ready that's too i'm
gonna go kick and scream and i
can't talk about people do with though
yeah people to it
i don't know yeah we have sick
brain yeah
ah
and we're back and it's time to
play a three church shit this was
submitted by brie
not to cheese and you fucking weirdo
thank you for clarifying while i thought
cheese came alive i was just wondering
if the cheese submitted it because the
cheese stands alone but what about that
breathe and ham commercial where ray larson
john
because the i was actually a person
and the cheese and then pete davidson's
id and that made sense from fast
ten yeah it was a really yeah
okay ah that commercial was well structured
it made sense and i enjoyed it
yes i saw this guy so this
um article that was like how did
p david like fuck
like how did pete davidson end up
in the summer's biggest blockbusters i'm like
what do you mean how he would
talk about him nonstop famous yeah yeah
that's how because if you like i
was an article
we talking why did i read this
i didn't read it i read the
headline read that's just as good like
how did he do to end up
in this world this country's biggest blockbusters
of the weirder that helen mirren was
in one yeah i mean you know
one what's even weird about more than
one three at least know she's been
part of the fast universe oh yeah
weird okay does it know she's in
shazam too when he's at an air
purifier you know i additions for that
minutiae zam yes teddy was the new
shazam yeah first my agent said that
this is a great part if you
can get it and i was like
great and then i found out later
or they already had a shazam movie
before that yeah and the part was
cast well it makes sense that shazam
would age too i mean the little
boy gets older so zamzam be as
old as you but also the cyber
handwritten and in my agents handwriting okay
weird huh shazam is the movie
yeah well right
shaq is the genie nah that's chasm
that's because then what is shazam it's
ah zachary levi is the superhero but
it's about a boy who when he
says a magic word becomes an adult
superhero oh and then he says the
word again and he turns back in
a little boy so when he's an
adult he has as much sex as
he possibly can yeah yeah it's good
when you're bringing this here i'll just
blast we can remember it when he's
a kid so i can't wait yeah
so nasty
alright i addition to b o museum
docent dos who is startled when helen
mirren character appears in museum oh okay
and see it
like seeing i'm going to appear let
me i'll just say that i give
some speech and i did they did
ask you to react to like all
this shit alright here i go all
this grain free shit okay and as
you can see this is the ancient
greek bullshit up here
wow and then she like flies around
the room and shit she flies around
the room so give me direction what
a weird thing to do because over
here we just fly her she's just
she knows she's over here now she
has a thunderbolt now she's gonna throw
it right out you right past you
yeah that was really good no way
the audience at home didn't see was
that paul i was
you'll figure it out rush really really
well yeah i mean i truly thought
that you were frightened for your life
i mean you wet your pants yeah
and you shot that i knew it
was going to happen so i concocted
this whole story so you do it
with universalism for the decides i don't
know which is
or elinor you
i can feel it coming like oh
good
i auditioned for sale in the store
instead of just buying or selling
to the hospital so these barely roadworthy
ah i feel like i'm gonna pee
soon i bet
right yeah i hope they asked me
to re-enact my
it's really smooth
i know you guys so well do
you would ask me to yeah yeah
alright this is a game called or
three two rather called under the umbrella
under the umbrella dd beatty i knew
the outerwear it's not wetter and it
is better the game starts with one
of us making a rule to ourselves
for example
whatever is under the umbrella has to
be green that's an example okay the
color green okay we don't share it
with the other two of us school
to the color purple so then the
first person will say under the umbrella
i will bring
elect one of these a cookie and
the player who made the rule will
say no since cookies aren't typically green
so i think that we since their
yes or no yes some cookies are
green but but typically cookies or brown
shit they're brown they're light brown so
many can layer brown and light brown
yeah typically typically typically typically typically the
game is so fun to cookie sure
it's true but that's just seasonal probably
it's probably a lucky charms i mean
like a shamrock shamrock or chris christmas
i would say is more often chris
green christmas decay crucible hey i might
have a shamrock cookie yeah cody j
griezmann yeah ok now i've won a
shit fuck up okay i want cookies
now lol give i think we have
i have you know have a couple
little snacks okay let's talk about crees
so so it's won by whoever guesses
it okay great let's do it please
just leave your nose please for some
reason last
at christmas i gave you my heart
the very next day you gave it
away this year to save me from
tears i'm gonna give you someone's i
start i'm just like fuck this when
jane and i were at home and
i started singing whoo gives a fuck
about three spans and then she started
singing it and we were singing it
all day to really be the thing
you sang it now
for six months yeah i haven't stopped
yeah like it something wrong we turn
on the mics and suddenly you start
talking who'll give a fuck up crease
maf okay i'm gonna yeah i'm gonna
i'm gonna because i read the rules
i'm gonna come up with a rule
for for this okay okay
i got the rule shit oh look
at this and it's not a thing
you're not trying to guess the thing
you're trying to guess the rule yes
okay got it okay hey look at
this umbrella over here oh what it's
got oh hey i'm an umbrella okay
or you are an umbrella oh that's
weird just that a lot of times
you got a lot of stuff under
that costume room
for me yeah yeah listen i'm underwear
i'm afraid that you may be a
underwear oh really scary so afraid this
is gonna get with so i'm going
to put an umbrella okay you tell
me if that's allowed to cookie yeah
bring it in no way we would
no no no no okay i'm sorry
but i have the rule okay no
cookies are not
oh um sorry to get your how
about this how about this guitar guitar
zan allowed
okay alright oh clouds are really getting
dark ah
how
okay i just want to put my
dune buggy under there no sir you
shan't put your dune buggy under this
umbrella how about my shoes your shoes
shan't be under this umbrella what am
i i'll stick one stick yeah shan't
be under this umbrella two sticks shantae
under this umbrella what about a pack
of
cigarettes shan't be under this umbrella what
about the president of the united states
no
what about
do we know are there any parameter
i know literally there's just one rule
like he can't be concepts yeah you
know it's objects okay it's my watch
under never about my clock
how about um a table now
can i put my pinky in there
no how about a strawberry know the
hell this sucks i know how about
the sweater my grandma knit me the
sweat on your grandma nittany yeah you
heard me
my mini stuff right around the room
she went to penn state
about makeup no no
how about a monster ah um
i'm gonna say no how about a
yeti
no okay what the fuck is it
then about a nope no how about
eyeballs further away further away
how about vampire bat yes spring in
how about a pumpkin now thought to
be halloween based how about a pigeon
sure bring you in okay how about
a butterfly yeah okay
how about i think i'm on an
angel fucker yeah bring that bring that
shit it's fucking wings
okay no one said tony bellew good
job
hey my turn huh so it wasn't
as bad if i gave you one
hint yes thank god but my turn
okay i'm ready you're ready can i
put my cylon warrior underneath your umbrella
that's a robot yeah yes is it
robots
no but i don't know the rules
about those things but i'll say yes
but let's just continue on you'll see
maybe i mean i can i put
pinocchio under there no can i put
my chat gpp under there yes can
i put haley joel osment in a
specific movie under there no can i
put determining oh wait maybe yeah
ai i put the terminator under here
yes
but it's not my real category you
gotta move away from this
not my resenting machines or ai eyes
know i mean
but the terminator and haley joel osment
is the movie i chose epg when
you find out what it is you
might say that didn't really count okay
well then do we get what what
do we get in return if that
happens i'll slap you both owe ah
okay
um is a can i put my
pixar lamp under here yes can i
put betty boop under there no can
i put woody from toy story under
no okay
can i put johnny five from a
short circuit or circuits that it's all
robot types early no i guess so
can i put wally under there probably
could i put
ah lightning mcqueen under there
i guess so
because it's herbie the love bug under
there kind of yeah is this like
anthropomorphized no it really was much more
simple than this but it you started
at a place where it just kind
of made sense but
like what was it when we're talking
where we start we sit well we
started doing more like some more things
that are not related to that and
then you see if it makes just
things that are not related to that
yeah can i put my hair under
here no
do stuff in this room in this
room ah i put a coaster under
there now can i put a microphone
under there yes of oh things that
are black
know things that are things that are
electronic chi enough keep going things that
are gonna put things have wires ah
the nine old battery under there
yeah fuck
so things things that work
keep asking you about stuff can i
put ah this video game under there
the game know can i put tv
under there yes electronics no can i
put a hairdryer under there yes can
i put things like bugs no oh
that's what i was just determined that
would be such a great way to
defeat him if you just unplug them
can i put a stove under there
yes clients is no yeah the cylon
isn't a household appliance although very human
i'll tell you yeah things could turn
out enough ah human beings know you
can turn them on a fine turn
them off
five oh my god alright pollster alright
i have my rule you have your
rule oh look at this umbrella can
i put a chip under it potato
chip no well
maybe can i put a single chocolate
chip under their father no father and
i wow your father i love you
daddy okay put a sandwich tend to
know
a car under there
no it's not seaworld's can i put
a um sure under there no can
i put a bra under their daddy
by the way you can put a
chip on the air either i can't
show so okay
perfect about when i put a puppy
under there
what kind of puppy golden doodle
it depends on it sounds kind of
put a dalmatian under their father depends
depends on what it's yes or no
mother fucker i know but i picked
a bad thing look you know i
always mess up the game yeah it's
happening again okay what is it like
things that are dead
yeah
yeah can i put a puppy it
depends yeah
yeah it was the first thing that
came to mind if i had said
things that can if i thought things
can tie things that can dying seconds
that our ally would have been interesting
but this is our allies are alive
is so broad but a chips on
alive nobody used to be a potato
oh jason yells at that point
we killed it within an extension but
are they alive
a plant i guess is a living
thing right but but but but
i don't want to kill a potato
i don't want to kill potato either
and i don't know if potatoes
mama just killed a potato is an
atma law alright let's try a drink
hey yeah okay you can do this
i got it i got it i
got you got it okay to make
sense yes can i put a backpack
under your umbrella absolutely not okay but
glasses under there no do you which
kind eyeglasses or drinking glasses
gonna say neither what can i put
an elephant under there ah can i
put a lighthouse under there can i
put a cardinal
can i put a an american pie
dvd under there no can i put
an apple not not even the extra
horny addition
no
can i put a car now can
i put a headphones know kind of
put ahead for us kinda put the
headphones on tomato you can't put headphones
kind of kind of put a headphone
can put ross perot under no can
i put um a a bracelet
made of beads no kind of native
giles bracelet no can i put a
kabbalah bracelet made of string no i
just remember what that was now can
i put the wind under there no
can i put a politician under there
no
can i put
a star under there no can i
put a planet under there no
can i put a light under there
now can you put a lamp under
there yes okay things that can be
turned to honor off
can i put the sun under there
no can i put a pen holder
under there yes can i put some
paper that would be on the desk
uhm
yes can i put a box of
permanent markers under there
no can i put a computer on
there no okay so it's not things
on my desk how about things on
a desk no can i put
go looking around is good can i
put kind of put kind of put
kind of phone no
can i put a trash can under
there now can i put
coasters there
yes things you can see from where
you're sitting no
i can see okay you can see
these coasters i get these cultures when
i'm with you
can i t thunder there
ooh no can i put any of
the muppets under there no
can i put this jai us birds
nope
can i put a plank of wood
under there
aw fuck a lamp a flank of
wood what else did you say that's
up and didn't hold a bunch of
papers some papers
things a lawyer would have things jesus
wept or would would like if you
were no i don't know just tell
us things may have wood things made
of wood so i was close with
a plank of wood oh my that
is absolutely beautiful
mostly yeah yeah damn damn that was
good damn that was good things made
of wood yeah sam numbers good papers
waiter was off i think but buddy
i mean i've made wood it is
made of although these days who can
tell boy that's true that they might
be made of ai made play
based
i liked plant paper i meet you
thanks bree bree thank you so much
this is going in the woodpile for
us though i hope we get one
from ham yeah thank you so much
if you want to call us call
who go hey claims eight as great
leave us a message and make it
easy to understand make it
to say to and say your ne
thirty seconds or less and say your
name so weeks ahead are you a
little follow us on instagram at three
am usa
and email us teachers at three monet
jamila com if you wanna hear ad-free
episodes listen to stitcher premium or cvb
world dot com you'll be glad you
do you'll be so glad you did
but ah you'll kind of miss us
during the ad breaks though you're like
oh man there was just dead silence
and yeah oh yeah because it's the
length of the yeah
there's no ad in there no ad
but hey we promised no ad but
try to fast forward and then you
miss it when it comes back and
it's frustrating yeah a lot it's a
lot it's a lot yeah so you
just process that having a nice random
um we gotta go and that's that's
the look i have
show show plus much i have a
show coming as asia eleven june eleventh
dynasty typewriter you can come see it
in person or you can live stream
it i have a great cast i
always have a great cast so just
do it i'm not on that show
but i want to recommend it as
well it's so good it's such a
good time that times that i did
it and you should live streaming think
i have shows in philadelphia the sixteen
and seventeenth and underground arts variety opie
doing my variety show there for the
first time it's gonna be a lot
of fun still some tickets left for
the early shows friday and saturday the
sixteenth or seventeenth of june glad you're
going to philadelphia i'm sorry we missed
it on the bang bang tour i'm
gonna make up for scott sins yeah
do you think i'll go to hell
because of that
there's so many things going to help
i mean you absolutely have fucked up
in so many other ways i got
to read the fine print do you
think god is playing a trick and
hell is actually heaven because it's so
easy to get into and he's like
i want you guys to be here
what if this is heaven heaven is
hell
alright we'll see ya bye bye
ugh