three
ah
um three of them
loran the first episode of the new
year i'm so sorry
oh the light accept your apology i
would have made it up immediately and
admitted then a man my name is
paula todd hi my name is scott
aquaman my name is la rana la
ca
that is lauren that's not bad for
your production company card and when the
owner of your shop doe
like imagine ah like monks singing it
you know yeah we're like mom ya
screen hakan all of us it's like
one of those filters where it looks
like a hundred people but it's just
one person and it's holly and i'm
making her mouth go oh mo
mangos were here it's a new year
and we're still us this is but
we're gonna be so different this year
do you guys have resolutions oh no
we talked about this in an early
episode do we have new awareness in
ah in an in recent episodes know
but but like if novell
members something like four last year yeah
like an in season one we talked
about reservoir yeah now now i suppose
so yeah right i can't believe they're
repeating topics i got i got to
work on new things i just love
the whole thing this isn't a repeated
topic this is a new topic what
do you want when you want to
do in the new year my main
goal
goal is to work on my fitness
okay i wanna get back into exercising
regularly i'm already doing as much as
i can at this moment but i
know that in the new year when
i have more help it will be
better do you think google's going to
become outdated and there's gonna be a
new thing that we all talk about
when you say google you're going to
sound old yeah but it'll be a
baby wound and it'll be called gugu
nets good time
it's got no time
you ever totally asleep or whatever myself
good grand baby i mentioned because google
i wish i could sleep twenty four
hours a day watching you just put
your brain in a jar but then
like do stuff i wish i could
put my brand and turn be like
hey good looking i'll be back to
pick this up later yeah and then
come back like twenty years from now
and be like hey i'm
here from my brain i would like
to put my brain in a jar
but i also like would like to
see it in the jar and i
don't know if i could do that
if the brains in the jar but
what if it you like your brand
because he's still receiving transmissions so you
could well yeah like your brain is
still working it's just resting okay let's
see what brain oh what's the point
ain't that you get to feel like
you're sleeping what you're doing stuff so
what two brains yeah walking around and
shit yeah two brains you have a
backup brain that will register sight in
those like you know any sort of
ah transmissions and stuff
so that's enough for you to see
that brain in the jar but it's
not where you have to think all
the time that's all i want and
then righteously um speaking of two brains
do you remember how we used to
think or maybe that we were told
that dinosaurs some dinosaurs had two brains
do you remember that i remember like
having to you
spring
ah ah wait like they were too
like they were two nuts like to
like um no they were not side
by side chestnut i don't remember like
there they had one in their head
and one in there bud or something
yeah like go it's in their spine
of their tail or something really remember
that yeah i remember hearing that when
i was a kid you know what
kind of not all dinosaurs but
certain dinosaurs like stegosaurus oh the double
dinosaur brain myth
yeah for decades popular articles and books
claimed that the armor plated sega sores
and the biggest of the sauropod dinosaurs
had second brains guys so many ads
are popping up oh guy
it's for real
i clicked out of it so i
don't know what's going on alright second
brain okay second brains and their romps
these dinosaurs said couldn't there lady lumps
these dinosaurs huh it was said could
reason a posteriori thanks to them extra
mass of tissue it was a cute
idea but it's totally wrong hypothesis that
actually underscores a
different dinosaur mystery do you want to
know what that is yeah you may
as well here's where the dinosaur brain
expert emily buchholtz outlined the double emily
bought holes like the double brand new
lead published second edition of the complete
dinosaur the idea stems from the work
of nineteenth century yale paleontologist on
f neil charles mom sorry did you
say a yelp paleontologist yale but paul
i think you should use the name
auth neil as one of your characters
so funny you'll
in an assessment of the sauropod camara
cyrus marsh notice that the amount of
vertebrae over the dinosaurs hips and large
to an expanded canal that was larger
than the cavity for the dennis brains
the brain this is the most suggestive
fact he wrote and according to buck
colts and eighteen eighty one more skillful
described a similar expansion
and the neural canal stegosaurus is a
posterior brain case okay but can we
just talk about how her names like
avid hole in she's his name is
off neil it's crazy because we still
go out every year it feels like
they're like this dennis who actually was
covered in feathers and we yeah yeah
i don't know showers doing something or
maybe some of
fur we were taught about that yeah
they're going to find out is that
there's no such thing as dinosaurs and
the earth is only five thousand years
old yes i love that you guys
believe that thank you it's so fun
to show different perspectives what i remember
as a kid thinking how good they
have if they had two brains what
would the other brain
yeah what's the other brain controlling yeah
and now i'm relieved to find out
that it doesn't make any sense and
of course it enough to brains is
is the size of the brain the
thing that makes you smarter because that's
what i always heard his motion of
the ocean
but i had always heard like oh
dinosaurs yeah they were big but they
had tiny pea-sized brains that's why they
weren't smart
almost fine yeah i thought they were
willfully ignorant
they were just like i don't want
to learn this yeah just wanna go
see an effect highly common sense
i got a lot of dinosaurs sense
i never heard their brains were that
small i don't know why i heard
that but i did and i couldn't
tell you why but i could tell
you that there is no clear correlation
between absolut early brain size and intelligence
assuming that absolutely brain size decisive for
intelligence than whales or elephants should be
more
intelligent than humans and horses more intelligent
than chimpanzees which definitely is not the
case yeah oh fuck sorry horses you're
damn dunk i saw a roast or
video of this elephant doing a show
i saw an elephant elephant doing a
joke this hand took the hat off
the woman portrait
both and then she's like you may
have that anyway and put her back
on her head i challenge him i
tried to enjoy a similar thing like
that where an elephant played a little
prank on somebody might have been the
exact same thing some other one after
i saw that spicy nolan and then
of course a bunch of people are
like that elephant has been cruelly trained
i knew that had to be the
fucking deal
i can't remember that video and socks
we've right it's like i yeah of
course elephants aren't just going to naturally
do that i guess but it's still
i thought it might be smart enough
to do that i think they're smart
we've talked to like elephants we talked
about the video about the elephant backing
up and the guy sweeping his cage
and we talked about that
that doesn't mean guy guy sweeping up
the elephant's cage he's just minding his
own business this elephant backs up in
the guy's head gets stuck in the
elephant's butt hole we never talked about
this okay so it sounds like colts
and backs his buck colts up in
this guy's head gets stuck in it
and he pops it out in immune
really bars
ah sassy
i mean that makes sense i guess
i mean i do if we've talked
about elephants i've definitely said this but
i just always remember and this isn't
as good as that by any means
but when i was little i went
to the zoo and they had a
video the elephant was the elephant cage
was empty at lincoln park zoo and
then there was a small tv hanging
in the corner of the
cage and it had a video playing
over and over of this elephant giving
birth and the the elephants come out
in a full sack and then oh
wow
and it just plops onto the ground
maybe that's it but i did think
about that when i was in labor
because there was a point where my
water hadn't broken and they said the
baby can be born with the water
being broken then i was like wow
like oh yeah i forgot what the
term is yeah for that there's a
classic term it's crazy to see a
video of a human baby with that
where they did the sun doesn't break
whatever and they come out
and then they pop the second on
the baby's ah
a way with they just had a
tv in the zoo so yeah zoo
for tds yeah one way to get
around oh life like animals must be
so expensive yeah just jeebies i mean
but tv tell you how small the
spaces are for the animals actually yeah
you're an adult and you realize like
oh they didn't have more room back
there and this is
actually really sad like when the like
bigger bigger cats are like pacing back
and forth like oh dressing room i
remember going to i used to love
going to zoo when i was a
kid philadelphia zoo all zoo in the
country went to the la zoo and
it destroyed zoos for me forever yes
like the like there is no philadelphia
wonder is it really cool because it's
old and have a made a lot
of improvements i mean like i haven't
been there in forever but i can
tell you i remember going in the
reptile house and there was a big
ah sea turtle who was just like
pressed up against the glass like throw
my house right out of the water
yeah he's put him up
glass
tits up yeah and it was just
like well that can't be this as
this animal's not thriving right yeah i
remember like at the lincoln park zoo
there's a lot of gorillas and they
would there was always a moment because
a lot to you how many growers
is alive i mean i know that's
a lotta yard i think
in chicago i think that's a lot
oh so you'll know you're quantifying it
by location because twenty two is like
huge and twenty five twenty five to
me is like a lot of gorillas
but five items in three
but this gorilla would always go up
and bash his arms against the glass
sheet and when you're a little kid
everyone goes like run away and said
it was crazy and that's like that's
fucked up ultimately that's bleak as hell
away but should they what do you
want him to be like running around
on the five freeway
well i'd rather he didn't see alternative
yes either is on the five or
because he can't they they take him
to california but put them on the
five this man or be in the
wild or on the five freeway yeah
we do we have coyotes that are
like going through our yard a lot
we catch on the cameras and like
and i saw
saw them how many other day while
i was watching the one walking the
dogs like they popped out in front
of us um and i don't know
i mean it's like i don't want
them to be hurt but i don't
want them here it's like you don't
have to leave but you can't say
here you know and now it's like
um the earth is one big bar
but there's someone on the neighborhood
ah whatever it is store outcast yeah
that podcast um who's like they're beautiful
animals and she takes pictures of them
and it runs like fuck you there
is there's there's always in every neighbor
every neighbor has one the coyote choosy
like super freak yeah he's like
sounds wonderful creatures
look hey there they're in charge i
mean i'm not going to talk shit
about him because they're the bosses now
the coyote yeah yes coyotes are now
in charge yeah they're the captain now
they're the type to look at look
at them look at them they're the
captain now
where's that guy easy he was good
other movie yeah when like a big
award know you got no he's not
really any category award yeah oh scar
yeah where do you go yeah but
he didn't swim he should be around
he's great he should die this show
i did he should replace you i
still think i believe he was in
some other
movie that i saw poster for somewhere
he's the only acceptable ah substitute for
any of us if we ever get
i agree what about doctor hang us
nor from the killing fields what what
are you really okay he could do
it to any non actor who has
acted for the first time and did
a good job
replace one of the three images something
happen to it i love them
that's a really good rule and it's
a great thing a child actor a
baby actor whose interests including like like
people like when you say non actors
like do they have any show business
experience like they did one role and
then yes one one role and they
did really well and then that was
it
okay or a char child actor who
was very very good but got out
of the business before they became an
i saw like one of those like
charles cosmo i saw one of those
buzzfeed articles or maybe it wasn't buzzfeed
and i'm but some other place that
was like these actors did a great
job but then never worked again or
they walked away from show business
and then i click on it's all
people who obviously just couldn't get another
part you know like so now that's
nice you know it was like you
know someone someone had a minor role
in an in a movie that kind
of was popular but then they never
got another role again and that's like
just strangely we never heard from them
again just didn't want to do something
oh yeah the chart is like
like that and your own picture was
in there oh no i'm sure mine
is some weird shit like that now
lauren i'm i'm bait i'm click bait
i've been clickbait can't bring it up
again don't tag me in that shit
anymore i blocked people who tagged me
in that
including me here now in black area
especially
oh my god what i was going
to ask you something just a second
ago we were talking about the substitutes
forest the i'm the cat oh god
did you watch kramer vs kramer didn't
you say you're going to i have
not watched it yet no i want
to
i liked that movie i've never seen
it i don't think this is scott
and paul hasn't you could beyond the
episode and that i'm no i've never
been on that show and i've no
desire to there's no fall hasn't seen
or paul has seen there i know
we haven't had room for paul we've
had too many great guests like santa
claus and phoebe
oh okay um i i think that
that kid in that movie was very
good wasn't he that's what i was
thinking i was like who's that dustin
hoffman yeah he's a cool cool little
kid who gets divorced meryl streep is
out of the movie where dustin hoffman
slapped meryl streep like like ah without
god god's gonna screen yeah don't
tell me about it
i give a shit y la la
listening if you feel like slapping someone
in a scene should you be able
to know ah oh your kid went
on to do a bunch so this
is what was so funny because i
was watching movie to day i'm airplane
gingrich going
who is that kid who is that
kid he's from kramer vs kramer i
was watching sixteen candles he's also in
ah wow and i almost googled them
but i was on the plane so
i couldn't i never pay for wi-fi
on the plane i i used my
time off but it should be included
in planes it should be included yeah
candles should be at this time because
now it's like twenty dollars
like to it's my addiction that i
need to pay twenty dollars to go
online you know do it it's the
chasm between people who can't afford it
and can't is so vast it's not
like yeah it's not like it's easy
okay five dollars you can have wi-fi
it's a now it's a thirty dollar
thanks guys it's a should make sure
just here because then everyone would do
it and they get
more money i feel like hotels it's
gotten it's gotten cheaper or free now
yeah because it used to be like
oh well if you send your computer
and it's free but a wi-fi that's
technology that costs so much i think
it's like so rude to make wi-fi
costs something in a hotel that's like
just yeah really well also there
should be free wi-fi across all cities
as well why if i find any
free everywhere there there are certain i
thought santa ah san francisco rather had
that for awhile where it's like free
wi-fi across the entire city and they
were like the infrastructure was like that
yeah it's a great idea because it's
like
everyone needs it now and so there
shouldn't be you know a barrier for
people who have less money to be
online well i think i think we
should have to pay for everything because
it's the market the free market and
if you earn like cars public of
california then go right ahead but i
like to pay for things
if i get sick i want to
rack up thousands and thousands of dollars
i just pictured this being the quote
on the threesome tweet
and there's no context this is nothing
with no inflection no paramedical kidding yeah
sarcasm fun doing funny voice of an
idiot
oh i'm sorry i don't think i
was a real boy idea tone oh
oh you think your characters not nydia
i don't think my character characters an
idiot we just might care thanks i'll
have the highest intelligence the piracy that
is their character love exactly we can
disagree but i'm not going to insult
them
um let's say you bring
baie
and we're back and we're just talk
about things we would do listen pretzel
gang i'm flying tomorrow janie and i
are flying to south carolina and it's
a little scary because you don't you
don't lately one of the safer play
aces i've flown like a bunch this
month after not ever doing it for
the whole pandemic and i feel actually
okay about that experience you're not hearing
a lot about people getting sick on
planes mainly scary killarney kickoff all the
maskey weirdos who are like yeah i'm
wearing a song instead i got i
watched the most fucking annoying man
and yesterday or or away this was
a couple of days to me please
don't be me playing too hard it's
me isn't it hopefully something so his
name was scott paul
ou um jake p this guy so
like everyone in the airport is wearing
a mask except for some people will
pull it down just to be annoying
i think like if you're eating a
time but there's people who are just
clearly trying to not wear it yeah
but whatever once you're on the plane
it's enforced so but it's also suggested
in the airport and desired by most
people because there's a boy
million people walking around with their covert
houses but um this guy of course
he was one of yours guys he
was a fifty year old white guy
with oh ya oh yes people was
dying to know what was going
he came up so the whole line
is there and he kind of he
comes up and he's he's not wearing
i'm asking you he's already being an
asshole he walks behind a woman who's
like kind of blocking his way but
he could totally go otherwise things like
excuse me so she has like move
out of the way and he has
no masks or interface and then he
does like a couple things like that
never what's going on who the fuck
is this guy he's a couple of
comments like oh what's his fucking deal
and then he gets
what's this because he cuts in line
at a certain point but he's training
play like oh no you go ahead
but he's like do a big show
but i was you know he's not
wearing a mask it's like it's very
clear that you're doing something that you're
trying to make some sort of point
he gets the front and then the
the woman checking the tickets is like
sir do you have a mask and
he was like huh
and she's like nah she points her
mass and he's like oh oh yeah
yeah i do i mean he touched
his pockets when he finds it and
then he puts it on and i'm
like behind him going like i want
us i want to just go like
that was a really great performance manno
but almost like you didn't know about
the mask styles and was really good
oh my god and so then i
am
like i'm sure i'm gonna be seated
right by this fucking guy and then
on the plane he is behind me
in the seat and he
has it on for most of the
fight i checked in a couple times
to see like it's going to be
annoying to check in yeah i just
learned iraq yeah you did not not
into it he couldn't tell he never
saw me and i was like i
was shoveling i'm looking over the crowd
or i'm doing like something where was
he directly behind you yeah but kitty
corner but in the same row yeah
sam yeah we all do this on
airplanes ch
check out the entire crowd
i had a dumb ass and he
was always looking down anyways phone or
whatever so it was fine but he
at the end took it off while
we were all still on the plane
and it's one of those things like
i just want to fight you you're
making me want to fight you because
you're caught you you clearly want to
fight people like you want to have
a problem and it also was one
of those things he had a big
giant
zit on his face i wanted to
go you know we wouldn't have to
see the zit if you put the
mascot like you like you have a
perfect out for this fucking zit
but anyway
i just was so annoyed i'm like
i hate people who are trying to
make a point with it's like just
yeah it's the same to hear someone
say someone say you're trying to make
the point by wearing it i'm just
trying to get to my next destination
but the final destination the ah shoe
thing though i feel like i've seen
things online where people will say that
people did
protest taking their shoes off in the
same way people are protesting masks yeah
don't remember that yeah i saw at
least one picture of that um but
but it's it's like everyone does that
and that's even dumber man that was
so before we got tna pre like
that was
it was so demoralizing because i feel
like i was traveling so much at
that time when they used the shoe
yeah you're sitting around your stocking feet
and it was like taking my bell
off taking my shoes off and and
it just felt like you never take
your mouse talk before huh you didn't
have similar where i wear it all
day long but i'm pleased to note
was not a belt list
individual lord before that incident you didn't
have to take your belts on nine
eleven i don't i don't remember when
you when you fly when you flew
all you had to do is walk
through the metal detector that was it
yeah yeah but it was like meyer
belts a thing
service shows up as like some things
on your yeah something's on your wheels
auto erotic asphyxiation don't do it in
the yeah they're like hey you can't
jerk yourself off to death on our
flight you can't get upset when you
walk through this line
do it on the early oh you
want nice try to take
yeah the first michael out to three
bad comes through here
um i i but it's also a
time where it felt like it was
just tense like the asap right was
scary everybody was tense it was scary
but it was also like i don't
know like there was a there was
a rudeness there was a dehumanizing aspect
to it where the the tna people
were treating you
i guess that they were instructed to
treat you that way that it was
very like it wasn't it wasn't pleasing
thank you you know it was not
it was not like human to human
contact it was like anytime i would
go into the airport it felt like
i was at the receiving end of
their irritation for months at that point
yeah and it was my first time
in the airport
and they would be like god it's
been five months of me having a
yell at assholes like you yeah you
know who don't know what you're doing
and it's like this is my first
i don't know what i'm doing because
you haven't instructed me kind person yeah
it was a drag it was but
at least now everything's cool and good
i like how everything works very cool
and good i think things are great
the way things are now and i
like your ssn hour i like now
what we say for a while yeah
yeah i agree this is great i
don't want it to be tomorrow night
at least yeah just see in the
now it should be known tonight what
was the what was the eagle eye
cherry save today save to that i
thought was stayed tonight oh i remember
when my arm hurts i got my
booster
i just remembered my arm
my incredible notice so there was kind
of sore but i wasn't thinking about
i was like yes or when did
you get it you got it today
yeah four hours ago and you forgot
you forgot already why is my arm
sore i did forget but i'm so
in the moment with you guys you
know yeah yeah that's what that's what
we're talking about and that's why we
want to say to all of the
people out there is like be in
the moment this year
our guys yeah donated like we it
can be so tempting to be like
oh i'm worried about one minute from
now or remember that thing i did
one minute ago that was so embarrassing
it's like notes it's now it's not
a minute oh don't get don't get
dragged into the quagmire of one minute
ago and don't future trip about one
minute from now yeah
don't you wish you could forget something
embarrassing you did one minute ago
yeah
the would i know we've we've talked
about this if you could forget something
you would write most things yes yeah
i'm just gonna lie and things people
places yeah ooh i would jettison a
lot i love my oh my god
eternal sun shining i got a couple
i love you
wouldn't you want about you got wouldn't
you think so yeah i mean there's
certain things that pop up that i'm
but here's the thing if you forget
about those things you might relive them
or you might relive them or it
might it might chip away at the
the person that you are now because
even gotten no experience
nsw
yeah that's true
yeah like anything bad happened without having
to look cooler that you wanted to
forget then yeah he did forget it
that he might not have empathy towards
people who experienced that bad thing or
something i sometimes wonder like if i
if i hadn't had the experiences that
i had when i was younger would
i have ended up in common
a i know i know what i
mean i think it's better like if
you had to relive your life you
should just do a totally different one
i think i want to forget anything
i wouldn't want to forget anything i
mean there are things i would forget
i wanna forget i guess but i
wouldn't want for anything from childhood cause
i feel like yeah that shapes you
but then there's a couple adult things
that
like it'd be great to not have
experienced that or not remember there are
some ah things in people's childhoods that
they know i'm saying for other no
apps i'm saying my own i don't
have anything so tragic that happened to
my my childhood but my yeah you
were a babysitter now your movie star
well they were unpleasant and bad experiences
and you paid for your entire college
experience yeah you gotta seventy five dollars
a week for my grandma not my
champion ray my dead grandma
i'm just saying i my my stuff
is more focused in my twenties and
thirties and i did buy the i
did work the entire time i was
in college as well do you know
where i hear somebody biology's you're fine
just brought that up everyone has been
drag me down i later i worked
a bigger square we've gone through all
of them well
we can do this where a restaurant
don't address the invent the investment for
right remember with bill murray's brother
i understand of course people have bad
things happen in childhood i want more
and i also i would highly what
i meant yes i would keep my
the unpleasant childhood stuff over the stuff
in my in my twenties and thirties
yeah it's it's your choice scott you
wanna go to your childhood stuff for
your twenty and thirty stuff but but
the things in my
twenties and thirties were all my fault
mine weren't
i to remember anything in my childhood
other than just like random statues every
once in a while you know it's
like random snatch oh no that was
random snatch ah you don't remember your
childhood know i remember certain things from
it but yeah i don't know oh
guys i had crazy dre
team last night oh do we want
to talk about this can't wait to
hear it it's a boundary is it
time is it time for the segment
dream depot is it about us no
it was not about losing someone we
know let me do the intro to
dream depot okay good will folk sure
about that time that threesome trains got
to take a loop shops the dream
depot
oh wait on second pull out ah
like
ah polish just screaming it's job you
take a loop a little shop at
the dream depot
hi guys like good blocks around depot
okay so i'm not gonna say who
it was but i'll tell you guys
later
i was gonna help inform the drink
he tells now and we'll cut that
no put it in the chat i
will put it in the chat um
but it's a person that i saw
last night for the first time in
a while so this is why they
were on gel i'll say so she
because yeah that's germane to the story
i said jermaine jackson
i was like where's your missouri okay
i have the name okay so i
saw this person and it was this
thing where we were working on an
award show i remember in tall john
was the head writer and i know
this because like they got the they
got the ratings immediately
they got the ratings immediately you want
show of the award show and came
over and told us well yeah there
was a little slippage ah you know
from last year but actually you guys
did a really good job and it
seemed like we retained a lot or
you know whatever and then i turned
to this person and and she's like
well that's good um can i go
have my baby now and
it turned out she was pregnant
and so we were like leaving the
shrine or wherever the award show was
and i'm like about to part company
with her and she goes oh but
don't you want to see me give
birth and i was like oh okay
so i go i go
to her house where she's she's already
to give birth and then they like
open up a flap in the stomach
and like like part it like this
like it's two saloon doors in a
in a old western town and there's
an eight year old inside
and i'm like wait was this baby
in you for eight years and it
was like no that baby has been
outside but we thought it needed a
little more time inside because to develop
so we we put it so we
put it back in and now now
it's already and then they pulled it
out of the stomach and then these
ah yeah and it was eight years
since anything i don't know
also means i saw this person last
night for the first time in a
long time but yeah but there's a
lot of metaphor
that i think until do you think
you're that eight year old baby
lawrence yeah yeah
oh this question for the room
for the tabe
what do you think what do you
think that metaphor is lower
i think two things one it could
be you thinking about you know your
plans for your family and the things
and maybe you've been thinking about this
for a long time so it feels
like a eight year old child
or it could be that you want
to see a little kid burst up
ah
ah that could be yeah is joe
rogan everybody joe is joe rogan um
anyway for the first time in a
long time
how did you feel when you woke
up ah well it was one of
those dreams well first of all okay
it was also i saw this person
at a party and and we had
you know how you have very vivid
dreams when you drink quite a bit
you know what i mean and it's
like you're not sleeping all that well
because you're sort of like going to
be hung over and your dehydrator or
whatever and
and yet you're having these vivid ass
dreams that you remember it was like
the first thing that i thought of
when i woke up and i was
like oh that was weird but it
all made sense of course when you're
a time of like oh yes of
course well if a if a if
a person is is not developing correctly
put them back in the womb yeah
i don't want to sue because god
you don't want to see my saloon
flaps open
and and an eight year old child
come out and you want them to
be outside when they're not ready yeah
exactly so anyway back in
well about time we got and along
glad we could stop at dream depot
that's a really nice whistle thank you
now what's the story about that whistle
um i wanted to get one and
i o
great story but there's probably more to
ah i was thinking for my come
in handy for a live show or
something i love it thank you i'm
shaking it i think it would be
good thanks i think it'd be good
on moon because well eve yeah my
when my family's listening to the polar
express to toot
when they're listening to your family listen
to them go to a audio table
now we found it on youtube because
it was a book first right yeah
but there's an audio cassette to listen
to on christmas eve that was read
by william hurt the polar express children's
book read by william the warmest person
i can think of as his voice
it was yeah
um no and it's great it's great
but then we there's only a liam
neeson version now and it's it's not
as good really i think his voice
would be cool to be taken bundles
yeah i know there is it is
on youtube but said william hurt just
wants to get to your liking but
it's a really sweet story
when read aloud now holly's gonna hear
it for the first oh last night
it's her first christmas and of course
this is the new year for us
it was her first christmas score said
miura is her first christmas it's the
day where we're recording this the day
you're listening to it
we're recording right next to you that's
what we do every time mids live
is a call in
hello
yes hi three-day run the oh sorry
i was just on paula poker i'm
talking to someone hang up yes right
click yeah this is freedom yeah there's
a rod district high rochester you're in
rochester your name is rochester rochester
okay yeah are you in rochester your
name is roger chester rodney gesture nah
your chester yes what's up
no u
probably
yeah he's like a guy ah man
he got it
roz roz chapter
um what does that make you think
did did nothing did you guys have
an every i know we left dream
depot but
do you have any dreams
i have dreams all the time and
i had a i had a dream
last night but sometimes i don't quite
remember them when i wake up but
i mean i know the feeling and
i too tend to have a lot
of dreams that are nightmares about a
certain person in my na me know
that i won't get into it here
but
oh i have like really stressful nightmares
that's what i guessed
ah they're bad i feel like my
dreams have gotten weirder in the last
couple of years i don't know if
it's because of because of quarantine just
because of how weird everything is but
i feel like they've gotten especially weird
and to the point where
i sort of i remember them much
later like just parts of them as
if they were
like memories of life instead of memories
of a dream do you know any
yeah i'll take you you've dreamed everything
that you've already dreamed already so you're
dreaming new things sorry what
lorna makes perfect sense you've dreamed everything
i dreamed already dreaming evening everything i've
already dreamed already so now i'm finally
dreaming yeah okay
oh i dreamed i already dreamed up
my allotted dreams and oh look now
i mean like overtime that's your see
now this is where it gets money
this is where yeah okay here we
go we're working overtime
um i still buy the way you
know the dreams i i've had about
the house that i added to the
two houses that i'm always in i
still haven't yeah haven't those still having
those dreams yeah it's i'm still having
those but i don't think you're the
only one i think gen jacqueline novak
i wanna say had this discussion on
puig
podcast i enjoy um come out her
poo yeah oh cool backward everyone wow
spell backwards it's capable and jacqueline novak
um oop use what you're trying to
say and and um and i
anyways i think she has had dreams
like that where she's walking she's in
the same house over and over again
that i will say the one that
i same house that scotsman it could
be could be oh man i'll look
for that wow yeah they'll look for
it's been it's been upgraded now to
where it's it's been upgraded it's
it's been upgraded i was aware it
looks like those guys it's been a
really nice area now which is great
oh no it's like an a really
nice part of town and it's right
over on george jefferson so that's not
bad but i'm not able to bet
it's now bad not able to sell
it though you're trying to sell it
i'm usually
we trying to sell it lately
guys that's kind of like yeah it's
like i'm it's it's it's a house
that i'm trying to get rid of
and i'm like showing it off usually
and i'm like oh gosh it's this
is messy own this room obviously is
is a problem yeah you know there's
only stairs or there's only like a
rope ladder to get to this room
unfortunately
oh that kind of thing and but
you can work around this right
that kind of thing i'm sorry i'm
so sorry that happened to you sorry
guys i really appreciate your support in
this terrible hi i'm sorry i haven't
had a recurring dream i used to
have a recurring dream when i was
a kid it was like a recurring
nightmare that was like a straight-up like
a dream about a monster you know
what i mean and i can't i
i
like i feel like i had a
almost a full week every night i
had the same dream and then it
never happened again and i never had
a recurring dream since oh my god
i remember when i was i think
i must have been twelve eleven or
twelve i had the scariest dream where
i woke up and was just terrified
and i went into my mom's
ah bedroom and i was like i'm
so good to bedroom
when i went back into her stomach
it's like ten shots i thought about
that oh that's right i'd never put
that together
no i went i went i had
to have been ten or something and
i went into i went into her
room and i was like terrified and
i was just shaking and i'm like
i had the worst dream she's like
ok come sleep with me and we
added a church picnic the next day
because there was a labor day picnic
every year and my mom told that
story to like some people
at the church and i was mortified
and just embarrassed because i was too
i was too old very embarrassing yeah
and i was like why would you
tell them that because like you know
why would she it's very weird i
don't know well she probably cute pussy
who came back to bed last night
because he had a scary dream is
made up ahead maybe she'd
heard that ah people talking about their
dreams is boring she's like i'm gonna
talk about his dreams that will be
interesting for sure did you find dream
depot boring call i never did i
look i one of the people i
liked your people's dreams if they have
a weird dream i like to hear
it it's like that's all just because
your dream doesn't make it uninteresting no
that's true i think
you have a problem we've started to
say like that people should never tell
their dreams because of that like it's
kind of become this thing of like
you should literally never say that you
had a dream yeah i mean it's
very foundation the dream depot was based
upon i tell you what i wouldn't
have dreamed depot if we didn't have
dreams dreams didn't exist there would be
no dream depot i thought
think my rest my case yeah if
dreams didn't exist there'd be a dream
depot which means thusly you would never
have bought the train whistle which you
never would be able to use and
no one have ever invented trains if
i didn't have this train whistle dream
depot never would have happened ah yes
thank you um but i think that
yeah i think it's become
thing i would rather hear somebody describe
even a boring dream than somebody telling
me something in a really exciting thing
that happened in real life yeah i
don't want to hear anything real exam
got your ride my bike that's exactly
what i
i would rather have somebody describe a
dull dream to me then tell me
what they thought something said when they
first looked at it i hate that
well that to me is like that's
just in your head that's not that's
only amusing tuesday that it didn't mean
anything to me when yeah that's what
you thought it said it doesn't say
that i've had that experience where i
thought
something said something it didn't say and
then it was amusing to me it's
not abusing anyone else i know it's
not i will say when someone miss
hears me and repeats back what they
heard in their laughing i just go
yes what i said yeah
they just think i said a different
thank you if they think i said
like a different joke that i said
but it's like actually better than what
i said and i'm like yeah well
sure i thought you meant any time
someone this years you know like if
i'd like to repeat and i'm like
that wasn't exactly it but that's fine
i dated a woman who was really
upset showing ah her ex
a boyfriend who would read every every
billboard that they ever passed when they
were driving that's so annoying
that's like a disorder just like because
it was so boring and just trying
to fill the time just like yeah
oh my god get a personality are
you talking to me yeah shut the
fuck
random person oh thank god no but
like the billboards because you're so bored
like just take something to talk about
our own talk just shut us it's
when people are that uncomfortable with silence
it's very um it's it's it's hard
to deal with i bet he wishes
that they had podcasts whenever that happened
right
you know what i was thinking oh
you're uncomfortable silence israeli sad is it
sounds nice
thinking silences during a recording it's weird
i was thinking today as i was
listening to doughboys i'm so happy i
guess that all of our funny friends
have podcast because people get to hear
how funny they are and they get
to like i just love that yeah
and i was i mean you know
there's a whole tr
trend right now with like extremely rich
celebrities having podcasts that doesn't interest me
as much but i do like how
people that would just be performing extremely
rich ex babysitters i'm not extremely rich
and you are so be quiet
mt yeah you're the last to be
joking about that
but i'm indebted to my eyeballs guys
do a poor season today so they
keep to hustling that i fed that
house in my dream because they really
gotta make some money on that house
metro
anyways whatever fucking should i give a
compliment to the world i was trying
to say it sounds i listen it's
not just big it's round i tend
to listen to podcasts that are hosted
by people i know and i love
live sometime because i feel like we're
hanging out with and i was thinking
about how nice it is that people
get to experience everyone's personality and how
funny they are like the doughboys are
so funny together and they have such
a huge fall
knowing and have so many listeners and
it just really nice it is so
funny to me the way mitch is
on that podcast because my experience with
him before i started listening to that
was always he was always very meek
with me and very like nervous deferential
definitely yeah but i didn't realize that
i thought that was just his personality
then i hear him
tearing into nick wider on that show
like oh okay i get this now
yeah
well um yeah you hear paul's actual
personality when he's off my keys so
me can he's so like please thank
you sir thank you may i turn
on my mic now sir
very shy we actually edit out what
he does between everything he says he
goes am i allowed to speak now
we have to go yeah because anyway
i'm such a fig and i know
it's a pain for the editors and
i know it's hard for them to
catch everyone we just said to do
one right there thank you talking okay
i'm not editing that one out
i think we have to take a
break
and we're back and it's time for
feature and it's time for richer because
we're back this sweet will come back
we wouldn't be doing three-tier woodwork is
absolutely true yeah this teacher is called
across to cut across to cut across
the stick across a classic papa lips
oh god what it's like acrostic and
across the apocalypse but it's one work
across departmental by john cassidy contestants must
think up acrostic poems on the flood
that described the plot of a movie
using the movie title as the spine
of the poem
example citizen kane crazy infamous tycoon irritates
zen emotions not kosher abolishes newspaper empire
that's something that's so smart
we can be smart that is so
smart i think we can so until
think we should pick a movie that
you like yeah um okay i got
one
okay won and yeah and and are
you supposed to guess it or i'm
just supposed to do it good i'm
gonna do i'm gonna do mine no
you go first go for some ah
well guess it's guessing we're still gonna
kick it off yeah yeah sure i
think she's a figure you see if
you can figure out what this movie
is and by the crows supposed to
cut you off if
we figured it out or just were
no we now cut me off okay
sorry sir
jazzy animal was shark jaws ah you
guys i have one too boy is
grown big yeah i got one boy
it's i go in extra terrestrial e
t yes thank you yeah we all
thought of we
love really dumplings that's great
okay alright let's try to do ah
a harder one okay i'm gonna do
i feel like i need to write
down that's ok we allow pens in
every
recording session for three of them we
have allowed eight pens in his real
some time sure so scott i'm gonna
i'm gonna google good movies she's google
good movies good okay oh man this
one's awesome
lovely
ah godwit
um as it's hard lovely intelligent teen
tries
love
emotionally
mouth it is
oh no i don't i thought was
a little women i thought so too
mouth ever remains mum and is okay
done little mermaid moray that was good
mouth ever remains mum thank you like
it that sounds like a palindrome but
it's not
okay i got one
then haley
expect death
in our star games we play one
word story then then physically haley haley
expects seeing
ah in oh xylophones
i didn't think
and um then haley sees
expired nobody's seemingly everywhere hey pretty good
do you ever include the i i
did i did do the i yeah
okay kimber when you look confused oh
yeah i'm sick it was the sixth
sense of the sixth and haley joel
osment is who yeah oh but then
i got tripped up by the acts
there should be more words to start
with x you're right
we should start something about that yeah
ah my turn okay okay let me
think of a movie
goomba of death
fares
a terrible
heart
ah event
r i p
ah stopped god of war
it was it god ghoul goomba of
death fares at f ah yeah terrible
heart event yes oh that good yeah
okay that was hard i was gonna
i think it was alright i like
to
alrighty
i'm gonna try another one alright people
with the character and the actor that
that doesn't happen a lot no usually
a character lives on when a movie's
done actor exactly if the actor dies
but the character doesn't die in the
movie the character is still alive yeah
and and more movies should end with
every character die
dying so that it equals out just
to be safe yes yeah but unfortunately
most actors die before characters do yeah
yeah lawrence he's not a hardware i'm
gonna try this one okay let's see
man
man elicit engagement
then elicits engagement okay
though the
ah house
experiences problems as
i
meetha hapa
is it misshapen
neath it but um what's her name
recourse exists so you're just saying words
recourse exists i ordered it in peppa
brand never more thus
oh baby girls oh mr perez
alright i have one last one
killer never investigates viewing everyone seeing
ah opportunities underneath trains
knives out
saves
there had to have been a train
in that movie somewhere right i hope
so for your wish i wish were
i got again i haven't there was
a scene where a train you know
a train just kind of like just
really goes right through the house
if i were rich that's what i
would do i have a tried of
a train tunnel in my house so
like silver spoons no no no a
real train tunnel wow what full size
train with a smaller house um no
the houses even bigger
it's it goes right through the living
the dimensions on everything your blow on
my tug it's a thousand by a
thousand wow
that's did we do it than we've
done with the thresher sank we do
and i think we did it nothing
we did it i think possibly we
did that now i can have a
nice nine pm dinner like i'm in
france
this is freedom after dark in um
that's what makes it so racy this
this i think this is the perfect
episode to to to kick off the
year i mean this is what twenty
twenty two is going to be all
about yes is people getting together and
twenty twenty two is all about
out them the human connection is what
twenty twenty two is now live podcast
go all over the world so i
have an instruction people all over the
world join hands yeah start a love
train love trump train yeah you know
what we're saying like a human centipede
of love
yes join hands but also have yourselves
surgically so natural literally you
who would see that movie why would
someone see it i heard about what
am i never see that well look
you gotta eat you know whatever yeah
you gotta yeah shit
okay guys you're i'm talking about something
serious and you're making fun what seriously
actors have to eat okay we can
make all the jokes we want
ah people that are in the movie
i think can't necessarily be identified as
that correct like you can't i was
that sure faces like they're not on
mtv i feel no they are but
it's like you would see somebody something
else say oh my god that was
like he was the middle of human
centipede oh my god i don't know
anything about it
it wasn't enough the salacious details that
we have discussed in our present should
that shouldn't have been allowed to be
made also you are here for censorship
interest of that movie yes i've just
so cool everyone's voice here you're a
human centipede cancel culture guides right i
have a single
cancel culture guy
i love that movie needs to be
recalled alright thank you for listening everybody
we love you still in the new
year we still love you we do
um three m usa on instagram and
twitter three m usa at gmail dot
com you can get our merchant pod
swag we've got some fun stuff in
the merch store stuff and tie crocs
by crocs even though they're probably
not sponsoring this particular app but if
they are they may never sponsors again
yeah you know us well let's take
the high road we're gonna take the
high road when they go low we
go high that's right no cracks no
matter what shoes are about as low
as you can get when it comes
to clothes that's true that's the truth
so
listen to us experience us and look
if you want to hear previous episodes
and you wanna hear these episodes ad-free
go head over to stitcher premium or
cb world dot com
you can't learn smelling her hair i
was feeling the edges oh okay you're
edging your hair i wasn't smelling my
hair i was feeling the edges
by everyone lie don't feel your edges
ugh