oh my
with the jaden they shall not be
assmed
sorry ah yeah um time my name
is lauren my name is paul my
name is ah it's ah it's something
else my name is poe my name
is paul i have a question i
remembered what it was yeah but i
have an issue i can't wait
you get doing okay run up and
do you remember when bottled water became
a thing yes i do because of
this and i was like i remember
it being fancy like there was evian
and then i remember now everybody has
it would you you were older than
me so what was that experience when
bottled water was like hey now you
need this and you have to
by the first thing that happened was
perrier and that was a big punchline
even though it was sparkling right like
what are you going to bathe in
perrier it's like so it's the bank
robbers bad show yeah it's like it's
water you're buying yeah but it was
because the idea was it was designer
water
then when bottle water came out it
was because i was i was starting
standup at that time like late eighties
it was a huge punchline yeah everybody
had a bottled water bit about how
ridiculous it was and then channa lindy
you guys well know what you mean
in the study they turned up the
terror
well ideal i don't but at the
time there was a lot of problems
with fucking water and just how but
were they just what were the problems
it depends on the city pigs read
read an article about how in los
angeles ah there is a campaign to
try to ah teach the citizens especially
people in lower income areas that the
water here is actually safe yeah from
the taps and it's not going to
kill you yeah because
because people are spending a lot of
money going out and getting bottled water
that they don't need when in l
a it's like it it's fine you
can it's not like maybe the country
that you came here from where the
the water is not safe the water
here is safe and you can you
don't have to spend all your money
on bottled water although when i moved
here i was told you know the
water is not good to drink railing
the town i thought that too because
i i was so in chicago it's
good and in new york it was
supposedly really make me suh dad and
i know when i move wow lay
it was like ooh i don't want
to drink this water yeah but it
was just like some sort of preconceived
new ships in my head though now
we're like say if i drink too
much the night before and i'll
wake up with like oh i need
some water i'll go i don't want
to go all the way upstairs to
our like our big you know we
have the filter the dispenser thing you
know like i don't want to go
all the way upstairs and i have
to think to myself there's a bathroom
right next to you idiot just like
go drink some water yeah and so
yeah it's fine it's fine to drink
but i think it used to be
bad and i think that david i
think that they've improved it but do
you think that they were just trying
to cash in like these companies were
like k na is like so fancy
and only like rich people have those
my perception and that then like oh
what if we make these other brands
cheaper than other people will buy water
too and it'll be like less of
a class thing yeah no now so
many people buy
water that it's weird to drink it
out of the tap yeah when i
saw it i mean this this could
be fake but i saw on that
penelope that penn and teller show bullshit
they were they were sounding way i'm
sorry but bull crap thank you they
were um showing the most companies just
like can't go out of a hose
and just like
pour it into
pour it into the bottles i really
resent like having to buy bottled water
like in the airport or places where
it just feels like you have but
see i i i always carry a
collapsible water bottle collapsible yeah my problem
is i carry these big ones but
then like all sam do huh i
carry these big ones wow yeah to
not when i get
not me in my bag it's the
guy's annoying you have ruined we ruined
you
tract away what makes you you and
we've gotten to the degree in essence
aren't actually yeah
huh
i have the airport my body is
my body's made up of like seventy
seventy five percent water so i just
cut myself open and just just drink
for months ninety really you can you
can hear me when i walk in
your water god yeah but but when
you fill up at the airport you're
that's tap water knowing that they have
those machines sometimes at the point where
it's like
a water refill machine but not every
airport has that i also never airport
shut but i've yeah i've done it
from the omen we try to do
it from the fucking water fountain oh
boy drives me crazy especially there's two
side by side and then you're trying
to pull up your oh yeah jennifer
gordon oh the person next to you
takes a drink and then your water
pressure goes yeah it goes down no
let go
there's blows up in their face i
wrote i wrote ah got you a
thing when i was in fifth grade
i think where we all it was
a school project where we all had
your writing modesty infinite jest yes i
wrote it fitted just in the fifth
grade um no we had to write
like a letter to the principal about
something and ah
i think that was just any thought
it was like demands
more like a ransom notes that we
get out of the newspaper
but i don't remember why we had
to write this but i do remember
writing mine about the drinking fountains in
and how they should be fixed that
when someone turns on the other one
ah yours goes down so low that
you can't you can't drink out of
it anymore i remember the principal calling
me into his office to explain why
that was the case and how it
could not be fixed and i was
just like oh okay cool i mean
yeah you didn't care for real
did he close it out with so
we could know
you got a mortgage my sack jackie
yea that was so cute did you
say wikipedia was of data yes change
back i don't like people do joke
changing but i do want and i'm
gonna beg for this right now my
hands and knee alright daddy change my
fucking like a picture i had a
nice one and some old dude really
hideous one of me at a county
gaming show and there's no lighting it's
like pitch pitch-black
quick someone do that to me they
they took the worst picture that they
could find that was here's an here's
what i found out it's gotta be
a picture that someone owns that you
can say like ah this person trait
it's like traceable back you can't be
a random okay no so what if
it was from like something like a
photo shoot with it's labeled who took
it i think that's that's
fine but what they took mine from
like south by southwest like you know
photograph are no good pictures from there
yeah photographs yeah like uploaded to the
internet by the photographer herself you know
and the grossest picture and everyone who
writes me all the time i changed
your wikipedia page dude man is horrible
you're looking at it now i'm looking
for my
they were molly i finally got my
change because we finally lowers his nice
know i needed a good one this
is unfair and yours is nice down
so it was a nice when there
was a lot of the nose epic
battle or people were changing what it
said and saying that i was a
mermaid that was fine and then manga
changed a really good one that's really
good yes from a super ego show
over time mine has a boner venus
thank you boner time super boner for
my panties on your time remains my
piano when i have a boner for
my penis the butterfly piece is so
hot my picture used to be named
my this is giving me a boner
right now
so picture of my penis yeah i
saw victory computers give me a boner
boner those little months
my wikipedia picture used to be me
on stage and in the background there
are bottles of water on the stage
because there was a like a bunch
of water party it was a water
party whatever and someone i want to
tweet references of the we were talking
about
so that's not a reference to a
previous water from a little store in
the lady would say water party yes
anyway anyone who worked who walked by
the counter when we will buy a
bunch of bottled waters for a rehearsal
of the person either going to say
oh water party and then one time
one time one time i went there
and a guy
did it so perfunctory like i like
he had to these it's like water
break exactly what it was a rule
we don't wanna say water party waterbody
oh what about how to party it's
interesting when you talk to someone who's
been in not to interrupt your momentum
rapidly jam here but talking to someone
who has is d
dealing with the sun to eviscerate someone
dealing with the same people in the
same industry as you and seeing if
they act exactly like the way they
act around you and the the what
we just had a conversation with someone
who goes to the same ivf place
that we go to and i can
finally talk about this because cool
for your service there's no worry out
and
and everyone should watch co-ops movie and
you'll get the backstory to some of
the backs or there's more there's more
stories documented somewhere in sex life yeah
but um in any case we go
to the same idf place i was
like does the doctor every time that
you go into the room and shirk
off does he like shake your hand
afterwards and say good job he's like
yep
yes so it's something so weird he's
like and now you demanded of cool
hello my hand anytime he hasn't job
anytime he hasn't done it cool off
goes you do something wrong he didn't
tell you good job that is weird
it's really where does he ask you
which hand it's like he wants to
shake that shake the hand that shook
i want to shout cancer fund owner
shook that baby out oh my god
anyway you were saying so in the
picture you see some bottles of water
and i tweeted something about climate change
once and this guy is like
oh you care so much about gaia
j look at the bottles
and it was a real gotcha rio
gotcha and this is on stage that
someone just supplied them for you yeah
there were just waters near me like
you did when you do destroy that
i did drink all of the and
there on your writer that every show
you do you need four hundred bottled
waters yes and then the empty bottles
have to go to destroy turtles and
you re-enact roger dahl
ltrs the wall and you just break
through them roger daltrey is the law
isn't that who i'm talking about no
right what writers who i'm talking to
my daughter says roger daltrey from the
filters i thought but i was like
hey i get on the same side
we're going to him i get don't
bring waters confused i remember i went
i went to some
award show where we won this really
weird award for the mister show oscar
so weird i was telling someone about
i was like a man nin gold
i was like it was i mean
it was a weird award but it
was kinda cool because roger waters gave
it to us like you he was
the presenter whatever the inflatable pig award
but that's the thing is it's likely
it was the gooseneck upside down towards
gooseneck say i like taking it out
no way no pago real yeah that's
a real thing you gotta do thing
so we're not just crazy things i
thought that's what we were always doing
wait you guys have been lying the
entire time real story every story has
been another shit happen to me what's
cool i'm cool i love how does
a weird to me anyway i tell
it has happened to me i told
some of the roger waters gave us
the word
they were very impressed then i went
yeah the guy from the who and
then they were less impressed because i
feel like roger dalton your slaughter will
show up to anything weight which person
wasn't well rodda who will start daltrey
gave it on your tv but i
thought it was why i get those
two confused i said waters and they
were really impressed and then not impressed
have you ever presented an award show
yes me too me check me too
too i did it with a woman
from rizzoli and isles and we had
a lot of fun and that was
the only time i ever saw timothy
amundsen at the hair and makeup awards
oh yeah we're like yeah that host
daily introduced a bunch of awards though
i don't remember how it went
went well i think they probably mean
it went well but i don't remember
what was a bit wassup yeah that's
right yeah no it went really well
with so
yeah i had to do a a
comedic bit at a
a show called the young hollywood awards
oh yeah years ago i think of
young hollywood paul f tompkins i was
young then you fucking asshole you're also
very hollywood you you rude queen
so the title yes how do you
you ricky
and i had started to do this
bit it was presented by movieline magazine
oh remembers magazines and was that or
just just dumped a banana onto the
table like a resounding thud i'm trying
to get to the bottom of my
buying time for lawrence food i don't
get what little morals bad to get
my hand cream guy
get believe gloves everything to make reveal
fresh i'm glad that we are doing
this podcast because gives you a chance
to catch up on stuff like i
know because i can never get into
my bag because in a real show
you're like two on yeah yeah no
here i'm very lax if i did
this at any other show i'd lose
track i'd be horrible any other
we'll keep talking huh so the movie
line so i did i mean i
did my little piece which was god
it was like a kid writing a
letter to hollywood that i was reading
or something oh okay running i it
actually went over way better than i
thought it was going to go over
it was a very strange event right
but afterwards after
i was done and thank god people
laughed um isn't it weird how like
the few times i've done it it's
it's like i did at the emmys
night or not the emmys emmys but
the creative emmys well ron jimmy yeah
yeah and the and the and this
other whatever it was but it's like
when you hear that first laugh it's
like oh thank god
it doesn't feel like you're gonna get
a laugh at all no yeah does
not feel like it and especially like
in your reading like someone's weird scratch
yeah i mean yeah yeah both times
i like sorta co wrote it so
i was like i believe in the
bit but yeah but who like bits
that i like are weirder this what
this was terrifying because it was a
just a bit me doing a bit
that i wrote right and your solo
that's yeah
oh yeah and thank god it went
well and then afterwards i was leaving
and i saw fucking harrison ford standing
in the lobbies waiting for his girlfriend
to come out of the bathroom calista
calista flockhart okay and i i had
to and i walked up to him
and i said
mr fuck you
you know dare you take on solo
for me would you say i said
i just wanted to say i'm a
huge fan of yours your work has
meant so much to me for years
and he could not have been and
i was fully expecting this is going
to be awful but just going yeah
thanks
kid or whatever he was so fucking
night oh games like big smile and
shook my hand and i was like
what did he see you are doing
yet yeah yeah it's always the first
person who ever said that to him
it had been here
everyone thinks he won't want to hear
that i just think you're working seven
days seven nights so the guy coming
up wants me to build him a
cabinet
ah that's nice so we liked your
bed that's great like my bit yay
stamp of approval i could get danny
asked me if he should get an
earring and i said no and maybe
oh so he didn't really like any
yeah she put a dribbble up his
ass yeah joe i know oh come
on you didn't have niger i just
love that rumor
what a fucking crazy you love that
rumor be it about anyone anybody so
let's break it dare so this is
the rumor yeah if you if i
darted is richard gear may be transferred
over to rod stewart although they have
the ten cc's know you didn't really
yeah i remember sees yeah gallons of
cbse
in his house it is known the
stomach that says oh no the the
rumor their stomach pumped for having gas
said stomach pumped from like a like
a like an o d kind of
situation they found if he would just
rushed to the hospital rest of the
hospital for whatever reason they assume an
o d let's look here too much
semen
the fuck could that how is the
full half what would be happening for
that to be just that he had
a challenge where he was like all
i could think more semen than you
and there's no but i remember as
a child like no one questioned it
at all i believe that was just
like the physics of it like yeah
anything that's like you you wouldn't drink
that much fruit
a punch and have to go to
the hospital he just all like whoa
what's happened also how much to produce
that much yeah well i mean you
are we talking about over what amount
well that's the question is the one
guy over years and rod stewart shazam
big day where he was like yeah
he's a good job but it was
the game where the guys stuff finally
built up enough that he could do
the challenge where he drinks a whole
paint can of it
oh okay okay yeah it just looks
like prior washed out they tell me
who's got a screwdriver and then richard
gere time as i asked going on
a main know i heard though probably
in like the fourth grade or something
like that and it was covered in
the fourth grade to absolute certainty that
it happens and that this was
is something that they heard from someone
reputable yeah like well my my dad
heard it from this person or what
yeah you know is like he was
rushed to the hospital and a found
alive durable of his ass and then
i remember being like why well because
there's a certain feeling when it's up
there that that it feels good doing
a little claw
love scratching at your prostate soft tissue
so thick yeah but i like to
imagine a lot of people doing it
yeah yeah no i like to imagine
it that's for sure well like the
about the moment it got in there
like you can't really squeeze it so
it got really small gotta i don't
think lush it's rib cage i assumed
he put like some sort of bait
up there right oh like a little
hamster treat
because it's only a tiny sliver of
cheese like swiss cheese that holes in
it was like a triangle he just
shoves out there then he was like
you should get it here's what i
think he's just a wavy usable bike
and he's he's bringing about nearest malady
here's an example guys gotta get i
think he put it he made a
little doll of like a sexy lady
oh yeah like pepe le pew yeah
yes oh good jaw yeah she's got
this ah ha that's hot so although
the all of those rumors that seem
so ridiculous now like you've gotta think
ten percent are real
yeah what's like what what's like another
one that you guys remember i keep
like i can't remember anything besides those
are like the really big ones well
there was doing remember going to cc
but i remembered it don't say embrace
cvcc i call stephen sees sure it's
good to have a nickname for everything
wow look at all the cc
what are you saying it's all semen
cc so shit rose i want i
don't mother who would say the kunai
schettler can show my cc on you
oh just stop guide ccl this shit
all over the sushi it smells like
seafood
the ccw ah oh alright this is
the most juice heavy episode we've ever
done i think it's nasty it's this
is nasty this this is you you
are nasty and you are now you
are nasty asking anyways
well what i can't think of any
other rumors though i feel all these
rumors there was a rumour about mick
jagger and david bowie oh yeah they
that they're like maybe angie walked in
on them in bed like yes in
flagrante that was updated to tom cruise
and ah fuckin rob thomas from matchbox
twenty
yeah yeah that didn't match i can
see but
who comes up who's the first person
to say it and then how does
it becomes yeah folklore that everybody knows
how does who's the first person is
to just say jingle bells batman smells
that too there was no internet yeah
like it's like things it's like it's
like that article i read about grumpy
cat and how they stole all their
jokes for the grumpy cat meme from
ah fr
on this one cartoonist who's likely who's
like you know there's nothing i can
do that's different thing yeah like one
of the most famous grumpy cat memes
was directly stolen from what was asked
ah it's like i had i had
a thing once but i can't remember
i'm not a grumpy guy fan so
i don't know but be sad but
i almost waited in line to meet
grumpy
cat one time i was working at
work and they had a sign on
the street in new york just the
other day york city and they had
a sign that said if you meet
grumpy cat had a sign what do
you mean by like an event and
like you could get in line i
think i would've had to pay but
i was like sure you have to
pay to me grumpy yeah but just
because it was only on this earth
for seven years and us were doing
yeah so i didn't know it
i was so ill-fated he died of
grumpiness ah let's see scrappy cat has
died five hours oh wait five rosie
cat has done it just died today
yeah yeah yeah where you been i
don't i was doing podcasts and can't
do podcast while grumpy cat is ill
when i had no idea you were
saying they'd stay
i was like wait he just died
grumpy cat went into hospice care three
weeks ago oh no but i mean
back to the original question that's it
wasn't richard lewis really upset that everyone
says from hell yeah when he was
the guy who said that yes one
of the rare cases you can actually
point to and go there's no like
i made it up yeah well like
i had fun once it was awful
that's
i have a dream that one day
you'll shut up yeah i had fun
once it was awful that's directly stolen
from a cartoon that is not right
it's a victimless crime
save your favorite memes i just had
this popeye associating of creative themes collection
can go back to later should i
create a collection yeah but go back
to it later okay
cool wow
like did they give me that isn't
i don't know it was a pop
of my my brow say william caused
you to go back to later yeah
i'm like well i'm going away you
know i'm just actually is kind of
useful because like how many times we've
the three of us are a text
chain but we're also in a different
text chain and how often is it
like you know the perfect mean to
respond yeah and you
or like furiously typing it in to
try to get it in before someone
here's what i find it's a very
fine line between ironic maiming right and
genuine meaning well yeah and whenever i
catch myself wanting to reply with like
a reaction gif or something i'm like
right do i really wanna do this
right yeah my one of those people
now
yeah i realize i replied to someone
who was ah how can i say
this without giving away what i'm talking
about diving writers say
someone someone texted me and said i
won't even tell you the context was
like did did you plant the family
guy right and know plan i don't
i don't want to say why he
said it right so but and i
replied with a picture of the family
all i could think about but he
was talking about the guy who was
talking about family did you plant the
okay he was just talking about the
fam the guy talking but you reference
the family guy he referenced a guy
you didn't mean the family guy the
tv show he meant the guy who
got who was talking about family okay
so he's but he said the family
guy lower case and i responded with
a pic like a gift to your
moving gif of the family guy huh
and then he never responded i'm
i'd later i'm like he just thinks
that i'm like that guy tweeting him
family guy i'm sure what the gif
was because if it was like no
like he just thought you said no
right no it was just a picture
of the word guy i don't even
know who the family guy is but
peter's dad right oh yeah family guy
is i don't never seen it but
how do you not know he's the
future dad right yeah
yeah he looks like a dad or
when it was still ease the family
guy i don't they never he's a
guy's in the family is it going
to be like the walking dead where
like one episode they're like we are
the walking dead i am the family
called the family guy because it's like
supposed to be funny like instead of
saying dad he's like that pharisee a
guy who considers himself to be like
i'm a family guy
like family's the most important thing i
don't know i never seen it i
never thought about why it's called it's
just words put together you know somebody
shows just maybe it maybe it was
supposed to be funny like you know
a show it's like you know but
i mean the title awareness like how
family guy i actually i actually heard
it was a comedy who you hear
that from
two semis and in the fourth grade
alright we need to take a break
we'll be right back
and we're back oh boy yeah well
okay chase threesome huh you guys were
talking about other things that i couldn't
relate to and so i wanted it
to we're doing that sleeping paul yeah
you can't relate because you're a robot
you've never slept you gotta power down
my man can you
nap anywhere no okay one place
those are your options
either get on this table and taking
ap racing remote places i mean nap
right in front of us i used
to never nap i was i was
like truly like against them again what
do you mean you're against well like
i don't know my whole childhood i
hated falling asleep on road trips i
didn't want to miss anything and then
it kind of just became like i
don't what about at school like during
naptime and stuff you had phoned that
we were missing anything yeah as i
have a phone lol before it was
even a thing oh well for now
imo but when i was growing up
like i think when i was in
high school my friends would take naps
like people are just tired right never
not like at school but like you
know they could fall asleep in all
the day or something would you look
at my age i remember being in
class and like fighting sleep paul me
too i would
that was impossible but my idea of
taking ditches lord please but the idea
the idea of taking a nap i
don't think i ever did that when
i was young what about when you
are like in your twenties or thirties
because he be he would be a
dream oh my god i just feel
like falling for things that it was
weird that i didn't do but everyone
else was like just take a nap
you're tired right and i wouldn't never
do
doing it when i was younger i
felt i felt like it was a
it was a thing that you fought
you fought against being sleepy hey you
know you wouldn't know when you're when
you're a teenager aren't you like just
generally you can stay up longer whatever
i don't know more tired too well
you need more sleeping you need more
rolling anymore sleep yeah and yet they
wake you up to go
a school yeah exactly it's horrible the
hours i think we teachers leave those
kids alone roger roger daltrey quote roger
i find myself now whenever i need
to take a nap like my whole
body starts to go numb i don't
know what it's like huh sound good
does not sound good i just like
every my extremities or whatever start to
like tingle and just i'm just like
they're like fighting it trying to stay
up and then yeah they're just telling
me to go to bed so that's
weird but i mean you switch when
you're lying down or
you get one year which is like
walking around no no when i'm like
i'm on a couch or whatever like
i'll be watching tv or reading or
something like the other day i was
reading in the middle of the day
to two pm i was walking down
the street first as a pretty lady
i didn't know what to say and
i um i was just listeners trying
to read and i'm like i gotta
read this stuff for work you know
no and just my whole body starts
to tangle i'm like oh right this
is it
it was down for the count for
another ten hours you put on the
michael jackson documentary this is it
i was like alright this is it
this guy there is cancelled i know
um i feel like the best thing
by the way the first this is
the first time it's happened me recently
but a michael jackson song came on
my ipod the other day and i
couldn't enjoy i'm usually surprised that they're
being he's still being
i played in public places i guess
i just really felt like this documentary
was like this video yeah yeah yeah
and it was like why is this
whenever one i usually can be like
look into jam i go back in
time to like when he was when
i was eighteen yeah imagine them and
like my
boner
no i go back in time to
when i first tried this i'm dropping
being i can remember they'd never
and i liked the songs i remember
the day that i first heard you
wanna be starting something my eye this
was it had to be the summer
that my dad was in the hospital
so and i i stayed at a
lot of different people's houses that summer
because my mom went down there with
him so like all the people in
our church like took us in for
around night or for ah the driving
yeah
you can come to the bail jail
was full
i'm going to the hospital
it was the start of ah a
lot of his medical problems which continued
to use de chien yes um that
was nothing even not consist yes ah
so something he's been battling for thirty
five years or so ah but any
case so that summer i was shunted
around i just remember it so clearly
i were
was ah at ah these people's houses
and we were watching st elsewhere i
remember i remember i believe the i
think that i saw the finale of
st elsewhere with the snowglobe their wow
and i also they had a walkman
which i had never seen before and
they put
it on me and and they turned
on kiss fm which is the fm
radio station put did on you and
they'll have now listen to this and
they're gonna interrupt you wanna be starting
something came on and it sounded so
good and stereo in my ears and
it was like such a good song
and so anytime i hear that song
i don't hear it as a song
anymore i hear it as that experience
you know what i mean so
i don't know whether i'm getting all
the dates wrong and whether i was
at that place multiple times and and
those all those things i also remember
the rankin bass specials being shown so
it was sure would have been around
christmas i don't know in any case
that but i heard i heard wanna
be starting something the other day i
turned it on and i was like
and about i know something good about
it too much so i fast forward
who did not want to be starting
so i did not want any daddy
yeah rankin and bass lorin they made
they were the team the animation team
that made all those ah stop motion
oh um rudolph register fisher stuff like
that yeah year without a santa claw
yeah
every ur scary excited by them yeah
and similar to the popeye special which
i've probably told you about in the
popeye episode i don't know if you
if i told you about my special
cbs had ah okay so we've made
christmas special we didn't have a television
with tinsel
yum
we didn't have a television for several
years my dad ours broke out on
the street mean no charge culvert our
culver our color rivers travels you need
to get out there tingling or your
dingley our color tv crapped out and
my dad said you watched too much
tv so we're not getting another one
so any threw it away and so
for several years probably fifth grade sixth
grade seventh grade degree we didn't have
a tv probably those three years grade
eleventh grade twelfth grade thirteenth grade four
so i was really into popeye as
i told you before and i would
read the i would check out books
from the library of the old cartoon
on this character i was very excited
by the robin williams
xs movie popeye was two and i'd
love to be like that shelley duvall
care that would be so fun if
we knew remake that using a reboot
well i went to a different movie
oh what do i type character i
just mean like where you get to
be like a big character like that
where it's okay in a crazy costume
and like like a tim burton type
thing
oh yeah sure sure sure so the
cbs was having a animated popeye special
and i like begged my friend my
best friend can i come over and
stay over over your house on friday
i need to watch this popeye special
and we don't have a tv and
he was like yeah sure okay whatever
and i thought he would keep it
on the q t
but instead i get there and his
dad who like you know suburban dads
they're all like you know fucking judgmental
and stern racist so they i walk
in and he's like so i understand
there's some popeye thing you have to
see ah just taking all the fun
out of it oh yeah everyone always
popped your balloon i know anyway
minter said as a pup i fail
to see it'll pop i lover oh
my god finally got it did you
want him to do like hey boys
it's almost seven o'clock time for the
show
ah but he doesn't even know the
character just like he's like this show
has so many big muscles on it
i ah i like this show hey
this show encourages kids to eat their
greens yeah um yeah so we finally
got a twelve inch black and white
tv i begged my my parents inches
i'm not big no really that's what
she said oh dear
i'm in trouble then because that's all
i have
ah but i finally got a twelve
inch black and white for my birthday
in the eighth grade i believe in
zoo odd car
just like right now we go around
doing drive in your tiny one foot
okay we'll wait
yes what was the puppy special was
a christmas special no it wasn't that
it was just like an animated special
like like a thirty minute you know
pop i finally can't be contained by
six when he was around the ga
christmas special everything has that's usually the
extent news i just learned that the
ground welcome to earthquakes this submission i
just learned
to think there was a grinch halloween
special
hi somebody was on raceway tv i'm
trying yeah it was talking about this
um but that it was like a
halloween thing that was featuring the grinch
and it seemed really cool that's cool
there's a berlin halloween special that i've
seen on t oz it's really funny
it's there the paul lynde halloween special
is truly insane kisses in it yeah
uh
ruth vod from the white house gene
simmons why is he from the white
house he just was at the way
you gotta do what you do do
any podcast you gotta keep him lie
i'm actually trying to limit my social
dreamily not online i know i set
a limit and mike set the passcode
on it oh shit oh i can't
wow pass code and just go on
so but shouldn't you snoop around and
figure out the passcode no i don't
want you and you can make stuff
and no heat we made it up
each other's i made up his two
yeah and um it says you wanna
say on here no because he might
hear this set some how and how
much time did you get and how
much time does he get i get
an hour and a half on social
media but sometimes includes text messaging if
you're on the
a window of times it's really annoying
well especially with that especially with like
our tex chain where i will literally
do a show here and pick up
my phone there's a one hundred and
seven messages from you helping idiots but
like the and then i his is
i think an hour of ah he
uses twitter more than instagram i use
instagram including reddit
um we were right it is not
because he i know he likes reddit
does like right anybody might have even
delete and talks about it yeah you
deleted reddit yeah right at the time
suck but i sew for a franco
week i was using this system where
he had the code and i couldn't
get past it and it was really
good because i had to stop at
it even if i didn't use even
if
were you trying to manage your time
or were you just like blowing through
an hour trying to manage it it
was kinda nice i'd be like okay
i'll go in for a second i'm
a little bit bored it's closing because
i'm not there's no because yeah we
can't yeah but sometimes text messaging would
have eaten up some of my hour
and a half and suddenly i'd be
gone and then just go right now
i can't do it anymore and it
was really nice and then i had
to get the password from
because i had to post something there
was just a situation and then oh
it i became an addict again it
was unleashed i just was like oh
because you got the password and i
wish you and all the time and
it was gross and i kept saying
a new one because i don't like
this part of myself yeah right yeah
well these websites make us all depress
yeah and it's on them all i
can feel it when i let myself
go
back in i could feel my mood
shift with it and just if water
these idiots so much of the news
grumpy cat dies so well yeah it's
it's really it's it's a bummer to
read the thoughts of people who think
such horrible things like i'm not have
to like sit here all day and
be opening my phone mindlessly and then
reading some horrific new
new law and like i don't want
you want to talk about it but
i did i do this thing where
i should stop doing it but where
and i don't even want to say
what it is but there are certain
like hashtags where i i hate people
who post this hash these certain hashtags
so much like i go and block
them like i'll wake up i'll wake
not immediately after work
yeah but if i go on twitter
i'll be like oh let me search
that hashtag and i'll go down the
list of the six or seven people
you know since i last yeah i'll
just block them all you know because
it's like well that's interesting my fucking
hates people with their mentality and don't
ever want them to have joy and
not that looking at my twitter page
will cause anyone joy but i just
lie
like i want them not to have
things yeah you know like i want
them not to have access to good
things and if i can just start
with my twitter and that if they
never hear about my show they'll never
get insulin
right but it starts with you searching
who knows what the butterfly effect of
that is
yeah i actually believe it but i
find myself reading the things that's no
know and that's thing yeah you searched
out you yeah i'm mad again i'm
like these fucking nudes i was so
annoyed by all the game of thrones
tweets that came out a couple weeks
ago that i muted a bunch of
game of thrones terms and it has
made my experience but something i don't
care i don't need to see i
don't know what it means i don't
care tonight this is my
hot take on game of gowns okay
bye and it's over by now by
the time yes and i've been i've
been fine you have not seen the
final episode as of this taping button
but it will be out by the
time and no spoilers paul's not gonna
spoil yeah spoiler it's a quick introduction
by this time i will have watched
the first and last episodes were doing
it first but there we go i
at this
the point i'm not seeing anything but
absolut please i feel for all the
complaints about it and for all the
love from it people are very fanatical
about this show and it really means
a lot to them and it's people
that you that are normally not fanatical
about stuff like this that really get
into it complain about the quality of
it that the you know the last
season
let them down and wasn't as good
since this porn this this season is
war this port was based port was
be coy with the store
this poor winter dragon when it got
to the point with the rape and
pillaging um i think all the major
you're not far off
i feel that the quality is pretty
much a straight line all season with
very tiny ornamental down up and down
like but not not like a wide
yoyo ing know i feel like it's
always been about the same of a
show yeah i don't understand but at
the same time i understand like say
there was something that i loved dearly
like like i've given up on the
star wars stuff you know like when
the prequels came out i remember brian
hussein and i were around the same
age twenty eight or whatever and just
so mad at them you know and
so mad at george lucas i actually
literally gave away all of my anger
for star wars ah
the day that george lucas sold star
wars to disney and then gave away
all that money to kids or whatever
yeah like you gave away that billion
dollars or whatever to kids in need
or whatever i was like why have
i been carrying around such like weird
anger to george lucas for fucking something
i have the original three that i
like yeah who cares
and i like the new ones you
know fine or whatever so i like
i'm in a much better place of
like not blaming people for like things
are good things that movies are hard
to make who cares but at the
same time i can understand like if
something that i really love like the
the marvel movies recently if they had
fucked up avengers endgame two to a
point i
i would have been like so bummed
about it but not like calling for
these people's heads you know but the
stuff like star wars was very important
to me indiana jones was very important
to me when i was a kid
but then that second one came out
like three years later it's like oh
we don't have to like this oh
i liked it you know what i
mean like when i was on board
i was still young enough to to
really be on board with the
and and and really enjoy it i
saw that one like three times yeah
like going wasn't all good as the
first one but yeah um but then
ah when i think about like star
wars specifically those when i was a
kid those movies were very important when
the prequels came out i was excited
to see them and to me the
sin of those movies was that they
just weren't that fun yeah the fun
and fun
any like humor is so important to
them then forget those star wars movies
are so funny and that's why the
last two have been great i mean
they've been fun to watch they've been
fun to other adventures but none of
these movies are perfect it's like exactly
there's i had a big conversation about
ghostbusters with a mutual friend where we
were talking we were talking about
friend she's yeah she's my best friend
wow weird wait a minute that's fantastic
to be a wife so you're so
we were talking about and i was
like look that original one as much
as i loved it when i was
fourteen it's not group it's not really
good like bill murray's hilarious and sucker
rod
it's not good bill murray's hilarious and
that's about it like it's not a
very good mood it's not very well
may over problems it's got a lot
of problems and then i watched the
new one i was like yeah this
one has a lot of problems too
and yet i see like a fourteen
year old girl just like during the
credits dancing in the aisles i'm like
these movies are not for us yeah
when i saw when i saw the
new one
first of all it was a lot
of laughs in there gangsters yeah yeah
ghostbuster good plus goods goods good guys
do this did i see the removing
good sponsor it's good but it's good
movie just did this bit to take
an officer like my singing the movie
is there a movie called goats bus
chose ghostbusters is this the right movie
that ever
i saw it written i only heard
people talking about it ghostbusters so if
i go see this movie ghostbusters i'm
seeing what i think is good semester
so nice is it good goads or
goats with which one is like spicy
their goads or it's goats are there
too it's one of the other options
are there two options here that i'd
need to choose from goads bios
sponsor scolds busters her i don't know
how many easer in it
so that scene where kate mckinnon is
it's towards the end the big battle
and she's walking down the street firing
those just the other day she saw
a pretty lady she didn't know it
so just go
um that i got so excited i
got like got goosebumps watching that because
i realized i never seen anything like
this yeah seen before and then i
immediately realized that like what it's going
to be meaningful who is gonna be
meaningful to yeah yeah same news captain
marvel so
i'll like it anyway but i but
i at the same time if they
had fucked up avengers endgame and i
know there are people out there who
think they did or whatever but if
they had fun i was so gratified
with that movie it was like the
culmination of all this stuff i'd liked
for the past like they're gay agenda
i know that's only part that i
scream oh wow
oh get it get a load of
this lauren i go to these movies
just have a good time i wanna
think about politics oh huh then dangle
in more men talk about their wives
i love hearing about talking about wives
there's this guy this character is there
further a big deal out of it
their first openly gay character and it's
a guy saying
yeah somebody i know died my husband
died that support group what do you
mean that's it nobody mean ruined ruined
dad's but it's not a main character
it's like oh it was iron man
it's not they've made we were just
timing raise my td about how on
arthur the cartoon yeah the dev teacher
teachers danny got married to a man
i heard
heard that's so nice it is nice
i thought we watched it yeah we
watched the club champ yeah but without
his my tv i thought you'd funny
watching her take on that you can
relate to gay rights like each other
like we need to write we need
to take a break well rat no
the teacher well
hi we're back and i'm back scott's
back lawrence back all three of us
are back call i'm scott
i'm lauren you know me oh you're
excited to know oh yeah me and
i nasty um my say and it's
feature time and your time tory paul
has a feature we and these are
sent to us nowadays using the hashtag
three cheer his rage are doubly a
t u r yes
creature three church creature you're within this
okay three church seeking share for the
funerals we cover good for you three
cheers so no so troodos features at
three church wash and call them three
trash tag three cheers all right so
like thinking all is gonna read this
one to change the name to three
tres is it three scherzer isn't saying
what
we call it a feature read the
base of the noisy yeah but that's
the hash i just said to be
reading let me just read the from
the from the base to the tip
of the base i will leave the
base of the summit of email
alright shevlin sent us this he's on
vacation or something i don't know what
is going on and some sort of
high handbook festival oh man those men
this comes from seeing man
ten daughter my head ted daughters his
screen name is signor haas wherein his
real name is ted daughters and he
has a screening items add handles ted
dot alright alright i don't this the
thing to fishing has been allowed this
is the whole problem with twitter yes
it made to take off
oh the one problem with it everyone
should have to have their real name
in it and have a blue check
mark so every dumb thing they say
is they're accountable for picture instead we
have that tina fey hamburger in the
very first few months yeah and it
fucked everything up i don't know what
that is that was an account that
people thought whatever
i was santa fe and everyone was
like following her and it was just
a picture of a hamburger like ha
how funny tina fey loves hamburgers so
much that that's her that's her avatar
so she should re tweet like those
chris rock things it's like oh right
that and everyone thought bill murray was
real to remember that that was ridiculous
anyway
ted daughter's saviour house
this is called know one more thing
i also read the raw one we'll
get we'll get back to you okay
back to your ted daughters one last
thing i have to say is that
i hate when people quote banksy because
who's got him that's fucking say that
where when are people quoting banksy in
memes so in me mean coaster me
is oh rude and the da da
da da da da in me is
oh
ou da da da da da da
da da
me oh ma
oh da o e hey me
a if the horse we've ever devin
and i are both crying and wanting
to escape okay don't drag him don't
drag him in i look for a
few days yeah darren having felon for
a friend and a dark tie how
dare you now tell me what the
game is you haven't get on the
micro quick just say oh no don't
bring don't bring it it's not boredom
no i was laughing and to get
to how coast sometimes it buzzes and
sometimes it doesn't this is the nice
mike
why would you ever use it don't
use these other one it's crazy oyster
that his laser for the audience laziness
is my castle with the lazy oh
alright thank god you can we talked
about that off
that was on ted daughters so no
it wasn't we were off oh mike
texted lauren and said he wanted to
tweet something i want to just pass
oh no you have to wait till
tomorrow my value what i've done the
same and i've asked you just tonight
you get to spank him if he
asks i orbiting whenever i want that's
marriage marriage boys marriage
again whatever wow people are against marriage
and the like why do i need
a piece of paper blah blah blah
so you can't spank banks or whatever
uranium don't you want the freedom to
spank me joshua the free like freedom
of speech was spamming holy cow what
is he saying harry carey haw if
i was
hot dog
and you are mainly my sorry this
one comes from
nils s nils typed that says add
handle nils nils types okay guy named
nils type this nils s the initial
game the initial gone on my gc
hit to it like lauren it's a
premium show i can't take ah think
of a famous person or character and
give the initials the
other players then ask yes or no
questions i can't wait to ask no
question someone gets
okay ready begin are you not a
mineral
um then they give the ah tell
someone gets it right then they give
the next set of initials so is
j c jesus christ jacques cousteau zhang
cryer or jiminy cricket sean kleier jesus
christ jacques cousteau jacques rao a roommate
jon cryer from two and a half
om to have homes and everything
oh no ma i don't speak french
okay i'm gonna go first okay okay
thirty shows are casey okay does this
guy have some sort of a sunshine
band no
if i got my no question in
you right off the bat didn't even
wait a second is this guy know
if it's a guy paul true is
this person
known for a famous baseball movie
no
is this person named kevin no
kevin corrigan you're off the list
as is kevin costner yes well although
he was awful this is in the
previous questions before i know my yes
hey i'm kind of like you haven't
they're off the table kevin's you're out
chevron's chevrons
does it mean no did you it
wasn't me it wasn't me i asked
no yeah i was the last one
okay then i'm just trying to play
the feature you guys gotta get along
i can't leave out to be a
team paul i can't take her down
i can't do this with you guys
you gotta get along i'm serious
it's a long trip okay see okay
alright think about it alright alright
is this a real person yes did
the everly brothers sing about you know
it's not cathy's clown
as a real person she's real cathy's
clown keys real oh that's right it
was him he was kathy clan yeah
that's right here he comes was worth
the everly brothers saying they were cathy's
clown or were i have a tip
for you yeah okay
i will return to this ask for
general questions that won't narrow down is
this procedure general is it first everly
brothers thing song but yeah this person
alive know is this person a woman
know is this person a man yes
we know we know it's a man
it could be non-binding
i'm not less
no she has ruined twenty questions
you waste a question on it now
oh please tweet this is like a
business our business is the problem this
i want this to call our new
rules
spread out i want the zoo genders
oh we want to play rules okay
alright um cocoon yeah do we need
kids bop new rules not yet know
yet alright it's your notes me because
you asked the man it's you i
um training have like men names with
k
sorry for my car fur okay keep
asking questions or go for is it's
a yeah we said it's real dead
ah and is this an actor no
is this an historical figure
no that means like what like like
someone in history or yeah his yeah
yeah no no one would know american
history x you like america is it
tony x keep going
um was his name tony x who
directed american history x tony oh i
can't remember his name was tony as
it was not tony said it was
something's crazy though it was something crazy
he was a weirdo wait is this
tony x and oh come on okay
ah kay kevin
kai ko ask a question okay is
this
it's like twenty questions as an entertainer
yes okay not an actor though nope
singer
singer check is it a singer yes
is it singer dead singer casey
colombo
people are going to be easy global
not going to be eating their steering
wheels
this is like
okay is it oh i'm busy today
is it you is it someone ah
who is like ah ah jazz or
big band singer no
is it kurt cobain yes oh damn
okay your turn you got it right
why didn't he call his band casey
in the funtime band
oh okay see in the moonlight would
they have been this popular if it
was casey in the fun time it
would have been ironic and cool yeah
i think they would have been exactly
as popular yeah
okay alright i need someone to show
right alright i got one nothing got
it re sorry we need to win
just to know what jazz guy you'll
go next regardless alright you'll go next
regardless
come on alright p f t let
me think of some initial we know
this is hard for you i got
with someone on deck towards so what
you do is you take the name
and then you erase all the letters
after the first
yeah
alright almost say yeah
h t h t are the initials
isn't an actor no is it an
historical figure is is it a woman
yeah is it harriet tubman yes ah
well after i chose ah
can't believe how easy that was that
was weird alright you're turning b yes
some of that old b s is
it an actor yes
is it a male actor that's why
i said actor yes
is it
is he a dramatic actor no
you got it
you got it yeah you locked in
will collect in the sector alone she
says she's got it so you gotta
guess is this no i don't but
it's nowhere whereas when it's a fun
what if i think she don't got
it that's the thing she could be
bluffing she could say that and like
make you guess preemptively ooh new role
play new rules new rules devin
and go devin play new roles you
gotta get this on deadly die time
he's got it here we go
this is not neutral now this little
jump for your love in theaters that
was oh detective pikachu oh it's an
ad okay one the world we we
couldn't spring for kids of new rules
we've got a way through an elevator
is it possible trump yeah why wouldn't
it be hey i've no idea yeah
let's buy this now
i started like hearing ya the rules
are what you pick a name of
a person say to people say yes
or no questions preferably no questions three
you gotta ask if they're dead or
a lot for you to throw in
the questions
five if you get if you think
you know you lock in and you
really pass to guess how far they
can think you're bluffing or they can
they can win even if you're not
monitoring your blood thing you don't have
to guess
alright alright so if they think you're
bluffing or just you can't know it
there
sounds like a challenge so say i
say i'm locked-in you could tell yeah
lynch yeah only you have to challenge
as much as just like ask a
regular question then if you get it
you get it and if you don't
say when fine but if you lock
in you have to get it right
was the other person wins alright here
we go so be so you're locked-in
b s a comedic actor
yeah that's all we know
is this person alive yes is it
ben stiller paul you win
what do you care if it was
if you're lying right now i see
wins who wasn't bob sagged
sorry lowe okay next round next round
free flow i like new rules alright
and really brings the same guy not
not that i don't love winning if
you're gonna guess you happen to look
up what do you think of bob
zagat do you think he described him
as an actor you see how many
episodes of full haha yeah i ever
watched that's going on
yeah
okay alright if you're gonna guess you
have to lock in and let the
other person exactly yeah ok okay that's
a neural that's seven ready yeah yeah
e p o no epfo home
is this person i'm locked in i'm
locked into are you okay so god
has to go first because i know
i said i was locked in which
means no it means no no i
said i was locked in which means
i have to give him a chance
you're not even going to ask a
single question oh no both know who
it is yeah go i know i
do go
ellen pompeo what was your guys elvis
presley ellen pompeo is ah yeah like
this my dad like yeah huh yeah
that was amazing ah good this is
getting really good okay oh okay oh
alright
that was amazing
yeah they're not a lot of vps
out there i guess nine that these
i don't think we both know nothing
is you talking out loud amusing okay
go ahead when you're logged in for
him to go
you're like yeah you're scratching you're like
okay god go ahead
alright got it d r d r
is this a man yes
is he an actor no
is he an historical figure
no see a singer no
is he
um
and like a politician ah no and
whatever the like yarou z r c
a host
yes see an entertainer no um i've
almost got it i can't think of
this guy's name unfortunately nah nah nah
hold on wait so you get guys
locked in your locked-in yep alright things
i used to go i get a
chance okay
most sort of
male damn right d r
it's not the are huguely
yeah
it's not ah it's not done a
rice god
um
i'm gonna let you flame out because
i can't even think of a d
r dan rather that's right
a rather okay i'm daniel rather damn
daniel was a hot jazz dad rather
more i'll do one k ah oh
shit i gotta think of someone too
many letters alright m g
is it a woman now dear
is it an entertainer
look i find what they do very
entertaining but no is is it an
athlete
no no i don't even think about
it
is it someone in film no ooh
is it a musician no it's not
musician g
ah so it's not
and it's not make g zombies and
michel gondry mick jagger
yeah just make dagger dragon i mean
the swords didn't gag it on david
billy's dong right yeah yeah i'm dongs
okay um gag gag gag and old
beau his dome is it a
is this somebody i like i've been
nursing
i tough texting m g
texting mg is it is it a
someone who works um
fucking i don't know what categories are
left
we didn't ask one that we've asked
almost every politician know is this person
alive no
we didn't ask me he asked everytime
is via the
host know what did i say before
did we say the gender yeah it
it's it yes you keeps we did
i believe we said it's a man
so or no we didn't we didn't
specify keep saying is it a man
yes okay okay just say yes mean
we've been counting the questions there's no
limit to the no i know one
thing no limit top
a dog
um
as a producer no
you keep asking questions the way all
these comments are slow
this person
see an actor know
says person in historical figure yes is
dead
was he someone who was weighted to
a war
ooh boy
probably i don't know we'll see a
president
no
it was the politician
ah no
are we going to be annoyed by
who it is scott had to go
take a phone call yo so we're
trying to oh alright it's not a
politician it's a historical figure
who maybe isn't it was a war
it was hard to figure out if
scott was having a tough time answering
the question or he was distracted with
the instructor because he was texting and
then it became a phone call which
is always a terrible sign bad bad
bad
maari ma j ro rover it's gotta
be martin my uncle matthew nothing but
name's marvin gambling sh
oh
let's pause
because this could go on for ten
minutes and then we're just spinning our
wheels isn't that what people are paying
for them and that use the restroom
you wanna guess alone yeah i guess
i'm gonna keep it going
m g from history
madame guzzo
um mata gary
sh me ulysses grant
no moses
good bible
um
mister god yours
matador garfunkel
me
missy elliott
um
the bow let's see ah miles davis
marquis gfa yet
more gushy chin
um
a to to to to to to
the ma e alia gerhart
musing g anthony
um
mrs god
ah myrtle ganders
ah mon old gik rano
got your mail
oh good mail call did we get
presence no but we did you and
scott and i didn't get anything raised
by tv company aiming gets me but
not fuck all of you gotta be
gotta open fuck all of you for
not sending me presence hey yeah we
like presence by the way it feels
like you guys don't really know that
about us yeah you know what
i mean we've got thing on ah
spanking pan yes i don't know what
the point is of us doing the
show that you pay for if you're
not gonna sit yeah
ah i lay down some solid guesses
while you were gone yeah i couldn't
believe you were still going on i
came oh i still going i mean
i was not running out of steam
everything stopped talking about that
don't know why you know he's a
deep guy and he's capable of talking
about a lot of different topics he
can talk about a bunch of stuff
yeah comic books um
because this part from my mutual vania
friends
four
lawrence having some kettle corn from boom
chicka pop grey popcorn company that gives
me some free stuff right
get as boom chicka pop yellow bag
all the way purple bag bring your
sweet and savory person wow yeah because
you're fun but you're also not fun
yellow butter y'all just straight up butter
popcorn it's just it's just so good
alright have you ever eaten a bag
of popcorn where you didn't eat the
whole thing
let me ask you this what smartcloud
white cheddar smile at the mess up
about boob positive
it feels gross to me after awhile
anyway that's new stuff but let me
ask you this like non messy popcorn
you can also tell them with your
mouth and put it on board are
sick your tongue
like an anteater
ich
i think are you watching the fucking
bachelor
like holy bow up your kid it
just like givi
wow
why is this is this suit of
can i tell you something i had
a dream last night
that you and scott had your own
side podcast and you did not tell
me about it and then yeah
are you in lavallee and really in
the dream of really hurt my feelings
it's like why did why did they
tell me i think not telling you
is the part where it becomes mean
yeah yeah yeah like it had been
set up you discussed it figure it
out also for some reason you are
on the phone like scott was in
studio and you were somewhere else
doing like street pieces
yeah you got to do it like
your jay walking fit could you
ah
this is hs unprecedented i don't know
i hope he's okay
i've never been to japan should i
go yeah a hundred you love it
what is something i should know about
it that i want clothes are perfectly
tailored to their body
and what looks immaculate you fit in
for the slob no law written no
i really didn't really yeah but i
like was like got up my game
tawny newsome told me a story of
shoe shopping in japan really difficult and
when yes and when she and chinese
on the tall side for me i
mean yeah and as
are you when she told the lady
her size the woman shrieked with laughter
that makes sense i when we went
mike and i went to tokyo a
few years ago am
we were looking everywhere for shoes because
there were so many amazing shoe stores
and i just wanted to buy something
cool and unique but every store didn't
carry size ten women choose em we
finally found a store that did and
then we got these cool nike high-tops
and then we wore them immediately and
they were so uncomfortable that i was
like these are fake like right there
at the base of these is like
cardboard like they're not nikes and it
was really disappointing and we had to
throw them out eventually because it was
like i can never wear them or
not it's not a good shoe and
you don't want that to mar your
memory of a otherwise wonderful trip well
yeah and his problem was that he
put them on right when we walked
out the store as we were leaving
he's like i'm going to switch
to the issues and then we were
walking around and got lost and stuff
and he was so mad about the
shoes hurting and it was like
but we we had a good day
he's very good at maps and figuring
out where things aren't that i would
say for me tokyo was very confusing
in certain areas because there a lot
of like small unmarked streets and he
would find we were going even if
there was no address i was like
i don't know how this is working
because it was very attractive what if
i found out that he was not
a real person
let me find ma it's working
um what did you find out genie
was a robot i'd be very sweet
ai or like i'd be like that's
very sophisticated yeah it's working because we
get into fight sometimes
like why did you make that part
of the program why don't you just
be nice all the time go with
whatever i say well the day or
you put a bunch i gotta be
a be up and this will learn
shibuya rhp sam
we'll never yeah why didn't we end
it i oh no we don't know
who m g is you know well
we'll pick it up in the next
episode well we gotta go to the
interest of time yeah we gotta shut
this down we just talked for twenty
excrement listen to d walked out of
here nearly twelve minutes all right well
fourteen minutes a
a have to be so perfect for
you devin devin does have to work
for you oh i thought you were
saying no i'm saying i was saying
you will look what lauren would you
tell is very powerful because you were
talking to devin but you release straight
at me no i was talking to
you and i was talking about devin
i just had a weird intonation wait
so so definitely
that's be perfect for yea devin doesn't
why not because he's not your slave
is that what i ask of my
slaves to be perfect for you i
don't want my sleep i've heard you
screaming that you need them to be
perfect for you anyway we have to
go we'll see you next time we
love you ally by
a