so
sorry
welcome back to thredup we're here again
we did it we're outside and you
believe that we are doing the podcast
again you leave we're about two and
a half scots apart from each other
yeah and this but not gods not
be three maybe three scots we might
respond to say you're i'm three scots
away paul's three scots away and i'm
three scots away from paul you're more
than three scots away morning equal lateral
triangle um no i believe that all
utah paul is little longer udall longest
side udall called out on you udall
thou dog what does that from finding
forrester yeah of course it is oh
of course you the man now dog
what else is from finding
forrester can you name some other details
i cannot i think i think they
wrote a baseball field at some point
is that right maybe it could be
i saw it don't remember any of
it other than yoda man now dog
stealing land i know ever of any
movie or any dog and his robyn
lamb say no he is not about
shishi betty
did say though at some point his
life thought he said that it was
there is john connor sean connery said
it na said oh ma dao doe
died right oh he's ah yeah he
died in a car of people mag
along with me farrow every time a
person dies i gotta put the picture
on the cover while people look that
was just the
i fucking hate i follow people magazine
on instagram and it's all good i
don't like i just love to have
it this is what lauren hates by
the way this is lauren and this
is what payments hey um i don't
know if it's new i actually think
we tend to think out every episode
but the people magazine i enjoy following
it it's just random little story
aries sometimes are various people sometimes they're
about celebrities and sometimes they're about regular
people and something remarkable or just cute
that happened when it is a celebrity
that people haven't heard of the comments
are like who the fuck says why
do you post all the shit do
you not understand that they post from
someone walking
on the street to some red carpet
yeah oh every day everyday from the
street to the carpet because you don't
know who the country star is you're
gonna rip them a new one and
they're like you you just predicted every
time like okay i don't know who
this is let's see the comments are
gonna go off yeah and it's like
whoo gives a shit that a baby
who cares man and it's like well
you have to win
that little baby got a cochlear implant
to you didn't know who that was
ah yeah er yeah that would be
so funny if people were sue the
fuck is this when that's done focuses
baby that's right that's the same yeah
that's what the account is it is
every wires yeah so why are you
mad that you don't know who that
celebrity is like you're just preemptively trying
to protect yourself when they
something i already had that happen to
be people going you used to be
a babysitter now you're a movie star
i don't care i just yeah i
do love that forgot trajectory
yeah next astronaut i mean there were
a lot more steps in between but
yeah would you go in space and
we talked about four i don't think
we let's talk about it right now
i go to space genera janey doesn't
either i would go to space you
want to go to space i don't
i don't like want to you know
go to mars and never come back
but if they said you could go
to the moon i would
go to the moon nobody does that
anymore
oh we're in the jungle by the
way does anyone go to the moon
anymore i'm into the jungle you're gonna
die once they do we were gonna
go back to the moon why don't
we do it again why what's like
the same city that we were gonna
go back to the moon for summary
ours yes
wasn't trying to go to the moon
jackie gleason was trying to talk about
what he did jackie gleason because i
don't think he did go there fucker
but i think you know i think
he eventually did get to go not
not like part of nasa but yeah
he didn't go i'm google you wanted
to go he and i know he
wanted to go i thought he got
to go oh he didn't get to
go he was certified all the people
like who are gonna go up in
the yukon mux mux thinking keylong books
suck
in two thousand and three lance bass
began serving as world space weeks and
two thousand three let's bass had money
back to two thousand and twenty and
bought the fucking he was no use
going gonna buy the brady bunch houseman
yeah hcc oh yeah bit him um
bass has stated that he believes young
people becoming marches in space exploration will
help the future
a planet from two thousand and three
to two dozen photos a group he
spent worldspace whorehouse american high school speaking
with students about space x exploration and
then he's a member of the space
society space abc de girl members of
the state society he absolutely doesn't seven
he told g q he absolutely still
intends on going to space and that
he hopes to work on
a space documentary just say something right
here on threesome this is a promise
to our listeners lance pass will never
go to space he also retained fluency
in russian with mr dwyer until i
learned during his training holy shit that's
intense wow now that's intense and yet
he didn't get to go and that's
let's focus back on ourselves though because
i want
i wanna hear i wanna hear about
paul's reasons for wanting to go to
the moon okay i wanna hear what
you're gonna do up there kick rocks
bitch
i'm gonna collect all the golf clubs
and solemn
um i would i i okay here
are my reasons i think it would
be an amazing experience right to go
when you say you get sick in
that kind of environment on roller roller
coasters vi no i don't i don't
i don't really have motion sickness i'm
i'm pretty good with stuff like that
what about emotional motion sickness
yeah moshe loves his it is true
that if i'm not adding i'm not
driving the car i do get sad
okay
roller coasters i'm always crying um i
ruined everyone when they have the photo
at the end i wanted to thrive
in my daddy i wanted to draw
zappos
yeah that's what i say if ever
i get in the front car i'm
driving the road
we're all screaming she did i would
kill to go away aesthetics either if
you guys right now any land oh
i would love it so well it's
gonna open back up and know that
bro let's go here to this thing
i've ever heard
oh no it's mainly it's outside the
backstreet boys do that they did the
monster video right yeah right ma hey
and which monster lance bashing wow even
season and say yeah they did they
did mac straight back hi should not
do that no answer
linkedin instinct backstreets back alright it's erin
ma section um oh yeah we can't
name a single thing i know that
my know though
not that bad
saying no to rid of nah that's
justin timberlake okay oh say can you
see anything i'm sure they did that
happy bow tie for instinct to sing
me happy birthday no they did do
tear out my heart but guys what's
the course in the bye bye song
bye bye bye
never cone of healing you know haven't
been revealed to you and that's when
they were puppets right and no that's
true yeah oh yeah i know know
that singular pepper that and it right
i think your puppet sebastian i want
to say no strings attached but that
was the name of the album to
be fair they were marionettes yes
i'm never going to beep until i've
never gone a pure banana pee and
poo
i'm never gonna pee and poo
never gonna pee and poo okay i'm
good booze
god no b o b but a
holy sabbath cells to die of septic
good huh something okay
you can take on a diet food
disease i don't do things always go
into me
she's h christ well back to paul
going up in space so to paul
would you you'd have to train with
knew it might be in russian like
man you would just go up well
okay i would i wonder what everyone
had to learn russian for that what's
the cutoff for you if you had
to if you had to learn russian
would you go up in space
yeah you know what yeah you would
okay when you think you want to
go if you had to go through
space for i'm not doing anything right
now i'm trying to narrow down a
little bit if you if you had
to go to space camp for two
years of training would you go
yeah on your own time ah i
don't know depends how much it costs
i guess remember when three dogs ovid
was really popping off and then they
fail you took off and that's popular
and it was like everyone was like
jealous yeah so here's the thing i
haven't thought about it in those terms
of like
what will be necessary to do right
i'm just saying if you could just
step five opportunities up onto a space
shuttle like you like you were going
on a plane yes if i had
the opportunity to opt-in to the space
shuttle already
two plane
i am interested you'll also played
make the spaceship some bad yes
this is terrible well okay how long
does it take to get to the
moon and back ah i know it's
between here in new york city umm
gates mean i don't know how long
i'll just having to memorize yeah yeah
google adsense you're not interested i'm gonna
keep this interesting google that google that
you gotta google has long day
hey i'm gonna die of food disease
no um three days to get to
the mo three days yeah you you
probably have six weeks to go in
there more since ah well i don't
even get to get out no i
go smoothly turn right back around
yeah minutes to walk around with my
gift shop
what was the movie i saw recently
where they're on the moon and they're
like gunmen having to chase moonbase have
it it was pretty pretty pretty much
made me not want to go to
the moon the bed pretty chase bed
pretty much into the moon well they
they got on the moon and they
were like ah fuck what wasn't it
and then they had chase between two
cars were like h you know what
well
no because he was like so interesting
like you know actually i would cancel
my trip clearly made up thing like
well if that's what it's gonna be
like forget it well now i have
to say there's been a couple of
ah that george clooney movie that just
came out and other end the cloverfield
movie and george mooney there are there
are certain clever moon there are certain
spaceship movies that have made
me not want to go out in
the same way i don't want to
be out on a ship in the
middle of the in the middle of
nowhere and i don't want to be
underneath like in the abyss don't you
feel like we have a new space
movie every four months yeah that's that's
about right how about a movie about
three a year indiana
well there were wars that i think
of yes yeah sorry
um but like all good yeah though
you are now him the bad that
george clooney movie was two different types
of i'm trapped in a terrible situation
type movie was one i'm trapped in
a spaceship that's break gravity and i
have to go yeah gravity is another
one where i like have to go
fix the ship and all this shit
can go rallies
scary and i saw that in the
theaters and i was going to see
in the theaters because you're like feel
like really bad they should call it
gravity because it got a hold of
me oh yeah and that part of
the sandra books fallen into the water
walking out yeah but then the other
part of the george clooney thing is
is you wander around in the snow
in a blizzard and like he's he's
he falls asleep in a shelter that
suddenly is
flooding and sinking into the ice and
shit like oh just all of my
all of my worst nightmares claustrophobic nightmares
other than like being drowning maybe it's
just george clooney have a problem with
yeah that's true he's a silver fox
though who ever seen twins now with
empty you don't hear about them wait
he has twins twins is because he
and emma
so he says i thought him and
danny de vito were a little sigh
you were saying that
watson like oh no that's an espresso
commercial oh my god i know oh
my god oh you're exasperate let's erase
this one ah we will never erase
one also paul so also so it's
not that far which is good so
because i was thinking oh wow if
you had to be
away from from janey for four months
would you do it well yeah you
do that for a job yeah would
you be away from four from janey
for four months for a job yeah
if i had to yeah would you
be away from janey for five months
for a job yes would you be
away from janey for six months for
a job yes
would you be away from janie for
seven months for not a job no
one would that wow
i want to know the what the
circumstances how many months yeah i'm gonna
be gone for seven months it is
not for a job show
you get away from co-op for four
months for a job
i i don't know it would depend
on your literal problem it would just
depend on the job i mean it's
your major malfunction it's the same thing
when i was younger and people were
like hey do you want to go
right on snl or whatever i was
like yeah i don't really want to
go move to new york i'm happy
here so you just don't want to
go away i yeah i have i've
ru
it's here but you're not moving you're
going i know hawaii for four months
to shoot a movie without kula and
she wait what i star in the
wrong missy yes as they're on me
yes they're doing a reboot but a
male very busy all male throng mr
re um no i'm probably gay
panic back into comedy if it was
a good enough part yeah i probably
would do anything for like a good
four months away for four months five
months it's it's i've a friend long
and hard i've i've a friend who
moved away for nine months though and
it's topple you know i think that
kind of sucks when you're on like
a t v show and you're like
yeah right it was abate yes
it was the boss baby my dad
was a sperm he moved away for
nine months the baby was totally different
recognize them
so much bigger ah big hassle is
smarmy yeah yeah it's a big empty
bad no but when you're people the
thing i don't i'm not jealous of
us when people are cast on a
show that shoots in like canada or
something or another that's so now i
live on facebook she likes yeah but
like not fully like they kind of
still have their place so have a
phd
friend got cast in a canadian show
and once it became pretty clear that
it was going to keep going they
bought a house in canada and moved
their partner up to canada with them
but their partner had to essentially agree
to tar not do anything themselves they
they had to just like live in
canada and not work themselves
show was the little turbo yeah that's
right is such a little cute show
i mean i've seen little hobos before
but the littlest he's smaller than anyone
and it was proven
did you know that that's an actual
show oh no i didn't it's it's
one of my favorite canadian references to
canadiana it is um it was a
show from the eighties i want to
say early eighties maybe late seventies early
eighties that was a ah um a
sort of incredible hulk highway to heaven
sore
out of show where this drifter character
moved from downtown but you might be
surprised to know let's hope it was
a german shepherd that's when i just
discovered can't so so this dog is
going from town to town by itself
start by itself starring london as hope
colin london that's a show the littlest
london know just how i'm gonna watch
london there isn't a show about a
dog unless it comes starring london it's
not a sitcom or whatever it's they
really gave the dog a title card
this he was the star what i
will say we give it saying so
you would help to reach you
would help someone with some kind of
problem i bet if you asked the
dog over a document like that if
you asked the dog what would you
rather have a title card or retreat
one tree
oh good it's like treats like the
marshmallow experiment yours dad you're gonna be
a famous dog i'll take the one
now dogs don't know they're in movies
but they do know they're on a
set they do know they're in a
workplace because they're what their trainer not
their own yes and so they go
to a place and they're like okay
this is i've been in places like
this before i know what is expected
of me to do but they don't
know half the time
um i won't do it they don't
know the concept of cameras though no
they don't they just see them they
see them as big things shadowy things
but some dogs can watch tv so
they know what tv is so wouldn't
it couldn't they just extrapolate that o
cameras must most filmmakers just because they
watched tv that doesn't mean they know
that it's ninety
tom i think it's a window my
dog will bark at doorbells on the
tv yeah never had a sound that
she's never heard as my dog will
too but my dog will not bark
at voices on tv because they know
it's tv yeah but isn't it weird
that they know that it's if you
have a doorbell on the show that's
like ding dong but you never had
a doorbell like that in your house
why should we change up our doorbell
so it's gotta be the pitch every
every two weeks i don't do that
because i'm not a fucking freak um
do you really should we stick with
westminster chimes can't get enough thing dong
ding dong ding dong ding dong ding
dong ding dong goes on for fifteen
minutes cool
um no but i just would like
for your do you do you think
dogs know what tv is they know
it's a thing that's broadcasting a thing
now my daughter's oh my dogs do
know how good they know that they
know it's bride no say no phones
they know they know they now know
phones because anytime we pick up the
phone to answer a phone call they
think it's us using our
our ah front door cam to talk
to someone who's delivering something so they
will immediately start barking anytime we pick
up the phone so they don't know
we know they know it's they know
it's communicating between us and yeah personnel
yeah that's like i definitely know when
they sit and you get a tree
dogs phones that's the same thing bhutto's
folks
dog does fall dogs are smarter than
you think i think they know hey
man they know what tv even if
they're smarter than i think so they
know whether on defining i know where
the cameras are his dogs his therapists
this is why
i take all my job to advice
me and my dog talk about tv
shows i do most of the talking
granite but boy what have you done
recently
let me start
so no what tb is so paul
would you would you go away right
for a year would you go away
right now well we had a situation
where i did what i was offered
a job she mentioned came with me
yes and this was this was we
had just moved in together so it
was a real turning point for us
yeah
you moved in in l a and
you got the job in new york
yes yeah and we'd lived together for
about six months something like that but
all six months and it was it
was a discussion of what how is
what is the best way to do
this do we do we do visits
you know like every month or or
like wow how do we work this
you know but i feel like oh
i want the best
case scenario in that you're both actors
not some lift and yoga is a
great place to live it feels like
it seems like it would be yeah
feels like a treat to get to
move there for a job i was
very exciting i'm saying yeah yeah yeah
yeah um but but what if what
if she couldn't what she was working
here
and ah what would you take a
five-year gig where you work nine months
out of the year if it was
a good gig yes i would and
we would figure it out what is
a good gig to you a job
that i would like to do that
pays me good money
and if it's ah honestly those are
consideration sometimes i don't think it's i
don't think i've ever had to turn
down something i've never had i've never
been put in that position where it
was like this is very good money
but this job will clearly be miserable
you know because of the project it
is the character the role the people
whatever um but yeah
you're always like kind of prepared for
that like there could come a situation
like that where it's like there are
here the upsides to this but the
downsides are many and is it worth
sacrificing this much time of your life
to do it it's like the bob
odenkirk conundrum of like having to move
to to san antonio or wherever they
shoot that in some areas
in new mexico or new mexico yeah
yeah yeah right in and just being
away from your family for so long
and then like trying to figure out
exactly how to navigate yeah but then
you work it out you know you
figure you figure out ah you figure
out the best possible plan you can
come up with yeah and it makes
it not as bad you know right
and it's also like it depends on
you know new mexico
oh it's probably not that you know
like flight wise yeah i'm gonna get
laid probably two hours yeah but i
also think like i find it exciting
to to get to live somewhere else
for a period of time yeah just
yeah you went to england for that
yeah it was like never four months
and i mean that was really cool
idea too it was a great experience
i whenever we get to do that
my life and then i know i
never would choose to and i would
i wouldn't even know how to figure
out how to move somewhere for a
period of time like that and like
legally with like visas or whatever i
don't write shit works so it's great
to get the opportunity to go somewhere
and then i also think like it
just opens up your life in this
interesting way like you just don't know
what's coming so it's kind of fun
yeah
there is something to the experience of
living in another country for long enough
where you can feel like you get
a sense of what life is like
there yeah there is a tourist you
are you're having to buy groceries you're
having to you know do the normal
shit you do in life in another
place and getting a getting a a
feel
for that is exciting and fun yes
say you had to move to the
moon for a job move
you are to live on the moon
is all and that let me tell
you the first moon tv show yes
all grey the rocks oh there's not
like a house it's like you're in
your suit but your you can piss
in the suit wait no you have
a house
you have a house but you still
have to plug this out there's no
structure i'm just out on the surface
of the malaria and here's my question
what the moon
is it really because i feel like
that video of them walking on it
you you could probably if you just
really didn't like the little prince that
day if you started in one place
and tried to walk around the whole
thing you could probably do it in
like five hours that's
it's like really trying to try to
like work out video game maps where
they say in real in real life
it would be this um how i
wanna know like the comparison like how
big is the moon i bet it's
it'll let me can we both guess
before you say what it is i
don't even know yeah like
like are we talking about diameter as
i was as compared to the earth
i would say well right i think
i'm gonna say it's one-third of the
earth oh okay i'll do that first
but i'm into compared to the us
because i feel like yeah sort of
slump sweet to visualize around hands across
america from the nineteen eighty six
i remember i have the customary i
had to learn the width of earth
that's what i said yeah that is
what you said nice nice okay and
compared to the usa
okay so the surface number to the
usa actually wait i think we're getting
another i love that song too real
i can't find that song moving usa
given the right wow and i proudly
stand up and stand up next to
you and you see a millennial today
laugh
being back at gen z with parodies
of god bless the usa i haven't
seen this but oh my god it's
terrible okay well i just want to
say that the moon is the same
size as russia canada and the us
combined so it's pretty low pretty big
well big but also small wow this
deep you couldn't walk across it in
five steps like i kind of thought
but steps
but it's pretty bad if they said
if they said hey we're going to
go film the first television show on
the moon i don't want anything to
do with that you don't want anything
to do with it but paul would
you do it you would now would
be tough because janie does not want
to go into space but and so
that's that is a way that we
can't we're halloween to worry that
yeah yeah okay let me let me
let me soften the deal soft in
the deal it was you were doing
do we're doing location shooting on the
moon and we're doing it for six
months if we're gonna we're gonna do
like three seasons worth of a show
do all of our location shooting on
the moon yes you would do it
the answer is yes nice i want
to do this now you want
go to the moon that freaking bad
i think i i mean that i
i think that just a priceless experience
yeah now maybe that's why it's cost
so much when they do these space
shelves it's like oh yeah it's gonna
cost seven million dollars because like it
is in a way priceless i think
i would go to the moon when
i'm ninety
you're gonna die on that night fine
though because i could die they're really
cool and they could put me in
a tomb if you could die on
the moon how would you um breathing
the air
i just think
it's just not it's not what i
foresee i'm not going there as my
death i'm not going there i was
wrong when i was i'm not going
everyone knows i'm gonna die peacefully in
my bed when i'm ninety nine that's
the only good way to die one
hundred i don't want to die falling
downstairs please go over any power downstairs
alone or in pairs honestly i think
about that every time i walk down
stairs yeah
like just the idea of like um
what if i just flew down these
fuckers
flew down these fuckers
oh and did fly on these fuckers
zero i break my neck or i
mean i was terrifying when i was
a kid i was obsessed with throwing
myself down carpeted stairs wow yeah i
love well the funniest thing was to
make like getting your sleeping bag and
go down the carpet and stairs we
were on car a cardboard box why
aren't you some person
i don't i wanted to be when
i was a kid i went oh
awesome person yeah oh no i got
anytime i've tried to do stunts it's
it's really not good i remember when
when i was a kid my my
dad was painting the church and i
had like a sort of penance as
a prank
you know he was he was a
deacon so you you know which you
he would do all these things chicken
he had a good dick and um
i'm like wait what does a deacon
compared to a priest actually died it's
just like the i don't even know
how religious stuff you could also fall
yeah you could have you take any
the two like
all the behind the scenes shit of
like the deacons would meet and decide
you know what should people be allowed
to tax hey
one point they excommunicated someone from our
church it was very exciting they basically
we went to the normal boring church
on a sunday no more and then
they said hey everyone stick around afterwards
because we're going to have an important
meeting and was like what and then
they they everyone meaning like the congregation
not just yeah
hopefully yeah so like like you're out
because what the normal the normal like
regulars hey all the normal regulars stickers
were gonna have no cliff
um and so then i hope you
brought some big rocks than everyone stuck
around and they're like ok so here's
what's going on there is one of
the members of the church ah wants
a divorce and is not sorry about
it
and doesn't want forgiveness for it thinks
it's the right thing to do if
you can imagine and so we have
no other
choice but to excommunicate this person because
the person is not saying like hey
i got a divorce it was a
oh sorry was there hell there was
a helicopter just under my breath i
wanted to interceptor singular um i didn't
want to disturb the fluffy baby please
yeah it it was so bizarre it
was like it's not like the person
got a divorce and felt bad about
it and asked for forgiveness it's this
person who's planning on getting a divorce
sees there's thinks there's nothing wrong with
it and therefore we need to we
need
to punish them and show that they
are not walking out i would honestly
be so glad to be excommunicated at
that point you go okay it's crazy
and i can bet that now oh
you guys yeah sure you have
you can bet that nowadays the church
is like divorce people married people whatever
come on please yeah please no one
wants to be religious anymore please but
to make less sense to us but
at the time he was just such
a like major what it was it's
so crazy and then i think i
waited on the person at all garden
wait is this restaurant roundup or wasn't
marie calendar's
there was ah was a catholic cardiology
or was it but i think i
waited on the person hey folks and
there had been a family
and i felt embarrassed because like i
was part like my dad was a
deacon and i was like hey how's
it going is sorry about all that
yeah guess your life is crumbled into
sin yeah too bad for all the
things that are bad
i'm just a teen yes
i'm only a teen and i'm saying
yeah coffee bean bow i tried to
note again never gone up huh
pleasure is your measure in my system
the ultimate mashup beelzebub match up and
t um alright we didn't have to
take a break
we're back we're back i've never gone
up ooh but huh
i'll give you guys a lot of
leeway okay this is where you draw
the line now just like you got
it out there you happy do you
have to keep reminding it's fine i'm
glad
start radio forum i'll never do it
again except for when i'm home i'm
wearing a track suit like star trek
yep
tracksuit top what's your parish leader ten
minutes ashley sullivan's island fire department south
carolina oh no it's not the fire
department this is just ah there's the
seal the seal of south of sullivan's
island south carolina it's the seal of
the city or seal of south carolina
so you love the series south carolina
gotta go there's oh thank you
i appreciate the you know the song
will help you remember yes of course
um does california have a song california
here i ah right back where i
started for ah ya got it yeah
shouted right oh hey every every state
has a state song i think really
if so yeah yeah let's look at
california is the place that
we're from google
i really think they're like popular songs
like chicago chicago i think they're like
all written to be the state songs
i think so um do you hear
that we do so like did your
high school have a song
ah yes what was it i can
venture ariens we honor the something like
that ours i remember i remember a
lot of hours e t h s
we will fight for you live and
die for you so do what's right
for you something like that that was
part of it that was that there
was that the fight song for the
sports teams me yeah we wanna get
up and sing it in the morning
because this is the state song of
california called i love you california
here we go
this is isn't that it's silent really
it's gonna take ten minutes now what
i expected
l i f o
this can't be the real word no
i like that i like it i
love it i want some more of
it wait country roads now is the
official state song what no well i
love you know i love you california
is the official state song that's just
a version z a ah ah
oh allah for and will you look
up oh that's california this the state
saw oh no you look at pennsylvania
yeah we're saying millennia c and pan
sylvania
so all of them
it's like the company that makes the
the jingles for radio hail pennsylvania
let's hear a little bit here you
will put some food you know would
yeah
hale here we go this is hale
pennsylvania
h a i o p e n
n
oh no oh this is like from
a skit god it's like a school
ten survey yeah my lady is your
name the lyrics steeped in gloria and
tradition object of claim
graven fanta foe of freedom t irony
d cry i'm gonna learn the song
until the bell of independence fill the
country sides i'd tie today ya okay
and survey yeah that's me
a your future be and we can
stop me feel like i get filled
with a yarder
i guess it's just nice to see
your his can't be more than one
i really hope it's not
so should you should maybe stopped outlet
right now we gotta hear illinois you
have to alright illinois you know when
sophia was gonna do fifty states albums
yeah yeah he did illinois and then
he stopped but i think michigan too
i know but i i like to
illinois cause that's where i'm from someone
really cared about anyway but i was
in you're like shoe
guy that went out of the good
alright here's the his funny and i'm
just realising now that we represent the
east the west and the feminism of
the country wow i read
mrs man lee foe we agree this
is judy garland oh hey easy noi
was i gregory's bird and rage
oh hey lee oh yeah comes on
oh buoy dams rustling through the movie
tree is now darwin dude's ma boo
tos all e coli in o e
oh hey okay live smell o o
e o e can you play old
man river just because it made me
think of that oh oh oh my
whew
my memory
i own mad river us g o
a b o se da de bo
na hey jaws james row
oh now that is a hallmark of
a great song is if three people
can sing three parts of it at
the same time
all these states i'm glad to say
that like it makes it sound like
it's easy good illinois was the best
illinois was started out it started out
a little bit weird and i really
liked it by the end and i
thought you know what i could really
see this in a musical and i
really want to i love that it
was sung by a lady sean connery
there's probably there's all sorts of different
versions of it online but we don't
need to hear my school song was
i went to bishop mcdevitt high school
which is about to close baron oh
because you're not there anymore yeah
around back they looked around like the
life of the party has gone past
thirty five years where is this guy
think he's coming
probably as though our our song went
like this the harshaw lin java marching
world we g
accent ball wild show rushing standard ever
knew was wrong dawned on something and
then let live that's all i remember
like yeah i i've lost the rest
all i remember is o cypress hi
we honor the
okay so nice i think more in
part i think we held up our
hands like sees oh wait we bear
our banner golden y dar sai sign
of royal tea what's the first line
the challenge of a marching world we
meet with accent bold
here this is my school song
well my bf
ah
we buying your fame ra ra ra
ra la janda blue we will proudly
wear may color their fly okay it
comes when we seeing many trophies will
bring some cheer cheer cheer we will
win the game for evenson i found
my soul don't have another song like
that i found my song from cyprus
let's hear it
hey reps this is an ex commercial
ah well they really updated it i
go this is from cyprus
the fuck sounds like shit
is this the sugar cubes
i think it's just getting going you
gotta rick roll us
yo rick roll
wow you guys oh cypress hill
i wanna kiss
i want to
alright wait i found mine by the
way speaking rick rolling have you seen
the video recently oh no what did
he do now
whom has you rolled lately they re-release
the video oh no week ago two
weeks ago in ultra high definition four
k y i don't know how bad
everyone's to make rolls better but it
looks ridiculous well that's like that's horrible
don't you remember when tv started doing
that and then it was
like everything like it was a play
yeah exactly what it was so mike
all the stuff of him dancing around
and all the dancers and stuff like
that it you can see you can
see the set now so bad you
look so it's like watching star trek
the next generation on on high done
by the way you know what i
saw on star trek next generation yeah
it was really funny i thought you
were
was ah clearly with what you said
it's just like watching star trek know
some paul yeah tell some well voice
was going oh you said it's just
like watching star trek ah and then
he literally the k of start talking
yankee done yeah yeah the purchasing okay
yeah you can
it's just go i'm not done and
then keep talking that's true instead of
just that's true sniping abby like a
bitch you know but i watched the
roadway and i apologize um you can
see like like on the holiday when
they go to the holiday if you
see anything yeah sometimes it's just tape
on the wall and you can really
see it yes it's just like a
pretty yellow tape on the
wall well i might have told you
when i watched i have the beverly
hills now too no seasons went into
on dvd and um i boot to
betsy mix who just drop in all
the time but i think the tv
frame somebody's gender yeah but they're just
dipping in it looks so safe pretty
common yeah oh i'm so good
oh do you ah mater hail to
you oh ma may fe coleridge be
oh god god are fine all gone
oh gee
a terrifying is that bringing him back
to become gods yeah to do with
ah my high school had a plan
to attack and dethrone god god that's
awesome and i still have that to
this day well that's where they're closing
they were able to do it eventually
admit defeat good for everyone who follows
god but bad for your skin yeah
yeah we gave it a shot
um what i saw on we gave
it a shot when i saw on
star trek was picard and wesley are
walking charge card hey y'all see yeah
star power after
they're walking they're walking through the ship
and picard turns to wesleyan gives him
some sort of piece of advice and
then he moves past cameron wesley stays
there and then you immediately see like
picard moving back to get back into
position
it was what do you mean like
he walks back claim you want back
into frame yeah so yeah i don't
know how it kept how it stays
because funny it's not like one of
those things where like like say tasha
yar like waving and or final episode
that's way in the background that like
people have to point out it literally
the first time i watched it was
like wait he just moved back
into frame what happened and i rewound
it three times yeah it was um
i just saw something i think it's
from seinfeld where there was like a
stand-in for one part i mean it's
noise friends i think friends there's a
stand-in who like make basically cut away
for a second and then there's a
standard minute scene and then it's back
to being the guy oh and i
wonder if it's metal longstanding who looks
a lot like matlab no
was playing the dad of someone oh
okay yeah like this little leaf boat
a look of belief bow that really
is like the that's the start of
a pixar movie gotta get a picture
of it maybe i'll post it may
like you will um but you know
the big famous one the star wars
like stormtrooper hitting his head when he
walks in i never saw that when
i was a kid
i don't know that it's right hook
it took like you know it being
a thing took me out of it
honestly i was like is this even
real that's why i've dismissed those films
dog the dog okay okay show also
shrek that's another way
donkey show don't get shanna donkey shit
just be on
doggy show thing you balls out ya
ho chair vagina ah it may be
not true but it might be true
to switch to the not true part
because i feel like i know people
i've seen the pingpong oh that shows
are popular at the ping pong balls
the donkey
show is when a woman fucks a
donkey and they said that ibm is
the ping pong balls part is true
because i won't say video at u
c e o hadn't happening was that
in a that was the and legal
video sharing covin
i made jokes when no one was
there it was i mean that was
your way there was a mysterious video
showing i was drawn to it
i woke up at home i heard
the sound of
i followed it until i found the
video i'm realising there's a palm tree
thing right but it's like hey i
known precipitately above me no above a
right right up here oh it's gonna
fall on one of the windy days
though i will say like boom i
heard one and it just came out
when it gets too bad today ever
climb up and trim that's a very
dangerous shot from tree
i'm jewry it seems very danger gyms
a tree trunk for many it's it's
ah i heard that's one of the
most dangerous jobs in l a because
it's it's a bendy tree it's not
stable well it's not even the falling
is the dangerous part it's the cutting
the the palm tree down in it
hitting you in the head and kill
you know can i tell you that
i recently i've been ah
ah i was telling scott earlier off
mike sorry i bring her off my
conversation into this i like and well
i think it's time we did okay
finally i learned later huh i've been
digitizing old v h s tape oh
yeah it's all my high school shows
oh god started with mary poppins um
where i played the role of birth
the gym your bird so
oh wonderful i was the old banker
oh of course when you invest your
tuppence show wouldn't he be commies um
and i thought in my mind i
did a very good accent
ah and when i saw it i
cannot believe i can't i thought i
had an expectation in my mind of
like well like i don't expect i'm
gonna be great you're a kid okay
whatever yeah i'm so much worse than
i remember
wow huh i not as bad as
some but still not good i remember
certain high school shows is being like
just as good as broadway things it's
like oh oh absolutely absolutely yeah but
it's just the magic of like filling
in all the details yeah yeah that's
just belief it's it's you are having
these experiences
for the you have nothing to compare
it to really yeah you know version
of my fair lady say right now
oh i'm just put on one for
you i miss the one man show
up it all started at a cold
july one man production of hair
up was down and blacklist and that's
when i was bored i woke up
in topsy-turvy world but yeah the my
fair lady i'd never seen it that
it probably also helped it was the
first time ever seeing this story so
it was like i was taken in
by the story and then the the
the lead guy i remember him being
so amazing
and he was like a legend he
graduated right as i came into high
school and he was such a legend
of like you got every good part
he was so amazing and i bet
if i were to actually watch that
show again like as an adult i'd
be like yeah little hammy know i
know i'd love to watch some old
thing like that it's it's wild i
really i
were you getting applause and stuff like
that
no that's all i was doing well
yes is this all your shot to
be on disney's encore oh my god
i keep forgetting i wanna watch that
i watched a few episodes of it
i feel like i got the idea
i want to get the idea i
like episode yeah i tell you the
three to watch oh great um i
when i first heard about that idea
i was like i would ap i
would do that in a heart
we should explain it
yeah it's basically just basically people who
were all in high school together in
a play in a musical usually they
get back together decades later to redo
the play now when when we first
heard the idea jamie thought they did
it like on fucking broadway like a
mounted like oh they
doing a full professional like for one
night obviously but like it was that
they were gonna do a full professional
version what do they do they don't
do it in the actual high school
yeah well that made that's what i
expected yeah but i felt like b'day
they try they do the daily bring
in like broadway performers as ringers to
be like
the chorus sometimes yeah so it's and
they and they do a full set
and they do like a major pro
i can't wait to yeah today they
like track down all the speaking like
whoever had speaking roles and there's they're
really interesting things of like oh this
guy was one of the leads of
oklahoman was a great dancer but now
he's in a wheelchair and so how
is he going to
adapt you know and like delves into
the the beefs behind performers or like
the people who used to be in
a romance who broke up and why
did they break up and all the
stuff it's really it's really good and
i was like oh yeah would i
do it ah you know i went
to like oh yeah that's your dream
i went to the school of the
arts and i was like
and you would love to do that
well the mary poppins the girl who
played mary poppins she like went to
broadway and got a tony nomination from
it and it's like it's wild how
many of them did not pursue like
this is not that wild but yeah
hardly any of them actually pursued showbiz
after that yeah yeah well they're all
also in different states which
i think is another impediment of like
there are certain people who were like
i decided to do it i moved
to new york i tried and and
you know i it just didn't work
out after yeah fiverr eight years there
are some people who are still trying
to do yeah you're racing and they're
and they're the people they're the people
who come in and they're sort of
like like
oh i'm going to be really good
in this and there and sometimes they're
not it's what you do it i
would probably do it i mean if
you were the right show i mean
like if it were like i said
the mary poppins was fun i would
do that and that had like a
guy who was on a nickelodeon show
was burt and but even the ones
from from the high school yeah he
was
yeah yeah so that one is like
those guys were really good like yeah
like it was the school of the
arts so like susan egan is who
i'm talking about she she ah like
voice disney cartoons and she was oh
yeah hitting the beast on broadway and
got a tony lash like she was
mary poppins and she was like professional
grade yeah like great you know this
was high school age
this is high school yeah so we
were all seventeen and and bert was
this guy david sedona who is also
like the best and you know like
ah went into a nickelodeon show out
of that right and so like yeah
i don't think it would be that
different you know like they would all
be just as good as they were
back then i mean for having seen
it i would i would do
and that of all the shows that
we did that was the most fun
i think the and also the one
i could bear like to do again
because we did like carousel which is
weird we did care show he did
the same shows yeah did you the
south pacific no no but we did
godspell really talking about guns i've never
done gods oh but it was it
was
a big it was a big deal
when i was a kid um i
i did yeah it was luther bilis
i was i was jigger jigger craigan
in oklahoma and no no in sars
cartel who is like he's he's criminal
and yeah he's basically the same dude
in oklahoma who is judged as judge
yeah
yeah and i i was shocked
i got i walked into the as
i'm digitizing these i can't like sit
and watch them as it's happening so
i will like check yourself yeah i
just got like a fucking i i
bought a while ago but a vcr
for this purpose right and then it's
just been sitting in the garage and
so i've finally doing it and um
i sent onto that company that we
talked about this though yeah yeah and
i was like i can just
i am to polling i was nervous
about sending them away because i was
like what if i never get back
but you did yes now i have
to figure out what it's out of
your dispose of these v h s
tapes because you can't just throw them
away you can't just throw well they're
not they're not great or not trashing
they're not recyclable why keep bum how
do you do it do you have
to drive to the
jump just shy and keep em um
no there's places that take them so
i have to like blockbusters
yeah it was anyway anymore
do you think you've saved someone dropped
off if you are a person who
disposed of them and someone dropped off
someone to watch em i would yeah
probably yeah i'd favoured enough i'd flip
around see what's on the yeah yeah
um i in in so incorrigible ties
all my porn name
finally digitize all my porn i walked
into the room and it was a
scene where i had like this huge
laugh line where the camera was not
on me because i was on the
other side of the stage oh damn
so there there on this other guy
the guy playing billy bigelow for his
setup to my line and then i
i do the line hugh
huge laugh and the camera fucking slowly
overall effects sort of show who made
the video the schools usually have an
audience yes somebody that they that offered
or said like i'll do it for
this fear whatever the recordings are terrible
and it's one camera yeah it's always
from the back of the room and
yeah always just like random zoom
being in and out when knows the
play and they're trying to yeah you're
out what's happening they're terrible and this
one what's amazing is we paid money
for this it cuts off before yan's
know because it was longer than two
hours since they were doing in high
quality yeah yeah oh yeah the highest
but i saw i walked in the
room my lifeline is missed and then
next i have a scene with
if this young lady named grace grace
maguire um and we have this exchange
where we don't like each other we're
trading insults i one point call or
a wobbly hipped old slut
wow that's a line though isn't it
i rely yeah but it was shocking
to be off scrap and there's people
there's people in the audit it gets
a mixed reaction from the crowd right
wow because there was there's probably slots
in the audience hey yeah they're excited
yes huh
you wobbly
let's look cool
there are gasps there are laughs and
then what you get or what person
applaud oh like six others is oh
well she would also like in someone's
business a lot in the play right
she was like she wants warmly hip
bones a wobbly hipped old slut my
my friends when we were entitled that
say i like
never heard it before when we were
in jesus christ superstar it was it
was like one of the better productions
i've ever done this was well i
thought you would save all time high
voltage this was when i was incredible
but it was it was it it
it you got raves like anyone who
came to it was like in tears
the entire time and it was oh
yeah i've not experienced that it was
it was one of the better shows
i'd ever done and my friend who
was in it ended up filming every
night of it with closeups and stuff
and then was going to edit it
together
wow and he did the most amazing
you know in the overture of jesus
christ superstar and yeah he did the
most amazing montage of people getting ready
for the shit like backstage stuff that's
somebody always amazing and then he got
up to like song two and gave
up on the projects because the rest
of the video is all just a
one ca
camera she sang so zaman did finish
it but he stopped finishing it good
yeah he finished he only finished like
two or three songs of it and
then was like this is just too
much fucking it's so so amazing for
everyone now yeah it was happening behind
the scenes stuff is really the best
i mean i don't have anything yeah
it's crazy like now with your having
your phone i feel like anyone who
as a school play must have so
much footage yeah yeah everything but we
just had like i have like other
photos of behind the scenes kind of
stuff a little bit we did a
concert in this band that i was
in for one night only we were
we like rehearsed over and over and
over and we only did one performance
and were you nervous ah
no and i in fact overslept and
barely made it to it because it
was midnight coffee because he was on
the news on this stage after a
performance of the normal heart we so
it was at midnight or something and
i used like went to sleep accidentally
and then they had to call me
and wake me up and and get
me there but the guy
yeah who shot that did all the
back stage stuff and like edited it
together and it was like that's one
of the few video tapes i have
alright that's that's cool where it's like
oh wow this is like a almost
a professional grade thing of a dumb
show that i did you know if
you need a digitized i'm your man
hey if you need one thing digitized
i'll
do it might take you up on
that good offer actually if i find
an old tape yeah oh wait yeah
was like one thing before we go
to break paul has a thing i
am remembering now gotta break i'll get
it okay we'll be right back
welcome back to threesome i remembered what
i was going to talk about say
it at the end of mary poppins
which i guess was that was our
we did we would do a fall
show and we would do a i
should say a winter show spring show
and the winter show was always children's
theatre and so when we did mary
poppins
at the very end of the tape
i completely forgot about this and have
no recollection of it whatsoever
we sang a couple christmas songs in
like we all leave the stage we
go somewhere wherever we go the camera
does not follow us so in pitch-black
we're singing you know oh come all
ye faithful or something near the end
this is how the tape ends at
the nfl come all ye faithful the
camera which is still been locked off
on the stage santa claus appears it
says merry christmas everybody he walks down
into the audience goes over to lap
these city slugs
notes so let's read a different joke
with the only way to show they
legendary oh yes huh let's say wow
boy you tell who probably don't say
i'm sex not going to super high
school plays but if they hear their
talk to bezier like i hear they
mention sluts and carousel um so santa
comes out says merry christmas
is everybody applauds he walks off walks
off stage into the audience um there's
a he goes to like the second
row he leans over and starts talking
to some people in the second row
we all the rest of the cats
like comes in behind like in the
background in front of the stage and
we start see
seeing some other christmas carol while santa
has
same shit with his back to the
camera with these people we've finished a
song and then the show's over who
who's even like i have no idea
what you have no recollection was so
weird oh wait i wonder range i
wonder if he was like going to
do something right after the show like
he walks down and gives a present
to elizabeth
and then it comes on stage goes
and like does a little speech because
they didn't put it in yeah i
don't know it looks like he's giving
them news like hey by the way
your grandma died
we are at war with iraq
i'll tell you
alright it's three your time this is
something called rated scene oh yeah this
is submitted by kristin kelly hello kristin
hikers saying yeah alright
first we improvise a two minute scene
oh no it has to be g
rated oh come on hold on i
think i think i see where this
is going lauren and you're gonna be
surprised we didn't listen then we do
the same scene over again we make
a pg how can we do it
again we all have an understanding with
that is we make energy thirteen one
f way
word and not in a nonsexual sense
and then we finally do it as
r rated okay we don't do mc
seventeen we knew we could do x
we can do x alright hold on
a second lso g i of course
is very sweet and nice i get
that yeah pg you can say damn
and hell and have it be have
it tough things happen later a little
adult right yeah yeah that's alright but
pg thirteen for instance a person who's
thirteen
with their parents present um thirteen you
can say a bunch of curse words
but you can only say the effort
f word once in a nonsense third
in a non-sexual context and then are
you can say the f word you
can be whatever you want but there's
no sex so actual cgi thirteen you
could say fuck you wanna stick my
dick in your pussy yeah i don't
see but i said fucking a non-sexual
yes that that does count and then
then are you can't show a male
erect penis but you can show i
wasn't going
we you know what
floppy dicks yeah alright let's start here
we go two minutes am do we
need a suggestion so okay here we
go are you timing i'm doing okay
dad dad yes what is it sweetheart
yes we're your two dads the dog
got out oh no is that why
the cops
did you call the police i called
the police because you always told me
if anything bad ever happened i should
call nine one one it's it's not
really a nine one one issue it's
it's it's more of a let's go
out ourselves and look and then call
we called but we're glad your ghostbusters
so that's right but we're glad you
are listening to us sonny thanks good
dad
dad that makes you the bad dad
i won why because you were scolding
you all good dead so like i
i'm still a good person i didn't
go that you don't remember what he
said thanks for listening to us i
never said you were a good i
think you're a good person but i
do not thank you for listening to
us i thank you for listening to
us i think he could be a
better per
listen wow bonnie go to bed we
get but the dog oh that's right
dog listen can i tell you a
secret and you can't tell bad dad
okay i'll just go over here the
dog's not coming back honey what do
you mean he doesn't like it here
this is really g
were you guys talking about huh there's
nothing dead said the dog doesn't like
it here and he's not coming back
dogs come why we are i'm sorry
i had to tell it felt right
what why would you lie to me
about the dog dog doesn't like you
are you sure the dog didn't just
die in isn't heaven in your honor
oh shit
shit this is feeling pg oh shit
oh oh my god
and see my pink wow we cannot
even get through to two minutes is
too long my pitch to agree my
pitches that it gets shorter at each
time i do a new thing because
it's like you're just going alright mini
led piaf thirty for the first for
the eugene let's just go right to
pg thirteen yeah we are
he said she said shit unfortunate so
that was the that was the bad
news bears era pg yeah that's true
so you get when you get one
f word you only get one focus
yeah and it has to be non-sexual
alright ready and go fuck what happened
dog got out oh no god i
want to say something so bad but
like yeah i wish i
i'd express my feelings about that dad
dad stop making out we need to
find the dog honey i love him
very much i want to shove my
tongue down his throat find something i
want to receive his tongue
wait yeah well this tourney is he's
seventeen so
my penis is not erect though don't
worry well mine is wham dunk weight
because see you can talk about it
though it's blue and honey
but yeah
okay alright i don't feel like oh
yeah i think we've missed this whole
thing you know kelly this is what
you wanted as a christian kristin kelly
ah okay let's do
do you want to go the other
way ah sure okay minute thirty we
start our okay and then we'll go
through yes and gee i like plants
turning it on a ten minute thirty
here we go
hey fuckers what's up hey can you
stop sucking my dick long enough for
us to talk no
there is a new scene where we
have a child oh yes
why do i have to suck your
dick in every scene we do
ah i don't know let's try to
get okay okay okay doocy new sushi
okay here we go and go
hey guys um the fuck do you
want what is it i'm sorry to
disturb you i know i'm supposed to
be on guard duty but i think
i saw something suspicious goddamn piece of
shit you know so liar these two
fucking assholes come up to me on
the street and they're like hey do
you
got a cigarette and i'm like good
the flaw gay yeah they probably thought
your limp dick was a cigarette which
is the same way hey hitting five
is not hard so skinny and little
and pure white with brown tips
smoke coming out of the yangtze
i hate p g thirteen version ready
to go fuck hey guys
hey what's wrong
i heard that guy ask you for
a cigarette yeah well i wanted to
say there's something suspicious out there these
guys came up to me were like
say they're like you do you have
a light or did you have a
cigarette and i was like get the
hell addy writes out your oh wow
yeah it presumably limp dick yeah yeah
let's talk about my ding dong
but describe it please well it's shriveled
and see yeah
g version oh no and go that
was me
hey guys what's up um i was
you know how i was playing outside
yeah um these kids came up and
asked if i had candy why don't
you put your little cigarettes
and see
ah i think we did
ah i mean no one wants us
to play the game correctly oh guys
thanks for listening all this fun so
late
we're done
uh