three
wow
oh me yeah oh yeah hey guys
i watched american idol the other day
the premiere where claudia conway was on
oh my god i cannot have
happen with that oh i don't know
by the time this comes out i
don't know and i'm not about to
watch another episode so but it just
was it seemed like so much like
oh let's get this teen girl who's
in this precarious situation to audition for
our show and that'll get a lot
of people to watch it because politics
are so in the news even a
singer so she's she's
okay but the the reason i brought
it up is because we were all
waving our hands when we did that
and that is such that is an
affectation that i just cannot stand when
singers yeah like try to scribble the
node in the air you know what
i mean
it reminds me of when the people
that would lead the songs at church
um there was this one guy who
ah would do it every week and
he would try to debut rush
yeah he was really charismatic beautiful long
curly hair and most mysterious glasses um
he would um raise and lower he
would you like stick out two fingers
and raise and lower them indicate where
the notes were going to to guide
people or
people are just for himself see the
signal no two guy because he was
not a dynamic singer right yeah
that's that's what i heard about i've
destroyed the show right yeah i think
i want a weird thing to grider
holding up wow my choir director in
middle school and how she would have
us sing over the orange in our
oh that's interesting like like ah
ah like projecting over over note rightly
worn orange so your mouth is like
really wide and open and that is
why you want to do orange is
the new black yeah because i was
like that'll i'll make some slot thing
she saw
okay i'll be famous
you know i would think of that
that visual makes me think of when
i would have when i was a
kid i had a terrible cough that
was aggravated by i think i grass
um because i would come in after
like oh yeah literally grass yeah i
would i would you know like a
dog out here mowing the lawn
coughing i would i would like lie
awake in bed just like coffee for
how long that's horrible for like hours
no i mean how many years of
your life um probably till high school
probably so so when you were very
young whistling high school is like saying
like hey why you guys keep coughing
like that no they all started to
me please keep k why i keep
please leave a comment how do you
share a room with
the most at one time was was
to other people my brothers we were
all in one room one point was
that because you had a new addition
to the family who needed a room
or yes my little brother probably honestly
i'm i i can't see you because
the sun is blazing from behind you
so it's just like your voice that
i'm looking off into the distance and
you're answering
as a comforting yeah ok lauren you
are good the sun is the sun
is setting and it is currently employing
guys singing and mine to be honest
but at some point it'll be down
and it will be three am after
dark so get ready for that when
that happens shit gets yes the gloves
are numinous cuss words yeah i'm too
scared
i use them now i'm very scared
hello a singing over the yard so
what it made me think of is
when i would have the bad coffin
i would try to um ah get
and i would this would this happen
when it would be sick too and
i would have a cough like you're
so hard to describe i would picture
a sort of uh
um like a tube in my in
my throat
next season it's also not after dark
yeah sorry oh yeah sorry sun still
up i retract it but like having
to get the air like like in
order to get the cough to be
over this is fucking hard to describe
okay i'm gonna try to imagine it
like going through the you would have
to get over the the curve in
the tube right i think you mean
like the flutter it's almost like a
cam maybe it was a cane shape
yes yeah i would think of it
as right and it's like you're trying
to get you're trying to get it
yeah yeah turn rural huh
it's like you're choking and you just
needed to come out right did you
ever see a doctor for it or
could you not afford yeah probably both
did your parents make you pay for
the doctor trips every man didn't even
when i was a kid they were
like okay we're giving a running tally
of everything you owe
there aren't they're not parents who do
that probably i have a friend who
has parent he has like a a
sort of dynamic with his parents and
money were
they'll like give him a loan that
helped him he's like an adult now
he just started getting a job where
he didn't really need you anymore but
there were periods of time where he
would like get a loan from them
or they would like buy his car
then or you know he would take
their old car and like pay them
off monthly installments yeah and it's like
very transactional and like plan like everyone's
aware
air of how much is owed right
yeah i don't know i feel like
that's i don't know but once you're
once you graduate or leave the house
yeah i can see that i'm yeah
i'm just saying there i feel like
i've read something where some parents tallied
up literally everything they ever spent on
their kid and then gave this sounds
familiar oh so mean like when they
turned
eighteen it's like hey here's fifty two
thousand dollars yesterday in the world that's
it's that's beyond it's completely insane like
that's what having a kid is yeah
your idea is stupid yeah you liked
fucking oh it's not after dark the
sun stamp sorry pose for six kids
in your family yeah yeah that's a
lot of kids too many actually just
think about this too
cause i have a friend who is
having a third child and then i
was we were talking about another friend
who has three kids i was like
oh she'll probably be excited you are
having three kids and she was like
she's about ever fourth and i was
like there are people having four and
five and six it is weird to
think about because i i just feel
like one would be enough yeah but
it's
but maybe to six kids like i
always thought i'd be the funniest thing
in the world when i was a
kid like it just seems like oh
my god it's so like all movies
that have like a bunch of yeah
home alone yeah yeah and you're like
oh my god just like chaos and
i love it and i still i
still really like that idea but then
as an adult it just sounds like
as an adult how do you mean
yeah yes you
go like well they're all going to
take care of themselves or something i
get i don't know but they don't
um i it's honestly more fun as
an adult to have a bunch of
siblings yeah than i was as a
kid why did you feel like you
always were fighting with somebody i always
was but it's also because because the
were spaced down it's like my sisters
were
moving out of the house not like
the sisters they were and are doing
it for themselves um so they were
they were so much older than i
was because i was at the other
end of the line that we didn't
really have that kind of vibe that
you see in the movies or whatever
like i was a tiny kid to
them alright you know what i mean
and right although i do remember one
i remember one time being in my
sister's bedroom with her and her friends
when i was little and they were
all um cooing over my eyelashes and
they like and they put mascara oh
yeah i would love to do that
to you oh boy yeah when i
once code is done i wa
gonna do it felt very i remember
that feeling i think that really imprinted
on me so i'm sure have to
get that foot tigger when i when
i was in high school my friend
had who i would hang out with
a lot had two siblings who are
twins who are like five and it
was so fun like i loved being
around them i thought it was just
like the best and i'm sure that
like love dicks
like high school girls who are like
wanting to like you know hang out
with them and play yeah so it's
cute like the guy who wanted the
rocky horror picture show videotape he was
nearly forgot about the previous episode i
know i can remember what the situation
was a guy who i i said
to recap i said i think my
uncle take that off of select oh
yea and then he when i said
oh he doesn't have any more he's
like we're you're gonna go to his
house and search through all his stuff
because you promised me word is bond
so
crazy anyway yeah eleven siblings eleven cause
they were you know
lps which i don't think so anymore
lcs is not little addiction hits
anyways can't say these little dick shit
is
a friend of graham who had there
were five siblings and that really seemed
like a lot and but they have
like i think their life was very
like creative because they had to find
all these ways to like stand out
well no because like just because my
shi'i my kids yeah they were all
very like the paint their furniture and
i'd be like funky and cool and
like
high goals that you know in the
fine things in the alley and make
it into something where you were you
in the suburbs lauren in chicago or
where you you were so yeah was
i mean i felt growing up in
the suburbs everything just look the same
in every house you know what i
mean like everyone just little pink bow
is you and i don't know i
don't know
how it compares but i feel like
my suburb wasn't fully a suburb like
it's ok it's around okay and it's
and there's like for example like unique
architecture like there's not each house is
different from the last one it's not
like there's it's like the brady bunch
style or you know like um like
one town over
like much more like every home was
built in the sixties and they all
the same right but like our town
i like there's older homes and more
character so so did everyone sort of
it felt like in the suburbs everyone
wanted to decorate their houses alike in
a way like yeah no i did
that did that vibe did but when
you're in the city it's like oh
wow this person has this sense of
style
yes it is this sense of sight
i think that carried over a bit
because most of my friends grew up
each house was completely like i had
a friend that really modern house mid-century
sort of than there's like the really
like crafty and then there's like a
victorian like there's just like different vibes
ooh what was your parents decorate huh
it's i would say what's hard to
like give it a name i guess
but i would say like goff cozy
um but very decorated like it's it's
like each room is like all the
choices are made so it's not like
for example i might have mentioned this
like i couldn't hang like a poster
on my wall really wow
oh oh what was the poster going
to be i don't know i just
it was never an option really it
was like joe trippi art on the
wall that's like framed and then i
have like a bulletin board i can
put stuff on the bullets oh i
see but they buddy poster would be
out of the decorating style yeah i'd
like to just look like shit like
yeah but like i always like would
think it was cool my friend's house
we have magazine like got milk ads
a lot of yeah yeah that was
like really cool huh okay oh my
god get every got milk huh
based on the wall like a big
collage
now let's remember i mean other you
are doing that but i'm saying like
do remember those ads they were i
remember the ads i just have never
thought anyone would cut them out and
make like in like you know seventeen
magazine then you're like oh yeah the
drew barrymore one or like whatever then
it's like you kind of collectible it's
like the precursor like that when the
big kids would put absolut ads when
they got to
oh absolutely that's also a very popular
thing yes yeah god that's so my
god that's funny i forgot about absolut
and that's way less interesting than the
got milk one sees the neighborhood i
lived in was weird because it's neighbor
called mount airy which when i tell
people i'm from philadelphia and then if
they're from philadelphia and san fernando and
he's like oh well not really feel
adelphia then fucking cock like little dick
shit heads there little did he know
that about the sunset though yeah but
at the same time um when i
was in heis i remember when i
was in high school i had i
had two girlfriends not at the same
time um so now talking about your
girlfriends that was my thing yeah now
i gotta hear about this
two scouts girl rwanda whoa
um their parents forbade them from from
coming to my neighborhood interesting because black
people lived in my neighborhood oh that's
all for for in their minds for
some reason it was my neighborhood was
extremely dangerous and there is crime and
yeah but it's like it really wasn't
it was just like a very normal
it was very basic what's it like
ah
you know rocky where you see you
know the stoops and the you know
no no no no my neighborhood was
much more suburban than that yeah yeah
yeah like there were there were there
were houses as opposed to row homes
right right um and we although we've
lived in a duplex but joining my
cousin's house right um
that in that way it was like
growing up with a lot of siblings
because we had a lot of um
matches in age oh so we we
all like we all play a lot
together anyway their shared a backyard there
were seven of them so there were
thirteen kids sharing a backyard going and
say i think that's like yeah that's
so me
many kids yeah and how did your
parents afford that with the six kids
my dad worked for the railroad all
the live loan choo-choo and my sound
bearing learning my mom
i remember his name was ah yeah
yeah yeah he had a way better
name it it was he and i
worked named kafka
sir yes sir topham hatt no really
no yeah ah and then my mom
worked as a receptionist for her brother's
piano tuning business oh okay and things
that look like he's looking for samurai
he's like he's like myself nah
yeah did you feel like you were
aware of finances growing up oh for
sure yeah it was a it was
a constant topic of discussion i will
say that we never wanted for anything
like we never went hungry we never
didn't have clothes we did shop at
the goodwill you know what i mean
but we were not i remember my
mother saying saying years later like my
children never knew that they were poor
oh that's nice yeah and we'd tell
i told them doesn't she every night
when they went to see your poor
i wish we were probably like lower
middle class that's how i feel you
feel like you didn't know and did
you feel like you know i never
i never felt like i they never
they would my mother would make us
keenly aware of how much shit costs
and what we could not afford like
frivolous things that were we were off
the table
but there was there was never a
she never gave us any panic about
it she never gave us any indication
my dad was laid off at one
point too and i remember that it
was um i'd like to demonstrate collection
that it was a big deal because
they hid that stuff from us very
artfully interesting yeah because they didn't want
you to worry yeah i
it was probably the i mean it
was probably didn't want us to worry
it's probably a pride thing was probably
like you know whatever but it was
it was also probably like but what
the fuck did how could we understand
it you know i mean you even
helped yeah why i couldn't i wouldn't
i put my foot down i like
as soon as i could talk i
was like let's get one thing straight
i'm the kid you're the adult i
didn't ask to be brought in here
ah here but i can take you
i was very precocious and imagined oh
cute i want one tooth missing those
i'll lick my beautiful eyelashes mascara that
you never watched ah
to this day
wow i will say um just one
thing about my bedroom growing up is
that it was always really cute and
i don't want to sound like i
didn't get to have anything fun because
i feel like if anyone in my
family are there like gorillas it's like
i'm complaining about nothing magazine i remember
her name beautiful grey and and the
bars
the door just my mom was always
down to like repaint my room even
though it was have like i had
a very small bedroom right right like
it was difficult but my parents were
always like wallpaper what kind of wallpapers
you on and and it's like and
then i have to help them put
it up and then like two years
later it's it's like trains would you
get it's i'm too old for it
and then it's like well yeah
twenty one you're gonna have to scrape
it off yourself stupid and like that's
extreme home makeover they're like this kid
like you know that show yeah really
move the truck and then the whole
house is like they would always do
theme rooms like kid kid likes cats
so his room's a little box and
shit this room every make it so
insane and then you're like in one
day that i think i'm yeah wasn't
pleased today it's like it just next
year did we beat the shit yeah
who said i liked cats like this
they're bringing the show back like i
heard that rumor yeah maybe i enjoy
that kind of thing i hope people
are hearing this whim because it's like
it's picked up oh my god it's
it's like we're at the beach here
okay yeah sure this is chose freedom
after dark almost pure chiles it's all
it's freedom freedom freedom during sunsets oh
we're about to
get wild over here she might gonna
go down my parents bought artwork from
museums i think they bought prints those
belong in a museum about the mona
lisa
but they they you know they were
always up and i always you know
they're always up on this wall and
i i got to know them very
well because i would stare at them
now i get it like ferry idler
but but i what i don't know
ferris bueller why don't i get like
a more like cameron um they went
to the museum offering stare a cameron
staring and then
oh wow please please please let me
know what i want please it's getting
his dad singing pointillism without without what
they were looking at stuff like george
surat but my parents it was just
such a weird collection of things that
they like not the same style they
were just random like okay here's a
painting of a guy with some bread
i'm stupid and i just did i
always looked at i'm going like do
they like these i don't know what
it is and they would always make
me depressed because i'd stare at them
for eighteen nineteen or twenty years you
know sometimes i think about like what
people hang on the wall and i
get sad right but boy am i
gonna make it said also thinking about
them the hopefulness of hanging it on
the wall yeah but what i found
out
was that they were they were they
were worth something i guess oh really
and that's why they never got rid
of him i was just always like
can we rush into shit um er
som for oh i don't know i
don't know whatever happened to it but
i was surprised when just five years
ago i think my my parents were
like oh yeah that that appreciated in
value and it ended up being worth
like
a thousand dollars for something like a
mona lisa
i never said that i said
but this is the same as my
beanie babies
i didn't even question
ah i'm not crazy she's great
ah
i was so your baby
very strong beanie baby collection that's your
dog's draw i said i love a
good one lower this is strong physical
action i gotta say i've seen a
few baby collections praising the straw
just one the very first one they
ever made i think if the first
one was a polar bear i had
that one the first beanie baby was
premature
and i would go i would save
six dollars and then go buy them
by how would you get the six
dollars chores and whatnot and then i
would what's the whatnot you're gonna stream
or specific like getting a birthday card
or like something where you get a
little money or something like actually sir
you dollars for valentine's day my grandma's
car give
money for valid likes huh why i'm
gonna crush on her jamerson see bill
in the mail it's a thing that
is classic grandma's classic great i love
it absolutely like oh look at all
these two dollar bills at the bank
oh i know what i'll do she
always goes thinking you look at all
of these two dollar bills at the
bank
the frame
nice
big pile of them she asks for
him and then i will save and
get my six dollars and then i
would walk and go to the store
there is little store in evanston called
mostly handmade and it was a very
cute little always the stuff that wasn't
having pool tables
it was like most things weren't handmade
i would say because teeny babies as
guys like i like gifts like they
were made in china gift shop and
meeting j j president don't
yeah ah so awesome said the president
gu yasha
anyways and i collected a bunch with
my mom secretly sold some of them
why after i care i was like
stop plant you know i think it
was after they were just at box
for a long time she sold some
because they were starting to become worth
hundreds each like well also they're probably
not worth that much anymore no peak
she was definitely crazy inventive real babies
she was definitely right to do it
but i remember we upset okay oh
my god you're right care betrayed she'll
jump and we usually would it saves
you from choking i don't know i
can't breathe gotta get it over the
two but anyway um well so did
she give you the money or did
she know i don't know what happened
i don't know if she'll
i don't know which one she sold
and i but i think she still
has the box and i'm probably going
to teach she has like a fur
coat she bought right afterwards yeah she's
got a look in my manager's fun
dalmatian puppies because made out of babies
what are you what did you do
that guy that'll be doing his legs
dangling at the bottom look at my
beauty volca oh my
the princess diana went like that was
the most expensive one it started to
become worth so much money oh and
still how again was it a princess
diana not even anything it's a purple
bear right has a crown oh well
that's related i'm gonna look up how
much it is right now um okay
my bitcoin why didn't we all buy
bitcoin i feel like such an asshole
as it seemed dumb it does seem
dumb i wish someone told me to
just remember i remember a friend of
mine was like i really just want
one bitcoin there at like one hundred
and fifty bucks right now and i
was like yeah it didn't seem interesting
to me but i mean why not
get fifty thousand no one is worth
fifty tess oh my god i'd be
so happy about one oh
i had fifty thousand dollars for bitcoin
is a it isn't a physical thing
um no it's an online thing right
yeah oh my god what e bay
wow
whoa you're kidding it's a site where
are ya
yeah bet on stuff okay where are
you think the print is staying and
eighty does not have a crown it
has a white flower on it's chest
it's just purple with a white flower
it's basically nothing okay okay this one
person is saying eighteen thousand dollars or
best offer oh hey it's maybe worth
ten then another one says to chain
other ones
thousand dollars or best offer another one's
two thousand than one's ninety five here's
where we start getting hero three first
edition princess diana beanie babies must read
i don't know if i'm going to
read this whole thing but guess how
much they want seven hundred two thousand
dollars and two hundred seven hundred to
two thousand seven hundred and two thousand
dollars or two thousand two hundred dollars
for three
of them yeah that's a lot of
money that's insane i'm starting to complete
i'm gonna all you're gonna do the
division for zag it says must reads
now mean i was and i am
gonna read it okay okay no you'll
get cursed
oh rand you rinku
huh
oh right right oh my god what
oh my god you're kidding first edition
are you actually reading this stupid this
is a real two first edition ghost
versions with a first issue pdcs ghost
this princess will change history less than
fifteen are known to be in the
world of the ghost version it's no
vulgar questions if she will sell this
this is based on over three hundred
plus offers when it comes down to
this version of the princess ghost version
so-called noodles are totally clueless oh and
st john's fired they can only guess
and speculate no proof no facts no
documentation nothing trust the number one beam
maybe authenticator in the world i currently
have yeah
they have seven
ghost version
wow with certificates of authenticity there's always
some listeners who know what this trust
the number one be a syndicator the
war meek who are you going to
believe your choice i'm also willing to
show it support me and see fire
from another current owner previous or until
better establish a timeline for this version
of the princess what a weirdo
oh i'm okay what can i ask
and do you know why is it
called the princess diana beanie baby because
it was a memorials commemorate it was
dedicated to her came out when she
died or when she was born
nothing in between once you're divorced turn
the wiki oh the wick is this
i mean are we seriously going to
the wiki we're following you
oh weeki take us to the wiki
lore and take us to the wiki
oh my god but there's probably a
listener who knows like your site there
so probably this prefer an original suggested
price of five to seven dollars in
nineteen eighty seven with proceeds benefiting the
diana princess of wales memorial fund today
the going rate is as low as
two dollars or
or maybe up to thirty according to
love my beanies dot com depending on
what kind of pellets are inside why
so hopefully based i've still list their
bears at upwards of sixty five thousand
there's little evidence that any five thousand
little evidence that any of soul wow
that's crucial i love it they asked
for this gigantic amount and then say
or best
offer seven thousand or fifteen dollars yeah
i should just order one for two
dollars just make them stop that's so
one hundred games to one of the
gamestop people flood the market where i
live demo and then make them worth
a lot it does my wish i
understood game stuff when it was happening
and that i did something about it
did what deregulated so called your congress
person i wish i had stopped it
i want i want to understand what
people are just getting money while i
live here look over here by the
way georgia lawley oh yeah mark it
up lady sit up ladies yeah i
enjoy your sago enjoy yourself
it's later than you think enjoy remember
i played the i was singing that
once because the specials did version of
it on their second album and my
and my grandma was like you know
that show it's for my for my
generation no ma'am i got ya
homemade record of me singing your favorite
whisper what do you think the first
person to ever go like i am
ah oh ah choices giving oh i
hope it was an actual old person
who notice their voice suddenly wavering their
fiftieth oh now these the oh
intimating dignity my god not only my
ball didn't need ah of cain
ah orthopedic shoe wig
edo wig i be joining him almost
a week again because hey mostly see
when we say it while wig you
sick freaks
i love it we love it said
louis city
it does make me sad when i
think about people collecting things in a
way and i'm someone who collects stuff
but i collect stuff for pleasure i
don't collect it
for just sell it to sell it
but i don't know any collection is
kind of a form of insanity like
collections i've collected things and then gotten
sick of collecting them yeah because it
does it does take up space and
it's like i don't want these i
don't know i go through periods where
i will accrue things that for
for some reason i feel like a
sense of completion about them yeah and
then i realised i don't care that
much like this is just taking up
space in my home know i collect
miniatures and i'm now really wanting a
really good way to display them and
i want it to be like ah
a lot of like a huge wall
eventually yeah oh i want be
so fun to me
and what we know when we've been
very well we wouldn't be fun for
my yeah he likes them too oh
he likes him okay so what what
room would you put him i don't
know it's it feels like a hallway
sort of thing like kind of like
you know you need some sort of
i haven't a little display right now
but it's full so i need to
yeah um some sort of shelving but
i want to have a cover on
it
it should almost be framed because they're
so small then they can fall you
know yeah and break yeah we have
we've lived in our home for
gods since i've been here in years
seventy years were ghost and the people
of new and we're trying to get
them out i knew one of us
was a ghost um i um and
i want to push the we saw
very little up on the walls because
janie is a little bit more a
new user
oh my god you love it you
love it you love it life went
out she's more what like you gotta
hang it just right she oh it's
not even hang it just right it's
like what deserves to be up on
the wall well this kind of my
point about people putting up like random
ass shit and i mean i've been
guilty of it
but like there's a feeling of like
wait you're gonna look at that every
every day yeah yeah yeah what i've
i've got a lot of things you
need to we have a lot of
things around a picture of you and
you gave me through that door and
i was like yeah
no and it meant a lot to
me did you hang it up it's
on my desk so i don't have
any wall space unfortunately oh well sorry
why tell you it's facing more i
see it more yeah well you made
it to my wall with the same
exact picture i'm sorry i look at
the picture view way more than i
look behind me at the pictures right
oh so like at your in your
setup that you have that you've posted
online of your like podcast area yes
you have a lot of photos up
there yes so that's like you do
feel like that's like your designated spots
like hey whenever you want
yeah well for sure i that that
you're offer that's my office so ah
on the walls i have ah
you know most it's almost all work
stuff yeah so it's not it's not
like our life together so that is
absolutely i can put whatever but i
did kind of in my mind i
was like well this is my workspace
so i'm gonna put stuff from my
work life my work-life you know up
here
and but we have things that we
had on the walls in previous places
that we've lived that we haven't hung
up in the new the new house
we've been in for seven years right
and i i want to yeah i
want to stuff up on the walls
there's a bunch of things and it's
like our and also whenever i take
a picture of the house
it's are something like over christmas two
pictures of the christmas tree and then
on either side of the christmas tree
the walls are just bare and it's
like this looks weird to me yeah
it doesn't look lived in yeah yeah
and there's i i like i like
other people's artwork on their walls and
photos and what they have we do
have one salon wall
that we hired a guy to do
like a task rabbit thing because we're
bad we're both bad at like measuring
and everything oh and taskrabbit okay i
will be happy to answer new shows
like csi real rabbit yeah scott i
don't wanna spoil it um so we
got this guy we wanted to have
all these all these photos on this
one wall
and i told the guy like yeah
they if you space them out like
ah an inch between the photos whatever
inch between the ideal was between
the idea was in our minds we
would keep adding pictures to this yeah
once we got like the middles the
base we would on the outer edges
we'd seen and even easier to do
because then you have like the the
guy and so kind of yes yes
well this guy filled the entire wall
will be the the orpik pilot
it's like just a battle
a little initiative any get it i
understand i don't know why but guidelines
make that answered my question because yeah
i thought about taskrabbit um i'm i'm
having the geek squad of mount my
tv shore and i was thinking first
about taskrabbit because i know people who've
done that but i'm like isn't a
task
but just likes someone who is random
like they don't necessarily know how to
do the thing like i'm right you
need a special i've never looked at
the site so i'm just like do
they do they say like i'm really
good at this this this this order
they kind of go like i'll do
whatever you need me to do i
don't remember i guess rambling any man
who will like come over to your
house and fix the fence
so yeah gambled like he was he'll
grind our knives you know he goes
up there na is god huh and
daddy you know oh it's funny
that's ugh that's my favorite song what
is it that's sort of oliver lang
knife grinder and will buy who will
buy this wonderful feeling there was a
knife grinder in my town growing up
is already saying nice knives to gras
a dive to mcgraw by the way
i didn't even sing that part i
remember the guy from high school kid
yesterday high school and it's it's in
my mind i honestly it was a
joy to sing it again because it's
in my mind a law i think
whenever i hear the word knife i
think yeah definitely
i'm gonna think about it now
i like it even knife grinder person
though and there's one um that was
at the like back when we could
have a farmers market there was a
guy there and and we got knives
sharp and i was like oh yeah
doi like i never done that doi
dot your god deut oh yeah but
no i understand you're supposed to do
that when you have a good set
of knives so yeah i think we
have to go to
commercial policing knives to grind on our
way out please no knives knives to
gras hi daddy knives to grow these
asking for like alright we'll be right
back
and we're back bay knives like ground
too much and then they get really
little yeah it's just like a little
nope
that's how the liberals played a little
metal triangle on top of the big
big knife handle but honestly like over
time that doesn't get worn down so
it's just like nothing i mean i
guess like i guess you'd probably get
rid of it before then yeah i
don't know did penny draw a knife
oh you gotta it's like you have
to call animal control
old pick up wrecking shit
you have to go stick it in
a record first and then animal control
will come you call seven one one
they come and get your knives
don't throw away knives and seems dangerous
um paul did you when you were
growing up did they i remember clearly
the year that they invented the what
looked like a switchblade and then you
would press the button and it was
a comb and you know yeah one
of those freak people out of like
oh my god he's got a knife
and insight because colin's arthur funds are
really
did it on happy day yeah yes
that's cool it was a coveted item
is so cool oh so so fucking
not a great comb not a great
comb no no because it really short
it's funny like combs were a big
thing when i was a kid like
divock yeah you would get him for
birthday presents absolutely you get all comb
set yeah yeah yeah yeah and your
birthday well no no no from friends
a friend would give you a comb
yeah that sucks yeah it's cool i
never got it from a friend for
me it would be
always like stocking stuff for christmas time
from it for me i remember early
like she combs said i remember birthday
party at chuck e cheese where someone
gave me a wallet now me i'm
ten so i'm ten yes you look
like shit you're a ghost i'm ten
um but no i remember getting a
wallet getting a comb you know it's
just like real use it
i'll remember getting a comb on picture
day yes yes yes yes i'll try
remember the last time i combed my
hair with a comb like i brush
my hair with a brush i use
a horse calm ass i use horses
as yours
i usually ah you know what i
usually would use a comb but i
stopped because i was told that with
my hair texture that's worse because they
have out we know because i have
wavy hair like makes it laying flatter
if i comb it and if i
just let it air-dry without combing it
and puts i just put little stuff
and let it air-dry that it's more
weight
even with more volume okay so there
you have anyone out there with wavy
hair has been combing and feeling like
you get to hear a little doll
one time i was on ecstasy at
a new year's eve party yeah okay
spice it up a little and i
brushed marilyn rice cubs hair
this is a greatly film actually just
thought you were like that story was
so boring i'm gonna pin em dough
if it is something way more interesting
i i can't remember if i so
i think i said in the guy
asked her to my brush your hair
that's so and she said sure and
so we're done it but she i
sat in a chair and she sat
on the floor in front of me
and i brushed her hair for like
wishing
salou or i don't think that she
was oh you no i can't remember
she might be a you don't need
to be to enjoy that it's exactly
like yes wait is that like a
a tip for all you eligible bachelor
russia girls here at a party shall
love it sure whoa do you remember
aaron and erin gives her brides office
and they're gonna brush people's hair
yeah their live show they said recently
on the bug is that they were
gonna have like a a braiding artist
to be there but like do people's
erin
by the way the sun is shining
down i mean it's down but behind
everything we can't even see it anymore
so is i mean can't see each
other is it from scared is it
three am after dark yet it's time
circus curse words but fuck
do you say budva as said fuck
ho ahead of the penis
just just the tip avila
shaft of the penis vein
skin of the penis
lauren is appears to be a menorah
the first time you saw a penis
hey like a live one yeah the
life out of a dead person not
at the morgue yeah
was it was it like oh that's
good did it did so i am
crazy for you don't remember what i
don't remember um
that moment it's three am after dark
everyone remember that you don't remember no
i don't remember what i thought of
it okay i don't i three master
dark by the way so you can
say play on it so you can
say whatever you want it's actually what
i find kind of interesting about it
is that i have no idea i
don't remember thinking anything about that i'm
sure i did but i don't
yeah and it's like you know this
is one of the problems with the
way that i've journaled my whole life
is that like i wouldn't have written
that in there in case katherine shot
yeah but it's like that's the kind
of thing that i'd love to see
too right yeah yeah yeah should parents
have an agreement that they will never
read a journal like my mom said
you would never she's claimed she'd never
has cracked one and i've i mean
i believe it but would she tell
you that when she when you were
younger like by the way i'm never
going to use your journey yes oh
that's nice yes so you can say
whatever you want in it i've never
yeah but i didn't mean less i
think you're on drugs but also like
i have a brother who i mean
she also i was never bored enough
to go to that but i would
snoop in his
a room so you know when you
know what you knew it makes you
think other people are going to do
this of course did you snoop in
your siblings where oh well man not
me or you shoot me yes join
me i looked at both of you
oh good
we my brother and i had a
pretty contentious relationship that was sort of
built on kind of fucking each other
over in a way ah was the
age difference two and a half years
but it was it was sort of
like he he would break in like
i had to
safe i got a safe one year
i had a safe too and he
figured out how to if you're thinking
i want it but never actually my
password what i'm i remember my safe's
code
yeah oh wow that was even say
i was picturing like the fuckin dial
it was a dial but you um
you you didn't have a code with
it it would just be kind of
lined up on the right part rice
cheatbook piece of shit yeah i had
a combination
huh my daydreams come true i had
a combination um safe that my brother
and i kept like to safe in
what
what a safe and what combination safe
i hit accommodations ah so it's called
safety yeah yeah um not worth it
and i would keep the word out
josh
joshua levy a charge you're only leaving
the high court
i had so many duds last episode
you have to leave that the last
episode right so fatally misunderstood thirty miles
own
um humiliated listening back to the lights
i don't remember we're talking about tmc
i got the last lap so that
everyone just heard but you were talking
with the one that we go oh
god this episode that we just record
yeah tmc i gotta look into this
little bit more anyways anyway so i
kept i kept my valuable stuff in
there mainly
like my most valuable comics and new
porn he figured out how to bend
basically benzie it was it was essentially
my yes
he started on suits
no it was cheap enough that he
figured out if you bent the door
he could figure out how to open
it yeah so i remember one day
i went into my room and like
everything was gone and it was oh
it was yeah he's very upset and
he stole it all in a and
he sold it
ahead and when i went next legit
not nice when i went and complained
about it his excuse was well he
doesn't take care of them he doesn't
deserve them and then did did he
get away with it probably i mean
you know i mean you put them
in the safe i think that's taking
care of it i don't like keys
and really putting them in bags and
boards are terrible but now you take
care
of em ah no i haven't read
this you never learned your lesson
yeah anyway so i mean but but
it was ah it was a pretty
constant like ah
sneaking into each other's rooms yeah yeah
kind of thing i remember sneaking into
my brother's room but not i remember
like really snooping it was more like
if he had stuff that i wanted
to play with their head like comic
books that i wanted to read and
stuff like that but i don't i
don't remember like like rifling through drawers
or anything like oh i definitely did
my brother put it
note and that was like get out
of my drawer awesome where we wouldn't
worry anything notes i mean i would
find you just want to know about
him or do you want to just
go snoop i mean you know it's
just very snoopy but i found sorts
of like you want to know what
people are hiding in they want to
know what's going on in here right
now
i want to know what is going
on i know what is my eyeliner
to know you know i found some
interesting stuff so it's like once you
find one thing that's interesting then you're
like well i'm not gonna stop here
you know like you know ah high
times magazine yeah i ty magazine
so anything like that i like i
found like a letter that his this
girl that he was like dating wrote
to him a lot and then i
read that and do that high times
magazine's injury
you better keep this letter ended in
the same way that's like juicy stuff
you know when you're like a little
sister i remember i found in my
in my brother's room i found ah
a thing of k chili oh my
god thats sick and that's the thing
you don't want to be thinking i
mean what's different for boys well so
so so i loved me thinking i
think i wouldn't have brothers have exist
served by that i mean i think
that's all i was i think i
was twelve and i told my friend
or classmates that i found this in
there like well would bring it to
school so then i brought it to
school so i brought it to school
and showed what everyone i've read around
and they
they were like
huh
it was so anticlimactic it was like
i don't know what i expected yeah
it was a tube of stuff yeah
that's exciting it's like why did you
know it's god i'm sorry i should
not have pushed you to do this
ah barkat up ladies spark it up
like ladies bark it up it up
ladies
barking oh mah got up ladies bar
huh
um but yeah and then i told
you about his bong in the rye
trying to bang oh yeah i mean
what are kids kids are keeping secrets
of what they're keeping drugs drinks porn
porn those n and i guess letters
or whatever you like notes have you
ever seen euphoria they're blackmailing people got
oh i've watched like half that show
i always think i want to finish
it but it's so intense it's very
intense it's it's tough so it's very
very well done though no i think
but just comatose yeah it's really um
not up like sally sloane like to
watch alone that i'm like well eventually
the right mood to want to watch
like some kid find his dad fucking
the team yeah yeah tell or you
know there's a lot right what
what what is that food really yeah
i'm really it's really like specific like
i just want to i want the
motives i want to watch something good
but i don't know what and i
know that you have this left you
don't eat right yeah yeah that's like
there there was some movie that ah
you you like anything that has to
do with the iraq war or whatever
like i've never seen a hurt locker
acre everyone said it was so good
and i'm like i'm never going to
be in the mood taiwan like too
late like three kings missed it three
kings i saw like like maybe the
the day it came out or something
i saw santa monica um let's hear
that well i don't know san diego
that well but oh i happened to
be shopping mc i don't remember i
i know where it is in santa
monica but i see strange dream ramadan
cool off and i happen to be
yeah it was on thursday sam see
okay i happen to be shopping there
and we were like let's go in
to see this movie i've never been
to that theater ever censor or previous
there was some movie some drama that
was based on a play i think
about it was nicole kidman and maybe
aaron eckhart or somebody and it was
about them
losing a child and i'm like low
when am i ever gonna yeah no
that's never i'm never gonna watch that
i know some things are just too
depressing yeah it's like you know going
in this is going to be a
bummer
so say like sad yea but it
depends what it is this is a
top as the greeks called it ah
catharsis oh yeah you go to college
and fuck every class
ah yeah ah
flunked art history twice took it the
second time thinking okay this time i'll
actually go to class not flunking but
that's literally my meget all the way
my stress nightmare that i don't go
to school like i mean like how
could you handle not going because i
would rather i was way more into
drama and so i my schedule i'm
sure i've talked about this yeah college
schedule as per
punishing know my college schedule i first
of all i was i was coming
out of high school where i was
in all like honors classes and and
so i always asked for more credits
than they have been you're allowed to
you have to get permission first over
whatever did your step overload my schedule
because i was like let me get
out of here in less time and
then i i
but my schedule was always ah my
first class was in at noon no
no my first class was at eight
and i would go eight to noon
and then i'd come home and watch
days of our lives
and then i would take a nap
and then i was
because that dates yeah he's either looks
like a lot oh yeah well you'll
see why because then i would go
to acting class at like four and
then i would be in productions that
started started rehearsals at seven and those
would go seven to eleven or seven
to ten or i don't remember and
then me and my friends would go
into my friends ah my friend frank's
van from eld
seven till five in the morning and
drink beer all night and talk wow
she is not recorded podcast which is
what i shaved yeah and then i
would i would roll into bed at
six am sleep for two hours and
get up at eight for for my
first class really awful it was so
fun that sounds fun i mean
now as for the classes yeah my
classes were terrible and i was only
going to class because i wanted to
be in drama and because my parents
said if you don't take classes and
get a c average you will have
to pay rent while you are here
oh hell no i was like hail
ma you know my landlord i will
never pay re
so i ended up having to pay
rent my general watch days of our
lives and ticket
but yeah so it was it was
two year i was i was in
junior college for two years and flints
almost every class to a point where
they were like okay you have to
pay rent now and that's not fair
you know what you beat me down
i will say that rent that's when
restaurant roundup started ah
before that i just had random jobs
like working in the warehouse and ah
not the not the music store but
ah and a literal warehouse where i
moved stuff for a living but that
sounds weird and disneyland oh i have
a question yes where do you think
all the stuff at amoeba records went
well they have a new store oh
they do go to new
store yeah oh that's less sad than
it seemed yeah they they it's it's
a little bit it seems yeah it's
a little smaller but it's across the
street from ah so it is sad
like everyone was a jew i mean
i think it is sad that they
shut down the main location which was
so historic but yeah so now it's
just some regular little store no it's
not little it's
still is big but it's across from
shake shack that must have been a
pain in the ass to move all
that shit oh and the check check
in the in in like glendale or
what i know now the shake shack
over here on ah oh they just
opened that on sunset right there looking
for the ways wherein said yes location
is not historic what i'm gonna get
that only home that sounds good then
that location used to be a party
yeah for the cinerama dome that we
we used to remember anytime we would
go to them why was everyone so
fucking sad about it because it's a
cool building and that's how music people
get that sounds like a little too
much remember anytime we would go to
the center radome we would try to
park there without paying the what was
it three dollars think so yeah because
i was we were all
oh yeah and it was like and
they had it it was a giant
parking lot honestly when you're broke like
that kind of thing is the worst
thing to spend money on like it's
so annoying thing yeah yeah you'd rather
buy popcorn or something like homeless pets
away it was a parking lot tow
wet and then they built that one
i remember when it was built i
can't remember what year but it was
it's not that old but the ninety
s two thousand
two because the first amoeba was where
in in san francisco and yeah that
sounds i think that's right and that's
probably more historic but yeah there are
tower records locations that are way more
historic amoeba i mean it just doesn't
exist anymore does it in japan there's
like one but they they really they
bought the rights to it go watch
colin x's documentary
i want to go to japan i
want to go to japan with you
while my guy and kula what's her
name cool up and go together here
yeah yeah that's your trip to japan
read em trip to japan sorry no
spouses allowed i wish it could be
different it would be the best time
japan's the most fun
dates over i would love to go
like it's fun i would love it
so much that was a place that
i wasn't that interested in going until
i would say like probably over the
last ten years i started thinking about
it more and more i never wanted
to go and yeah it never crossed
my mind i was like i think
i want to do and when mike
and i first started dating that was
like he was like we should go
on a trip somewhere we both have
never been and that's why we
chose that do you know when i
realised it was it was that i
think i had it in the back
of my mind it was the fear
of going some place where i couldn't
speak the language yeah and then it
easy for either yeah that's what i've
heard and then but then after i
went to ah france ah that i
realised oh it's not the end of
the world like yeah you can get
plenty of people here don't know what's
going
ing on yeah la sect also within
proposed to make sure it's with that
by the way yeah okay well do
la la six yeah see even out
of context it's funny it's funny and
it should be a pillow too it
should absolutely be a billow yeah but
first the three-day m gibbins so you
turn it over it's like you don't
realize you're mitchell
yeah yeah manjhi a poor wally we
have the jimmy cheesy scott oh yes
getting josh about those giblets huh josh
where um ah jim it's um they
make a really easy in japan especially
i thought it was even easier than
france because in france you like you
know
you pretty much like you have the
translation app and you can like look
up stuff on menus and and the
waiters will usually work with you and
all like as if they're not snooty
at all when we have written french
food so i know of course yeah
for guys
but
for eisenberg i like giotto or the
fine fine and fluffy is um but
with the paul pie but in tokyo
especially like the subway system they and
i was saying god it would be
so how great would it be if
the subway system here in america we're
as inclusive as it is there where
it's like they're trying to make sure
that english tourists are very well taken
care of and like they they shove
them in the subway with a stick
they well we never went during during
those times which just seems crazy to
me it's yeah yard bar if you
if the listeners haven't don't know what
we're talking about during rush hour there's
videos yeah there's
audio's it's amazing crazy like so many
people are taking the subways that they
literally have they hire people to push
them into the subway to smash them
in we have to assume they're doing
that with covert around now so they
might not be the stick people are
out of work oh that's the big
tragedy with covert maybe they're keeping people
a par with the stick yeah
the amount of work they had to
learn a new skill
alright we have to take a break
we'll be right back
alright we're back and it's time for
three shirt and we're gonna try to
get this one right this is a
rare three-tier correction we we did this
one terribly the first time we didn't
know this this was submitted by matilda
g and um one person thinks of
a criteria or theme
or category of things that their guests
can bring to the picnic okay examples
are things that are blue things that
start with a round-shaped things etc then
the guests start asking if they can
bring specific things to the picnic if
one guest asks to bring something that
fits the criteria the organizer lets them
know that they can come to the
picnic if the thing
it does not fit the criteria they
can't come as the game goes on
the guests must try to guess what
the criteria is so wait how are
we doing iran so we were just
saying we like basically only which only
two people would be guessing and and
the the person who knew what the
thing was would just say no no
no
the person who knows what the thing
is has to add a thing as
well so basically if it was everything
that's red and you were naming like
a banana i'd be like no and
then you know what you can bring
this yeah no but you can bring
ah that's what we were doing wrong
because yeah we were just saying no
yeah yeah no yeah and yours was
so specific yeah i know
you already made you feel bad i
saw my age alright who wants to
think of when i think of the
thing okay um ok i got it
alright can i bring an abacus no
but but but you can bring for
good
yeah let's do it the right way
for you to go and then i
was gonna do it we could do
that and go show every other person
so that it's a little strung out
a little bit can i bring ah
potato chips yes you can oh um
and then i should add something to
well maybe oh maybe then yeah only
let's see you let's get
what you nose to nose to nose
in a row not just to nose
okay yeah okay can i bring ah
parsley
no
can i bring pretzels yes
okay can i bring um
reese's pieces
yeah
you got me to add one good
no no no no run a role
here i have yeah um
can i bring ah red vines no
no okay can i bring
deli meat that's put into a bag
no
i was trying to figure out the
bags things in bags
okay so that's chosen a row okay
so um i'm going to bring um
i'm going to bring ah some leaves
leaves like often trees yeah and in
the auto so potato chips press oh
k pieces yeah okay lee can i
bring a teddy bear no weight without
fuss
like thank him drown thing just browsing
though those are all time president the
chips are brown if they're old enough
yeah bring really off your arm of
your kid
potato chips pretzels reese's pieces reese's pieces
excuse me i hate hills
dare you thank you zet your giana
what is yeah gigi please pcs they
are pieces of reeses the word peace
is spelled normal
it shouldn't be no one is talking
about the spelling just come on talking
about the pronunciation
um i'm trying to say throughline oh
what about
a nestle's crunch bar yep
i think i know
i think i know you think you
know i think it's things that are
crunchy yeah day yay
right now we're doing okay oh no
who wants to go next i will
go next to prove that i've really
paid attention okay
i got it um no i don't
tell those again
um okay and yes okay i'm going
to a picnic and i would like
to bring an umbrella who's picking are
you going to yours yeah that's right
oh sorry um an umbrella maybe maybe
depends if it's open or not or
closed
instead if it's poked out it oh
depends on what color what are you
going to bring i'm gonna bring your
teddy picker
you fuckin pussy so surely
i mix it just
ah no fall so maybe it's not
the color okay because teddy bears can
be as you know like it is
purple if it's a beanie baby and
you said it was brown you had
had to be brown is brown anywhere
okay that i'm gonna bring um i
remember the earlier example for something brown
was
a teddy bear and wouldn't bring a
blanket
maybe i'm gonna bring a red rose
now
i'm going to bring a plaid suit
ah no that's what yeah yeah yeah
yeah you gotta go some one of
the things that i'm bringing and i
would appreciate if people could get on
board
ah i'm gonna be bringing a guacamole
a i'm gonna bring kermit the frog
okay i'm gonna bring um boogers
i'm going to bring slimer aka onion
head okay when you both can come
to my picnic things that agree yeah
hey we're playing the game right it's
easier and it's not good
ah ok makes the category harder okay
okay okay
i am i got it i am
going to a picnic do you guys
want to come and if so what
are you going to bring who's picnic
is this
i miss my friends but okay you're
sure we're allowed to go
oh come oh clear with it okay
alright i'm going to bring um you
know garden hose
no you can't do that oh so
we're building a diary no why would
you bring your diary you silly but
i will tell you i'm gonna bring
a plate okay i'm going to bring
forks now you can't do that i'm
going to bring a drawing of the
sun no
but i'm probably gonna bring some fish
bait
the fuck
alright i'm gonna bring ah
if
batteries
no sorry you can't come if you
bring batteries i'm going to bring
ah
oh ah a dog food bowl
no sorry
but this is a plus one situation
so i'm probably going to bring my
mate your mate sure get it okay
ah i'm gonna bring a figure eight
yes please come i'm gonna bring ah
ice skate sure just one alright
yes things that rhyme with eight yeah
hey
we're not dumb are you happy we
play the game the right way and
this is what happened here awesome
alright it's getting looks sleek cream after
dark it's it's getting very cold we
gotta go we're gonna go coke and
coca cola hellfire oh yeah ghostwriter yes
but thank you so much for listening
remember to listen
oh my god why honestly though you
say tip your waiter today saying remember
to listen thank you know to listen
again you can you aren't subscribe and
listen every thursday and you know don't
be like gail simone who didn't even
know about this show for years tell
your friends about it yeah tell your
friends if your friends
with gail simone teller rebel automatic because
she forgets every week at gail simone
on twitter tweeter and say gail i
have a podcast you would love that
you're already listening to it's called freedom
gail simone she's a great comic writer
and a wonderful person with this she
is a fan of the show but
she only goes out about a month
ago okay everything i just said
nope we got if we're keeping paul
thing and we're keeping that in and
then take my now take no
alright we'll see you next time okay
bye-bye
a