it's freedom
ah i'm a winner three now
yeah i stay winning freedom
oh i know and they went after
wow another one are nuts how does
it feel to be a winner it
feels good i get it now okay
is this the first thing you've ever
watched he sure is got and you
made by the wheels i made up
the rules yeah that helps yeah by
the way yes or by the way
no you are scott yes i
i'm scott and you are it's in
the dark recesses of my mind why
isn't the dark recesses so shine a
light in there she's not not on
the edge of my mind with the
tip of my tongue the dark recesses
of my branch of my mind really
far in there it's in my mind's
eye by alan dean foster yes the
splinter of which
ah paul you are paul correct and
look who's here look across the table
my name is lauren q public
what was the spell what was the
temptation
q public rabbah rabbah
oh my god welcome to another episode
of three oh yeah the show where
we talk yeah let's right and you
listen yeah or don't well you could
also talk during when we're talking but
it feels like it'd be annoying yeah
we're not gonna hear it no but
to the whoever they're talking to yeah
or if they're just talking to themselves
oh they're talking back to
us yeah you can do that right
sure oh i just assumed he meant
talk at the same time sure i
mean it would be hard to get
a word in edgewise we barely row
actually i learned a couple episodes back
and i was like i'm gonna interrupt
less than i was like that's going
to be impossible
i think we all do it sorry
yeah i could try but yeah we
all feel that way like the hour
before the show starts as long ago
today i'm not going to interrupt yeah
i don't feel like he's to get
interrupted yeah i like to be a
little more surgical with my interactions
oh and not just sees on the
one thing can pay for your two
words i bring to the table oh
yes what do you do new business
you have a table bring there's just
say lawrence topic so it's not lawrence
topics it's not about a baby you
know this this is a table bring
in anyone can call a table bring
at any time okay let me see
if i can find the original inspiration
okay so i
i posted a click whole instagram post
congratulations yeah and i put it in
my story yeah great um and it
said this is what you should call
him now mcdonald's has announced it has
changed ronald mcdonald's name to intensity that
was really funny very funny so i
posted that i received i mean it
was just a few messages but a
few messages from people who thought it
was real and they were like what
what is going on and i was
like oh click hole is the onion
it's owned by the onion and like
what i didn't know that i i
didn't realize they were moving into that
space i go what like movies that
yeah hey mcdonald's okay thanks and then
i'm like sir you
see are you holding me off yeah
just casually as i'm linking up right
at me i just resting bitch thinks
yes or yes
i'm looking back at some other posts
and i'm like
you thought that was real like this
is a picture of patrick mahomes and
it says the quote is you gotta
wonder how many worms are under this
thing patrick mahomes and his first thought
when stepping onto a football field and
then didn't really say that like you
know cleavable than the other posts were
news i mean i don't know six
times in the child's payment lease would
instead of murdering someone chucky just brutally
mocked their car over ah the leisure
innovation child snowman has entirely of piss
snow
early via i ordered a sweatshirt from
them yeah ah which said it was
a christmas like holiday holiday ugly sweater
type sweatshirt and it said i just
saw all of you at thanksgiving right
and i thought that was very funny
so i i ordered it and they
sent me one that said merry christmas
scott ackerman on it oh well
it was a mistake a little sketch
those mistake oh there's a we want
to wish me that did you get
your money back yeah yeah good i
demanded it i sued them a seagrass
court this was a private purchase so
here's what happens they do that for
everyone who buys anything from really yes
they also send you a personalized basically
just sell the personal premiums they might
those would be more popular like the
surprise element but it was very nice
i did a costume change in the
middle of ah christmas in front of
everyone yes i know era's tool strip
down to my underwear put on my
same pants but i just joined your
you turn your backdoor yeah like
okay so look look look look at
this i'm not going to you you're
all gonna be um i also inadvertently
fooled people with an instagram post where
i had um bloody makeup on my
face those will get people they really
do and i thought because i was
i was shooting something and in this
one scene i get beat up and
i thought this would be
funny it's pretty obvious i read the
new romine film right now the makeup
is well done but i'm saying yeah
my assumption is typically i wouldn't real
why would i enjoy posting why blood
come yes yes yes so wouldn't you
get medical attention yeah like it's just
crazy yeah yeah so i had to
reassure people all day because
people were texted me saying oh my
god are you okay i like to
think that they thought it was after
one of these episodes we just beat
the shit out of you why do
you like to think i like it
why because i have a twisted mind
i like to think that too that
came right from the twisted mind of
scott ackerman that's right i borrowed mine
from danny devito
which was original twisted mind i think
he was i can't think of a
twisted mind before john krasinski has gotten
twisted oh i guess he has an
imagination now oh yes meditation well movies
from the imagination of john chris oh
the way he imagines the same thing
over and over
maybe a little boy came from one
idea visible friend and even quieter imaginary
friend i mean oh oh oh i
see a different film franchise i have
to say drop dead fred right that
ties into the premise of the film
in the which is probably why they're
saying it they have quite persistent imaginary
for oh noise somebody medication i certainly
did
understand oh no but you were you
were hyping it up to us like
it was well you want to call
it from the friend everyone will make
step mind of missile and basil leaf
frank wyler makes it filed one of
my favorite references i you know is
a classic yeah i don't know if
ever read it whereas all i remember
about that children's book is
the after but it was ah it
was ah it was a chat brother
and sister chapter book brothers sister and
they hid out in the museum oh
and i did read that and they
would collect dinosaur bones what's right the
dinosaur bones they would ride the dinosaur
but yeah that's all the way until
they broke into the house or came
back alive um and they
would collect the coins from the fountain
to buy food at the auto mat
i you know all i remember read
that because out of all familiar to
me they should come back they should
come back what about bridge to terrible
never read it don't like bridge books
okay yeah i don't like tear bithumb
books what's on a bridge book bridge
on the river why
todd bridges autobiography
does the apple i-pad he does i'm
sure now what point is it anyway
master chief vs a memoir that's a
good question i don't i e autobiography
feels very text but memoir feels like
i'd like to write an autobiography biography
but i'm not famous you're gonna say
biography memoir feels like
funny i centered an autobiographical book memoir
feels more like it's my autobiography but
i'm taking some creative liberties
i feel like memoirs may be not
about your entire life like it's not
a chronological journey of here's my here's
my whole story is sort of like
i'm famous and here's my remembrances it's
all i'll tell you what wikipedia has
please it is any nonfiction narrative writing
ng based on the author's personal memories
the assertions made in the work are
thus understood to be factual that's a
memoir or autobiography that's a mnemonic
memoir why didn't you look at dictionary
dot com
can't you let me look at dictionary
dot com on wikipedia okay yeah please
yeah so what did they do that
what is shared dot com is an
online dictionary whose domain was first registered
on may fourteen nineteen ninety five does
oh my gosh your question anniversary is
coming up because he's crazy like pedia
has chronicled everything
i only know that everyone remember to
message dictionary dot com yes on may
fourteenth and say congrats guys can you
look up morality sancho panza kinda look
up milk yeah i'm just curious how
indepth it goes
well i'll tell you one thing gibbs
straight controversy milk is a white liquid
food oh what
good good
i didn't say this it didn't say
that it does say that it's a
white liquid food in food you can
click on wouldn't you start with drink
and that's food you can click on
milk's news like the mammary glands of
mammals
to call the mammals because of memory
or yeah most i think it's just
happening to the mammary glands because they
are mammals what the opposite of what
you said the exact youth thing a
thing you said too they call them
mammals because of memory glands like the
mammary glands renamed for like they're the
star
not the unit as a whole i
meant either but you said it
yeah
memoir is an historical account or biography
written from personal knowledge and account written
by a public figure of their life
and experiences the proceedings of a learned
society like memoirs of the royal so
you've got to write a memoir of
put one oh i fly to use
a book
amazing i want really hot i'm like
so high i was a little warm
usually i had that well i had
the heat on because it was freezing
and that's why the door open i'm
so sorry do i do turn on
something else yeah yeah oh would you
turn on your heart light maybe that'll
yeah the things down open a window
or something you open a window can
we add these able to be guessed
was
they're able to be open okay i'll
open it i'm autobiography and account of
a person's life written by that person
so they're the same thing the same
ass thing yeah although for some reason
memoir gets more detail but that that
this is what i mean though is
like i feel like if you're a
non famous person like ah i don't
know who wrote ever everlasting job stopper
i'll do it
learn you pick up the slack tuck
everlasting do what nobody nobody oh okay
what do you think i'm an idiot
it was such a crack well i
didn't want to get us all freezing
burr i didn't know what would happen
if i just i'll start with a
crack you know sure you start with
crack and then opening up the window
even more
pack them in heroin and then you
just see what happens crack it could
be a gateway drug i suppose since
you start with why not go higher
and crack yeah
i would just smoke crack socially and
then before i knew it i was
doing it alone
constantly though either way is it fun
do you think crack i e like
we've all said we didn't like the
idea of coke and everyone was like
years square so i guess we have
to say crack is cool it's very
cool yeah it's a big deal that
crack were smoking in high school
where does it where were the most
square podcast hosts around yeah that can't
be true we have i mean we
haven't turned out okay i can't remember
what i haven't done i have not
done coke okay none of us have
done coke no desire we only smoke
so but it's like everyone i knew
well no i don't wanna get back
into the coke
conversation because i do have friends who
are cool who don't coke but the
slight wear sunglasses people like first think
of are the worst one thousand percent
of that's kind of the message caucus
sending exact is i'm a douchebag yes
but cool people have been known to
drive of course so what am i
going
so john wayne gacy
the clown kids that's not fair i
don't know if he's ever done coke
yeah don't ever disparage him i apologize
don't drag his name through the mud
my friend patrick bateman used to do
it a lot but and that you
know i have his business card do
you not like really watch that movie
that was a fun movie oh so
fun you know what i didn't like
it at the time and i wonder
if i would like it more now
i just
love christian bale i don't do you
really like him because of your batman
experience um because ah jist of life
may i introduce you to the prestige
what's that oh is it the third
set it's the third guy that makes
you do a noise um the prestige
is
ah christian bailey i believe is that
the one with hugh jackman huge jacked
man is in this hugh jackman plays
a role he plays a double role
in this noise really avoid it was
old news that i'm happy for him
but you know what i bet that
something i learned felt bad about and
forgot well because he's with his wife
for like ever in a long time
yeah
oh yeah i'm happy for them both
i think sometimes that can be a
great step yeah of course it can
be
um to not living with that person
he wants his the news is that
he wants his estranged wife to sign
an n da o e not suspicious
so not amicable um tricky he plays
a double role in the prestige and
the
one character is so entertaining that i
wished that they'd had it he had
it's own he had his own movie
you should do this but you should
write a spin off like a sitcom
like a young sheldon of my imagination
yes prestigious mind of
tompkins
you've never created a show that's been
on the air just see the advertisements
are out there yeah people are like
barely big show real time i go
along with it
that is what i vote for do
you have that on your arm to
be as you're most known for yeah
and i'm the one who who makes
it that i'm the one who i
am the one who makes it that
i am the one who knocks on
my did he know breaking bad spoilers
why did he knock he didn't knock
he was being figure
native he never knocked no he's out
there's bragging about knocking i think he's
knocked on a door in the show
but nigh in the way that he's
talking about and i actually know that
i'm thinking about i don't think he's
ever knocked on a door there's no
i've always marched in like like fonzie
hell didn't bargain was never just sauntered
in kramer barge dan kramer would barter
yeah and
lemon squidgy famously barged yes oh so
lenny squidgy kramer and then bryan cranston
breaking bad they're all the characters on
tv who just would throw open a
door urkel urkel urkel fable elastic xander
in the in the credits they're trying
to keep him out yeah he has
the strength of ten men
entire families pushing on the door you
know nerds are really struggling yeah yeah
kind of one of their secret thing
they get that nerd um adrenaline to
remember the show beauty and the geek
of course yeah what reality shows did
not last that you wish had lasted
oh wow i was thinking about or
when reality tv came out
in the early two thousands and how
novel it was and i would watch
every single one of them no man
i was just like i was thinking
back on it going like why did
i waste my time on it there
was one where like porn stars were
cast in a shakespeare play and it
followed them but yeah that's a lot
of pho and they all cms
repeated to get like juliet and romeo
and juliet or something magical of course
and it was like a it feels
like it was a ten episode thing
that followed them all the way to
the end of performing this to a
fake audience i'm sure well the swan
was one that was oh the swan
terrible yes but it was fan swann
lynn swann
yeah it's all about him the swan
live
the swan for people who don't know
is a show where people just got
complete head to toe plastic surgery yeah
so special and they were away from
their family for like three months while
they were covered and then they came
back and looked completely different including like
weight loss yeah new teeth and everyone's
different hair oh cool face who are
you yeah it's like i think those
children i would
love to interview some of the children
not i don't want to integrate them
i want to watch him like a
bill cosby interviewing kids kind of show
i think no and they're saying they're
all adults um west in that show
art linkletter tiffany haddish telling me there's
a trait she ready she ready to
do that show she she was
ready and she did do it um
and you can do it and was
it had i knew it was it
hot or not the lorenzo lamas oh
yeah where you at a point during
the pointer laser pointer what's ah so
that's why it or not was a
website or oh the website i remember
yeah okay so knowledge it was very
popular and they made a tv show
out of it where it was three
judges allah
the american idol and lorenzo lamas discussing
human being was one of them and
he would aim a laser pointer at
women in their bikinis and show parts
of their body problem areas so disgusting
yeah that was a one season or
oh yeah that's sickening yes sickening where
a rare instance of network television saying
womb guess we were wrong about how
discussing everyone let's course correct
yeah i guess they must not everyone
would love that yeah let's just like
nobody is perfect so nobody's gonna like
this nobody's perfect i swear probes neural
ladies nervous that i know what he's
perfect of course sure it does seem
like a lot of
a lot of stuff like this culture
is reaction to the previous decade like
i was thinking about gross-out comedies you
know in the nineties and i was
like why was everything all why we're
here though i did
but you know like why why were
those the most popular comedies and then
you go well it's because in the
eighties everything was so like monoculture was
just so like straight norm and especially
like everything on tv was like home
improvement and it's also endless imitations of
the one thing that was successful right
i was just talking on the way
here
ear on the phone to my friend
about three it was hands-free and he
brought up the movie eddie and then
i thought that was the one where
whoopi goldberg had a dinosaur for a
friend and then he looked up in
those theodore rex i was like that
was a period of time where it's
right that could happen yeah when almost
didn't come out or something like that
it was like a
big lawsuit i can't remember touching go
there for a while you don't know
but there were so many things but
we got it at that time were
like an animal or a puppet or
thanks yeah i was forced to be
in it it was originally intended for
theatrical it went direct to video and
consequentially consequently became the most expensive directive
video film ever made monster essential
how much ah the budge is that
what you're asking is wikipedia got thirty
three point five million look it up
on dictionary dot com yeah theodore rex
theater rex is a movie thank you
dictionary dot com um yeah i believe
she had made an oral agreed
amant if you know what i mean
to star in the film excuse and
then attempted to back out and ah
they sued her it was settled and
then she agreed to star in it
i'm sorry if you just said you're
gonna do it and you don't want
to you can't be sued into that's
i would love to hear that conversation
there's so many times that incidents where
someone says
and they do if somebody agrees to
something in there backing away from you
i don't think that should count
yeah she in with the dinosaur and
that's where i care a lot about
a famous dinosaur just one second i
just have to go guess i'll get
my car i see like a celebrity
and she's like his agent or something
i don't know cops i believe oh
what
who is who is the first scenario
i can see the dinosaurs celebrity yeah
and she's getting older i don't know
what the plot
there's sorts of slippery shit about it
i believe they are police officers you're
on your phone what does that actually
scary for your gadgets a battery a
bat two external battery there are you
out all day why do you need
that
not nearly an electrical plug are you
who are you to ask me that
i'm your who doesn't fucker you i'm
your work acquaintance
that's fair um than my my phone
was already half drain ed when i
got here how long have you been
up where it's early in the morning
you know you set your connections until
um we have to say great alright
and we're back let me talk about
connections okay talk about connection this this
this year your final word on the
scheduled date this recording of course but
the other day we had one where
i couldn't get it and i believe
lauren were you stumped as well um
yesterday yeah and
the the thing that really held me
up was and i was very surprised
at the reveal was ah measurements of
water yeah and so yeah but that
was it was like descriptions of type
like yeah it was like bead drop
something like that glob one of them
was glob
i've never heard that in my life
above water i think of glob is
like more viscous like mustard you got
a glob of mustard on my shirt
i glob but is mustard considered a
liquid not by me i think i've
never drunk it well is mustard considered
a liquid maybe with lex wikipedia
mustard as a liquid yellow food um
i feel like blob is short for
globule which means a drop then say
globule it's not like a common like
people aren't going around saying globule they're
not saying a lobbying job of water
on my shirt no one's ever said
that no one has ever said that
little glue
tub of water came out of my
eye yes here it was one of
them too yeah it's like i'll give
you that when that's clever glad to
know i i've been crushing spelling bee
lately i get genius almost every day
i know nobody you don't care maybe
i don't try for queen b o
genius so you never gotten always get
queen bee i'll look at my stats
okay well i i
oh do we i can't do this
right now but i'm not gonna happen
don't do it right now when you
gonna do it i mean tell you
something i only learn you made an
oral agreement only learned about queen bee
like last week i didn't know that
was a thing because they say wow
it goes you get to regulations you're
teasing i'm like oh no you can
go further queen b i didn't and
so i learned that but then i
was like
that's my whole day at that point
we'll know that you've got to use
the assistant what i'll forward you the
drone there's an assistant following the bc
enhance thing the ah it's like a
separate thing that tells you how many
how many words you have left and
all that kind of stuff oh what's
it like
yeah it gives you hints and stuff
like that i got fed up with
spelling bee really yeah first i was
like this is boring it wasn't yeah
it wasn't fun after ten i got
addicted sure and now it's part of
my life track that's like me with
crack where do i think is like
basic bitch i've gone back to wordle
i'd still do it yeah but where
are those basic bitch than
no connections where it's like you really
thinking you're sophisticated and you have sunday
the okay on that all day if
you want to you know kind of
just go in and out more you
can try to get you know like
like the restaurant the bird yeah exactly
that's what we're talking getting hungry i
want fries now oh update i did
not go to foster trees and i
thought that was fucked up yeah we
asked about it
it er lauren did at least yeah
and i read that new didn't even
say a word back because he said
he didn't go and i said wow
did you feel it was like a
sort of two-person memoir yeah i thought
that was between you guys i was
wondering why he was on three and
you are right there are dear reader
because my problem with you not going
here's my ears
our issue with you not gonna bring
so i used said you were going
to you made it an oral agreement
that you were going to get us
to cease i'm suing you for one
fosters free what is whoopi had said
i had my fingers crossed back who
pulls the ended up doing the movie
for two million more than what you'd
agreed to well that sounds like a
good way to work it out absolutely
you got sued and they got more
and undersea
hand at that but if that happened
to me right i would hold a
dinosaur movie for millions of dollars and
yes to make me extra while you
already have and then if they gave
me extra night for millions if they
gave me but it made millions so
congressional that's nice for them um and
they gave me extra money like okay
we understand you you don't really want
to do this we know we're fucking
you over by holding you to a
high
f s promise will give you a
couple extra million dollars i would then
i would act the shit out of
that movie yeah i'd say alright you
make good you know what you got
me yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna do
this better than i do with the
plot of theodore rex i need to
know so i can make references to
it okay dear to share dotcoms ah
look it's one paragraph i'll tell you
that much
in an alternate futuristic society already crazy
where humans and anthropomorphic dinosaurs co-exist so
there's more than one a tough police
detective named katie coltrane is paired with
an anthropomorphic taranto source named theodore rex
to find the killer of we understand
there
super morphey now ram sai swung center
o regular dinosaur t rex being a
diet of being a cop is so
like ineffective like you can't run no
he's just shy the ways a human
side maybe they can run what do
i fuck this is not that different
from zootopia
really starring shakira but there are not
two things utopia was inspired by this
there's a humans in utopia and other
humans but it it is a lot
like that of like oh it's a
weird futuristic society show on where every
everything is anthropomorphic and to like upside
down a phone is to like make
shit out of me
me they should pixar should segue into
everything's a lie i would flying toy
story but everything there's a room there's
one human beings are driven crazy
stop talking shop clothes are talking and
then you see the actual reality of
it which is he's the last man
on earth and he's just before me
there was something didn't do wow he's
super into wally right now oh juristic
story and yeah yeah sad last few
days she's been absurd
obsessed with wally and eve when i
saw wally it was ah the occasion
was janie and i were trying to
get to know our nephew um and
we're like we never spent time with
him let's take him to the movies
we take him to see wally and
where he's sitting in between us and
then when the eve the female
robot shows up the lady robot he
went wow he did a wolf's on
i said that's an appropriate and you
and he's thirty seven yeah and i'm
one hundred and twelve
so she had a sort of ray
gun a laser gun or what i'm
really an arm that shot little bolts
and he kept asking me why she
have i gone
and i and so i as of
the second amendment yes and so i
right yes and then i got out
my decker born with these rights now
still talking picture yeah they're still trying
to take our guns away yeah even
those holy focuses on the world and
um so he asked me again and
i tried to like get some i
tried
to get popcorn on him and i
was like because she scared
then he asked me again and i
was like i don't know stop asking
here first and i talk a little
shit you know you don't talk during
a movie yeah he just wanted to
know about the gum hey i know
we spend time together but you don't
all talk during movies and we were
taking him home and there was construction
on a street so we had to
like you know take a different route
and he
kept saying this isn't the way this
isn't the way you're going the wrong
way that's really cute he's scared you're
kidnapping him i guess he seemed more
annoyed like we were well because kid
kids love structure yeah they like to
know i don't give a fuck what
kids like we explained as likely like
and that wasn't good enough forum so
it's like fuck you do
dude okay you know your attitude and
obviously your baggage with your nephew is
jus
you need to tone it down at
least twelve notches rally oh i've never
forgive him um i think he's about
to go to college okay let's call
them up and find out why he
was so pissed about that does he
still remembers it vividly he might you
know sometimes when you have a younger
member you guys went the wrong way
will because like like idiots if he
didn't hang out with you
often it might have it might have
been a core memory
a core memory formed i wish we'd
gotten on instagram yeah oh man what
it had so so many hearts
if you live your life for the
hard stone football i really do one
hundred time one quarter hearted at a
time
one quarter heart so while you're checking
your watch you know what i just
got a little buzz on my wrist
and it's from my friend joe who
i want i wanna say like three
weeks ago left me a nice um
voice memo on my phone ah that
was just saying hey i'm talked to
in awhile and i was just thinking
about you i just wanted to say
hi nice
and ah and i was like that's
really nice and then i completely spaced
on getting back to him oh now
he's left me another voice mellow like
hey bitch hey melina shit nice thing
now she is yeah this is joe
namath right how long how often are
you i saw him one set of
ah netflix i was there forbid hopefully
i was there afraid of the terrible
embarrassing pitch
i didn't know that at the time
of course of course you felt passionate
about it and he was in the
waiting room as well he had his
own show to pitch real i don't
know whatever happened but neither of our
shows can be interesting but it was
she'll see him in person his show
was a football
just begun a jennifer po the word
show scrolling magic mark what does she
get there like any questions other networks
already show this stuff and then when
he left he left the football on
the chair ah well or was that
him wait wait what if he did
a body swap with football he's after
he was so embarrassed by his pitch
she's like i'd rather just be a
football that he gets thrown games like
oh this is what it feels like
i'm sorry yeah that's right because you
have to learn a lesson in a
body swap movie yeah just like the
football learned food is good
how to appreciate pigs what your skin
is made of
the football jodie body
well rinse be yeah it was like
i'm so sorry i did this
i'm so sorry my skin is made
of you
oh please it's ok don't do it
it just is well your body is
like that you didn't do it it
was like you didn't do it it
is okay you got you i guess
so
ah huh i was asking how often
do you use the voice memo feature
just said i use it more than
i has no four but not that
often here's a period where i wouldn't
text people i'd send a video because
i just thought it was funnier yeah
it's funny you're like good morning where
are you
dude i'm mostly use the voice memo
feature when people leave a word out
in a in a text and then
i you want to berate them i
read it back in a thick accent
i was going to store but ran
out of time we can still do
the russian accent right yeah absolutely they
fucking suck
not the people of course they're leaders
they're all guards yes that's who you're
making fun of yes putin yes pu
tang i have some friends to use
it i like it especially for a
long story yes exactly but sometimes the
phone will then like close during it
and then you have to like find
the spot again i'm like they haven't
mastered that
that let it play bitch let him
cook obviously i'm missing to cinnamon phone
because it was let him go let
him continue cladding ca look we're after
him cook to cook just just a
pure word association i'm just saying that
when anyone says let him cook they're
talking about tim cook and what does
that mean to you because he's the
guy who
it's all these great things for apple
right and so are you seeing it
as let tim cook do his thing
like let him take watch tim cook
let tim cook oh i'm mad at
you yeah i'm sorry i figured it
out i hate you
you looked at me but you pointed
at him i'm into swinging around this
way everybody would go
i like that system that's not bad
i hate you look you already had
no twenty-eight both
looking at no one pointing at both
oh level this is where the audience
that over back to us mister
no i say it was relieving intentional
pauses less than it was raining so
hard oh my god so hard i
lie it was great until i have
a sound machine by the way that's
rain sounding and i woke up in
the middle of the night because the
actual rain was louder than the actual
like this were done was i make
the black box i'm all clay i
was like it was like the sow
the machine and then i realised it
was life i have this window in
my room that is why okay
my room's up to code i have
one it when it's pouring that hard
now there will be a drop go
to duped within the window frame oh
fuck don't know don't try to legitimize
oh we're using it now but every
episode sleep and only started having a
dream with that sound because it sounds
like tap
tap tap and i was like it
was like a morse code situation my
dream knows who's we were trying to
decode it it was like really really
deep it was like great dream and
i kind of woke up and i'm
like oh it's the fucking window and
then like when you're aware of that
like i was just laying there going
like oh this is so annoying there's
no way to stop it yeah because
it's within the windows you can't put
like a towel unless i was gonna
open
on the screen and do all this
shit i'm like what you're not gonna
i'm not gonna do that at three
am oh and i just had to
lay there and be annoyed too annoying
the sucks can't i put a pillow
over my head i put my sleep
crown over my head ad
she is a grad great head pillow
what does that again it's a fluffy
little pillow that you can put over
your eyes like an i'm asked her
over your ear okay on your side
and cover your eyes the same time
it's lightweight it's squishy it's being chosen
you can also cuddle it me to
r and um it was handy
but you don't think you're on the
pillsbury dough boy you are the pillsbury
dough goo goo ga you've been undercover
this whole time yeah where where is
he still in person is he still
out doing so yeah he's still out
there i'm glad in these streets we
stay makina we stand the doughy king
he is securing the dough bag
we have a we we just stopped
using these air filters that we just
would have on my seaweed that someone
in my home would have on just
twenty four hours a day there's let
me see who else is in your
home you also let's not important and
then finally you you
finally this person stopped i'm trying to
make the list i have to i
have run out of time finally this
person said asked me to these do
anything and i was like no they
don't let's get rid of the oh
my
oh happy i've always wanted the yeah
that's the white noise sort of gone
well i like white noise doing anything
i like white noise but i prefer
c chi prefers violet
i don't see don de lillo when
terms have been noise i had but
i felt like never i ah i
prefer environmental sounds yeah like an ocean
earth yeah like that or that oh
yeah yeah
kolkata shh go go oh she's oh
radhe oh good so um we so
the first night without them they were
in your bedroom or your house in
general or what they were in every
room in the house except the bathrooms
and they didn't do anything
i don't think they made any defense
for a while yet mother person who
lives in my house has more environmental
issues than i do i see i
don't really have allergies like you don't
believe in global warming is what you're
saying it's just made up if global
warming how can we have winter why
is it so cold here in l
a as couple of days yeah it
doesn't make any sense does it exactly
yeah why is it sewing
in places it's never seen before it's
getting a bit weird it took everyone
so long to come up with climate
change but it's like it's too late
to like why don't think of it
in the first place dummies yeah
because but they would have done the
same thing i know the climate changes
every season yeah every day is different
thing that was like i don't remember
what country it was but they did
um a program where if you recycled
your groceries i mean your your trash
recycle my grocery recycle your trash proper
here these are back like you sorted
in the bins like to the two
there
rules yeah you would get like a
star on your garbage from five like
huh
the kid in elementary like ups the
everyone's like a burmese by like a
million percent like everyone was properly because
they're getting stars and i'm like if
i got a star i was ashamed
to not have this yeah yeah i
wanted i want to like have a
competition to recycle i definitely do it
wrong there's so many things you find
out like
years a million years into it they're
like fruit plastic containers you can't see
i'm like oh what the fuck here's
their way to chicken bones one is
really what's that you can put chicken
bones and the recycled
no yeah like now you have to
put them in the green bin because
yes it's so much gas it's like
really like from qingdao yeah yeah the
gas from chicken bones what the fuck
what why okay i'm gonna lie do
we recycle jack and bones some recycling
it's composting yeah
yeah but it's kind of the same
yeah i also saw this article that
was like companies have known forever that
like for thirty years that recycling doesn't
do shit yeah i've had in the
checking and i'm like absolutely and also
in law like they they they don't
they just mix all the plastic exactly
i never believe they're doing anything with
it
this is what's it's hard to care
i used to think that maybe it
was making a difference and then once
i found out it was not really
making a difference i was like this
is bleak and it sucks and now
i will put nothing makes a difference
i will put the envelope with the
little plastic window in the recycling because
i don't fuckin yeah what am i
supposed to do yeah well i put
the regions today we can't we you
we can't they're they're impossible to recycle
the fans a little window yeah
why did i bump i'm holding paper
and plastic in here and maybe fish
enjoy the window
when they get their heads wrapped in
leash and jelly the window you know
like what do they wanna just be
in an envelope without a window i
wouldn't we have a fucking machine yes
the whole separates yeah why wouldn't we
have a machine why go on but
so what were you gonna say you
got rid of the filters first night
wow your unfiltered and yeah i'm on
filter keeping are you triggered much and
watch my netflix special um so the
first night we did one of my
personal favorite rain tracks listen to that
on repeat and you both agree on
this yes because i think that's your
sample it for a little while and
say oh what do you think of
this no this is what i used
for awhile is it let me put
this on
mike would love to have music on
board they don't i don't use it
i don't like to phone no no
no no you can't do that you'd
have to be a continual song because
the fading out and the silence in
between and then suddenly a song starts
i would wake me up all the
time yeah well that we have sonos
amici okay i'm getting out of my
you are so then the next time
lost then the next night i tried
a different race
soundtrack which was heavy focus the first
one medium solid i'm solid rain the
next one just heavy rain not solid
not solid because it got louder as
it went on that was a mistake
mistake number three the next night it
seemed like i had lost my privileges
to pick out the song even though
we identify
the problem was but now this person
in your person said can not be
rain whoa they were like zeros every
sale sleep well there's ocean we tried
ocean but we tried that i like
ocean to you have the danger of
birds though but see i don't if
that's too many birds in the shared
a hotel are you putting
radon yeah because i don't even think
of that and then i'm like oh
i think i would like that it's
good yeah it's good also the album
that i have is on spotify i
don't know but here's is similar to
that is it a cd we had
its shade dear um yeah rom we
had yeah rum we have sonos speakers
yeah
congratulations thank you oh they work almost
all the time okay and so we
tried there's like built-in channels on sonos
that you can use but this rain
track this ocean track was so short
it was something like thirty seconds come
although it kept fading in fading out
like this fucking sucks who would ever
want that no one drained
idiot i have lower fixed sound machine
by the way it's compact i'd i'd
take it to hotels what's it called
not interested
saudi man don't i know it yeah
it does rain i don't like the
sound from sound machines what do you
mean it does rain i felt like
it sounds to rcu and timmy yeah
oh it sounds perfect has to hear
it anyway come sleep with us tonight
so she's okay well i'm scared okay
i did see it i had a
nightmare last night so i do need
to sleep
you came here in your pajamas and
yeah hugged my mom and dad are
dead so i need sleeps in paris
right so um parents you so this
so this person in my house said
hey what about that didn't feel like
a boat sounds through ah huh and
i did i knew have an album
that is called pirate ship
ip on beyond pirate ship so you
hear like a vast and a hoy
and only knows i'm not sure oh
no most places essentially what it is
like a huge ship like an old
would just sort of creaking badly yeah
now either back and forth it's great
like or you hear the whir of
the boat ship oh scary
like
loser how did we originally learn in
the same way how do we know
that dinosaurs you know didn't have feathers
or did how do we know what
pirates are like and what they're talking
like what they're acting like on the
boat like we have such pirate lore
and filling invented voice memos okay so
there they were recording things i think
probably it was like pirates as power
that's where the that era of pirates
was dying out there like please don't
people just sounded like i think they
were messy bitches please tell the bison
are about
it's a peculiar dialect to say our
all the time it is it really
is you know i bet a lot
of it is preserved because of sea
shanties like yoho and shit like that
yeah there yoho is like the primary
source for all pirate lol that's like
step one yeah yoho said stone if
you will and we have to go
go do
and we're back and it's time for
guys time for three time for three-term
it's time for three years three years
again we'd like to play three trees
put it on and you say hey
i like that game that you say
we're doing i want to go and
see i'm dewey i want to go
and see larry pick two
an owl yeah well yeah we did
ma while we were waiting for your
ass sorry a o three years of
game that we play if you would
like to send us a three cheer
a little parlor game a car game
something like that senators at three m
usa at gmail dot com car game
we could play in a car we
should do one episode from a car
where we're driving ratio our drama for
fun it was fun a second one
was rough that was i was i
want to go to bed or better
remember yeah um this one's called press
conference we've played it before yeah and
we're gonna play it again right now
going to play it again right now
so ah two of
us are interviewers and one is a
celebrity the interviewers text each other who
the celebrity is and the celebrity tries
to guess who they are from the
questions we're asking it's so simple and
it's so easy and i anyone could
do it if you have expensive phones
that cost at least a thousand dollars
and you have two friends and a
wireless service
so podcast is a podcast only game
who's going to be the celebrity who
cares i think paul because he doesn't
care i'll text you forgot me hoy
open-heart just like a pirate
they did hoist a lot of things
they wasted the jolly roger oh my
god they would hoist i guess people
over the side that's true
it would kill all of them for
sure but you know it's so it's
so tough because you go like oh
yeah you could throw me over the
side whatever i'll swim to shore but
sometimes they're too far away yeah that's
the thing that's where they get ya
joe keel hauling is yeah i used
to know what is it shy look
it up on dexterity they basically in
two lesbians move into together really fast
like bump into each other non sexually
lauren good weapons it is basically being
a ah run you
under the boat like on a row
about the length of the boat oh
right if i'm remembering correctly in a
row it happened donna rovers yeah otherwise
you'd get away yeah like fuck is
like schools i'm like ha lucky looks
all by whale
asterisk gets swallowed by whale that asterisk
alright ready for this i texted you
did you get it okay alright here
we go and go thank you all
for being here i don't normally give
press conferences or maybe i do but
here i am and i hope you
will because i mean this is a
really important thing for the city jose
now i'll take your questions okay just
crying that wasn't a question that was
an interjection yeah here's hole you're not
supposed to do anything okay so i
say no i'll take your question
hey
look i know you're different from us
but come on yeah i am we
still respect you as part of our
society thankyou way things have gone we
live in a society i joe
what nevermind do you feel like you
don't understand him excuse me i know
that is a george costanza excuse me
do you feel like your coworkers are
doing all they can to keep us
safe i think they're trying their best
and i think that what about you
are you trying your bags we establish
if this is real or fictional it
doesn't
who cares what i care if a
person like that you're being it can
be any yeah or do you mean
the game
ah why is everything in the room
talking to me my life
well i'm just do you really want
to know if i'm real or fictional
yeah i really do
i don't think we should tell him
fucking hell am i theodore rex yeah
of course you fuckin asshole
so you mean to tell you
yeah
i knew you're gonna pull some shit
alright who was either that or enjoy
pay huh
the theodore eczema review enjoy anyways would
be joy yeah i didn't know there
were two choices alright who's the celebrity
now oh you get to pick
oh god i'll be this lawrence let's
god is the one who says lauren
is the celebrity okay lauren's a celebrity
and paul do you text on things
too okay
and lauren you and i can talk
while this is happening okay so but
filling in the blank sort of thing
well he already texted me okay okay
ready here we go
ah huh
hello hello i'm getting off your phone
press conference why did you cause you're
if you're just gonna be on your
phone i didn't realize you all had
arrived i'm ready well maybe i would
look over your head phone phone for
one second you fucking assholes is there
something i can help you we didn't
come here to be called fucking asshole
and you somewhere for for this
press conference i want to just make
a little statement so it is wednesday
and i do want everyone to know
that this day forward from now on
will be called humpday does anyone have
any questions yes yeah yeah i have
a question did you want to say
yours first or should we say yeah
will you answer my friend's question sure
is humpday because of you know
those things that
new here you know you and your
i'll let you finish your sentence you
know is it because it's it's because
of those things on your you and
the rest of you and my on
your back my quasimodo what a weird
thing to a strange way i'm asking
yeah we were questions questions know it's
rhetorical and my qua
easy modo those things my back if
you're quasimodo do not breathe so it's
it's it's hum day because of the
things that my back um if you
pick my hump does a glob not
come out
ah that's so gross guys why do
you need yes why
you're not dr pimple popper but be
a great thing good because
press coverage what do you need you
need what is it do you have
trouble buying clothes
um because i'm shaped like king koopa
because i am king koopa yeah you're
a lot like king koopa shooters to
me i have trouble buying clothes because
no you know i have my must
have special cameras for you i have
the maid i have a have a
tailor and does that come with taxpayers'
expense from time to time when i
have an event about your uniform my
uniform is i have four thousand copies
of this and it's a lot it's
too many is that it's experiencing everything
for you guys bought that last year
that was about four million jesus christ
i would rather that you're not on
the force if if we're gonna have
to pay for all okay so i'm
i'm a cop
you tell us okay i'm a cop
how do you feel about your partner
being so reluctant to work with them
theater
ah
scott europe europe or texts me that
celebrity please i think you text i
just texted you i know but she'll
also she texted me i never get
to text anyone oh i like texting
one of my data plan i'm out
can you imagine having a data plan
in this day and age to remember
when long distance phone calls were a
huge d oh my god my parents
would if if you just lived like
three towns away sometimes you would not
be able to talk to your friends
three towns away
question question karzai says
i have anything a podium yet flash
flash flash flash crash the question i'm
flashing yeah yeah yeah yeah alright alright
alright it's time for leica bag like
press conferences we ah la oh let's
do one okay how does it feel
if you i mean honestly feels amoy
amazing great thank you so much next
question you seem to have switched careers
it was just a conscious decision it
wasn't an unconscious decision i i i
was awake when i decided to do
this and i went for it and
yeah i mean i think it's working
out how well what do you guys
think don't ask us do you feel
that your
your friends on the force are taking
good care of you
okay my theodore rex know am i
whoopi goldberg yeah
oh so yeah let's play so good
thank god you've got that lid closed
yep sport top you wanna play a
regular round yeah okay yeah i'll text
you lauren oh you got to tell
is how's that sound i cherokee okay
ah hey i'm going to ticket to
the movie
shore day
i'm waiting to type a long text
there
it's a long name
it's a clue oh ah
it's not the quick brown fox jumped
over the lazy dog
a lot of questions for that guy
i don't know enough about this person
okay na who wasn't ah use you
ah no he was future the rapper
but i don't really know o nor
do i okay oh okay scott you
sell me your street cred and dumb
it down
ah yes take us out of the
salons of paris
good good sure okay
hello hello hello hello buddy hi stretch
hello shoes what's up what's up what's
up i sell sorry come on oh
can you tie your horse please sure
absolutely sorry about that where's your friend
my friend yeah ah he could not
be here and why is that did
you kill him no i did not
kill him any time up normally your
type kills that type of person but
your friends it's we're friends he's in
space right now he's space i wanna
hear about it that's great what's she
doing
last
that can happen so you're saying we
were it's unusual that we're friends because
normally my type kills that type of
purse yeah well you're wrong i'm wrong
yeah it's not unusual tom jones i'm
tom jones nope
so it isn't tom jones doesn't even
exist who is that well at this
point in time oh okay um so
tell us about this latest adventure i
am riding around on my horse i
am shooting bad guys sure yeah we
hope so i'm becoming a legend okay
yeah what were you wearing on your
chest i'm wearing a star that means
i'm the sheriff yeah oh are you
the sheriff oh that's interesting dead giveaway
of your identity i am the sheriff
do you find it's hard to see
peripherally
um because of my special glasses that's
your glasses under there under my mask
yeah you meant to say underwear and
i would be like oh i made
you say you're meant to say so
so you want conversation to be scripted
no i just it's a class are
you going to tell me my epidermis
show
it is though jolson it's huge yes
we have glasses under that mask sometimes
but not right now for this okay
and you're the sheriff no not really
sure if i'm kind of i work
alone oh you do what about your
friend he works with me sometimes so
using space yes it's spanish look don't
tell anybody
said that okay well there's a lot
of people here we're all reporter yeah
follow up question what that mouth do
well it says things like butch cavendish
i'm gonna tie you up and take
you to the sheriff because i'm not
the sheriff you got in i was
played by armie hammer in a movie
that nobody saw i flew on a
southwest plane next to him on his
way to that job
job readmission on a southwest play while
i was in new mexico i think
there's an easy flight oh okay sure
do you remember ah being in a
car with jay thomas
oh yes i do and the story
is told on david letterman many years
in a row okay ah my name
is lone ranger yeah and goodbye lie
and your friend tonto was in space
yes that is true okay i want
to read about this or see this
adventure somehow you'll find out tonto in
space once tom jones's board you will
know
great about dogfish alright great now it's
lull lauren yeah and paul you're texting
me okay i got to text two
times to one text me
no because this will be my second
time texting no no lauren will text
you about me oh so i'm not
texting i see you know you're texting
no you're texting me right now
about lol i'm texting you about lorin
yes okay that's i was asking okay
and i answered
goddamn i hate you
would you say oh yes heard you
whisper step up to me and say
that
i wish i knew who i was
we'll find out in a second everybody
get off my fucking
um your thumb still work i'm waiting
on that text bro i'm getting slow
i started texting the person that i
classic mistake but yeah
this person will get that text
but they made me
oh you're three texting your friend joe
or sending it to a celebrity on
your show next week okay i got
just my friend joe
alright
hello
oh hi knock knock yeah just for
the masaka becomes this where the fresco
no one not happening in my my
house no kramer i
okay it's happening in my house um
i am just getting more recorded is
it cool to come in come in
come in come in i'm i'm excited
why does is happening in your house
i thought you lived in a castle
yeah this is funny
outside place i i wasn't really planning
to let anyone know i lived here
but this is like an apartment it's
an air bnb oh okay cells under
construction oh yeah i see okay is
it because um your brother is maybe
incurred some damage yeah well um or
maybe that huh
huge ape i am princess peach no
no you're gone that's how do you
wish in your wildest fucking dream somebody's
full of themselves oh and princess page
there's actually interesting you say that your
princess beach when you spend so much
time ah trying to make her life
miserable yeah oh okay this is really
the ah you know it feels very
ah i may have gotten this wrong
about the tacky about you having a
castle that might be your brother it's
true i'm not sure if he's gotten
that wrong
my brother's the one with the castle
oh okay who's that
hi
oh awfully evasive now why i haven't
had my breakfast i'm embarrassed for you
um you've any other questions just why
why do you why do you hate
well he hasn't okay your brother has
a mansion
okay i know you hate that guy
that looks like you so much
guy that looks like me so somewhat
i'm a man shot you tell me
you also have a mansion i guess
i'm a member in your family has
a mansion what's nice is my house
a mansion my brother's a man inherited
wealth is our what about what i
can't be a woman shin yeah well
there were no women in my family
that is true that is true as
far as we know yeah but but
was this all like during world war
two people
will love it all i mean you're
you're from italy right i'm mario no
you're no i'm not you wish sorry
that is disgusting we love mar he
love him it's a him
you're not a him hey i'm not
him i'm easing him no you're no
he's he's not mario
but i am male yeah yeah you're
male and i can prove it that
but we all know that away is
your penis big that no no one
has ever seen that except i'm sure
there's some fan art
um
you know i'm really at a loss
this morning huh yeah why i have
a live press conference in the serbian
p
let's get it can we just go
back to your mansion yeah okay come
here there's ghosts and stuff like that
there right oh
maybe next time passing you're not king
koopa you wish i wish i was
yeah we all do there's go my
mansion
i mean no there's not the guy
that you hate there's ghost in his
mansion
the guy that i hate yeah you
know your your good buddy wario
yeah huh i'm doug huh you're not
doing enough oh my god nerve of
this guy ego who the fuck am
i toad no and you're lugging toad
luigi
you were so close what i think
one of the rear luigi's lanky rival
amboise luigi yea yes i'm glad we
picked something hook weeping or if that
was my fault i enjoyed it i
looked up a lot of facts about
it but i'm glad you did yeah
it was i got it you got
it
i thought i fell off the the
mario train after the initial his initial
appearances the new movies fun i've heard
it's fun but there's a lot i
don't know about the games because i
have not played them yeah i mean
i played the mmo a lot as
a kid but then you know many
advanced time to put away childish things
like yours um
without love i'm like a clanging gong
coding one more one more and you
texted to paul about me
and be be be bold be brave
take no prisoners you know yes okay
hi everybody this is not an air
bnb obviously you're standing at a podium
yet you would have air bnb come
with a podium first question why did
you say that i just wanted everyone
to be comfortable here
ah you know and on the steps
of city hall because you know you
hear about it you never go to
visit really you know but this is
it city hall what's good right i
think at this point in history where
we are right now and you having
the position that you do would your
ancestors be proud of you
my ancestors that's so hard because i
haven't seen them in so long yeah
their ancestors yeah i mean i've ever
seen them i saw my grandma maybe
i was thinking farther back than that
farther back than my grandpa they stay
murders in the city what are you
going to do about it i mean
i'm i'm probably going to
going to investigate it when i do
something like that yeah sound like me
it would be helpful good you get
your whole team on it yeah my
whole team ah yeah i'll get my
team on this yeah who are the
members of my team again like who
who would you like to see on
this investigation the usual gang listen most
people you've hired over the years
what do you say to people say
you might as well be a chicken
for how closely you're related to that
two one two that i may as
well be a chicken yeah to how
closely i'm related to a chicken yeah
you heard me yeah so okay so
looking up related to chicken onion oh
no i'm just saying that a guy
like me theodore rex yeah fitted with
hey all right daddy did a press
conference everybody was again if you'd like
since three-tier write to us at three
m usa gmail dot com and if
you'd like to call us if you
want to leave us a voicemail for
our three
premium episodes that we do every other
week then just go to the website
you know it hag claims eight dot
com and leave us a voicemail i
don't know how that works and i'm
not gonna look it up yeah i
actually went to it last night and
i see how it works it's very
simple you just press the record button
on there yeah but then you have
it sounds too simple yeah need to
talk you have to talk oh yeah
just press arena record your thoughts oh
that's too bad yeah um and ah
if you want to on tuesdays we
put out our old episodes that's called
three visiting on the shoes they're out
from behind the pay wall and they
are fun and every other week we've
put out our three meme episodes that's
at cb world and also apple podcast
premium
and follow us at three dm usa
on instagram's do oh my gosh so
much going on there so much good
stuff we're baking you you ou um
perfect we'll see you next week thanks
so much for listening time hi lauren
really means that
yeah bye