three
just saying a system integrated with some
peppy mice or yellow
i know jimmy yeah but check me
out
ah rah rah sis boom bah dah
we must be must we must increase
our bust la la la la la
la la la la la and ou
de good care yeah good little knight
frame that they hid
i put that on a mix tape
for really i did wild world yeah
and there was something wrong with the
tape and it it recorded it
like once but also another time just
slightly off weirdly enough so and i
always and what do you mean and
the person was like this song's weird
it was like hope you hope you
meet a lot you know what i
mean it was just slightly off for
some reason whatever the tape the tape
recorded is slightly off meaning a recorded
double double
one what it was like with samuel
l shutdown with the other millisecond off
so you will be twice as hot
later so using wild world and i'll
do what oh baby shop
yeah
that's very loose hypnotic i got him
just now getting hypnotized i like chicken
ahmed chicken mama he looks like like
his feathers are flopping but can you
believe it a chicken just walked into
a chicken says blah
hi everyone welcome to three them this
is two hundred and one yes two
hundred one you my name is lord
my name is paul my name is
john why didn't you say it like
me
i wanted you to have your own
thing i wanted it to be a
thing we all did let's start again
my name is lauren my name is
lauren my name is lauren would you
want this is like scott's mix table
over huh
yeah and what did the person the
person said this is weird and they
blamed you yeah they were so mad
at me really probably you still
um no it's cool culotte no
i'm on good terms most keep moist
and he's got i think for the
most career maybe does have secrets why
do you have so many secrets
i can't tell you fuck i know
ironically it's a secret oh alright either
lie detector game show i hope so
um i want to play you on
it it doesn't sound show everyone merely
the character apologize yeah
wait it doesn't sound that familiar we
should do it three and board game
doesn't it seem like it would be
an obvious game show like dexter yeah
i mean there have been lie detectors
and in shows
that's how they're happening google i remember
lie to tell ya familiar to me
lie detector gay moment of truth posted
by hosted by of course what's his
name brian de morris this guy
this oh mark ah carl marky mark
he was named theo blue yeah mark
wahlberg yeah not that markle yeah yeah
right
roadshow markwell wasn't this guy the original
something something host something something well almost
a bachelor and i was like talking
looks like chris harrison no he was
ah antiques roadshow as afro yeah he's
probably hosted other stuff and he was
like you know what i think all
these people are lying i wanna do
my next show i want to be
all about liars you want to hate
a he
people lie and do a lie about
how much the objects are worth i
was supposed to be fraud he he
was the original temptation island guy and
then he came back tuition island as
a contestant
now that's a show where you go
and sit with your partner and see
if you want to fuck somebody oh
yeah nice i guess what if you
even go on it you probably do
let's discuss yeah i didn't do why
would you why else would you go
but all these people going like i'm
doing it just to prove that we
love each other
i mean that's solicitation but they don't
i mean women on the show get
paid to seduce these people yeah hell
yeah and it's always women's interesting man
is that correct no no somebody all
the couples yeah no the male of
the couples know something there's some dementia
awry people on the island who are
trying to attempt you oh it's like
all these couples go and then they
got hooked up with each other yeah
of course no no no no no
they put hot hot people on the
twenty twenty hot men twenty hot women
forgot how it works i like my
idea better i like your idea better
little nasty because then it's like you
have to convince everybody to go along
with it yeah so that it's mutually
sure we're not gonna put any hot
people on this island
like why some couples aren't hot couples
are never a couples come on
if you're coupled up out there you
ugly everyone knows this couples aren't hot
i guess you're right yeah it's too
bad really it's too bad it's just
the way it happens to all of
us something you'll never che had something
carl called the mark walberg show
and it lasted two episodes to two
that's not long to hear him say
karl rove yeah i know guys we
both let him go and because there's
also one of those things i was
like oh he said curled but because
the next word he was gonna see
was mark so i got why he
did it and the l and le
marche edge but i got why he
didn't shush
i just was shocked scott
yeah i get what he was like
it would've been really fun to make
fun of it because yeah because it
was a funny thing it was like
to hear harald somebody carl yes like
that's not a thing you can't according
saying yeah unless you're carl tart and
he can curl whatever you want i
guess but what happens when he corals
something new paul oh fuck just get
turned around on me oh gee
he's gonna respond to some emails if
you guys who are you who you
carlin
good
now reality recap yeah yeah i just
dipped my toe into the new love
is blind season okay and i'm magic
tea yeah and it's not over for
monday it's not new anymore of course
first episodes went about the one thing
that happens your first episode this guy
has a list of questions and so
you know they can't see each other
and either side of this partition like
ah love and is he's like i
have fifteen questions one through fifteen name
and number then i'll read you the
question can answer it and then the
girls will i would honestly pretend i
wasn't there again like seven or whatever
then he reads the question
and one goes so he's like i
don't know the questions like what's one
thing you wish you did differently in
a relationship i don't know and then
these are all like conversation starters yeah
man i've been that but and then
the girls like such and such what
about hugo's well i didn't expect it
to get turned around on me like
how on earth are you going to
write a list of questions nothing they're
going to say and what about you
or eve
even when you're writing the questions think
of your own answer prompt you to
think of your own life i know
it was so a guy who who
is like i don't know where he's
socially adept or whatever yeah yeah but
then he hits it off with one
girl in the first episode and it
seems like his real personality is underneath
there somehow who's more at ease
ease but and then this other time
this calls just answering a question she
goes on and on and he just
leaves the room and she doesn't know
she can't see him he just like
done and he just like lee you
just leaves that was such a funny
power move to me have just like
she's talking and talking he just like
gets but it's not a power do
you know that happened to me i
earl really
this was many years ago at the
aspen comedy festival and i was there
doing driven to drink this one man
show that i had written around the
time and in this show i told
this disgusting story about ah mopping up
a bar table with a rag and
then squeezing the rag into a glass
and
drinking it um because you are so
hungry for alcohol
the phrasing is
because somebody had dared one of us
to do it and then wants the
first person did it then we all
felt like we had to do it
that's not how that works no it's
terrible
um but after the after the shows
of the last night and i met
you know there's some party wrap party
for the whole festival and a ah
a guy came up to me and
ah i forget he worked for something
or other in the business some network
or something and
and he said you know i really
liked your story i really liked your
show and the story was so crazy
and i was trying to tell this
ah now very famous person um about
it and then that famous person was
there and this guy calls him over
and says oh you have to hear
this story and i'm like well it's
his bed
story is better to show x kind
of a full bit and the guy
was like really pressuring me and so
i was like okay ah so i
started to tell the story and then
the soon to be famous guy just
kind of looked away and then walked
away in the middle of it i
love the ny even in the middle
oh really
it's just like i'm dying i don't
think i got that far into it
oh i didn't want to hear this
and and to his credit this guy
didn't want to tell it so why
should i be here wow interestingly like
i was like oh i'm sorry about
that
yahoo bizarre easy but he has to
go be famous you know waiting for
him outside he had a schedule to
keep and it worked because now he's
famous is he someone that i didn't
know yeah he's very famous have i
met him ah probably and couldn't say
for sure but probably i'd love to
pieces together by you telling me
when we're not recording exactly perfect and
i mean this the person was not
i don't even blame it on super
rude and i'm blaming him at all
but it was right saying it was
humiliating if no no no it's not
cool it's not cool yeah walk away
from someone who's talking have you ever
gotten the chance to do it to
this person
no you should put yourself in a
situation far where you fall turn the
tables on them all now we gonna
remember me from thirty years ago it
was want to do i've got to
track down that same guy yeah and
get him yeah to prompt the famous
person to tell a story to tell
us this the same
story you just made jackie he's got
the same story agile
oh really no just reminded me of
this podcast that was like bingeing and
then completely forgot about heavyweights i don't
know what that is here it's where
people have like a problem with someone
from their past and then this guy
the host like goes and like helps
the two people reconnect to like figure
it out or something ooh myself it's
his own personal stuff and some of
it's
other people's she's would you choose early
interesting um
i don't know that i have like
a lingering question about maybe i do
but i don't know i mean i
don't know if i would do it
in that context but it's kind of
a safe context like there's ah there's
like a girl who was kicked out
of her sorority and she never understood
why so then this guy kind of
like why was connected with all these
people she's a bitch
she's a basic bitch but i mean
then like another episode one of the
first episodes is like his the host
uncle and dad don't speak and he
reconnects them wow and then they have
like a meeting and it's on the
podcast and and you hear it yeah
and they're all really interesting because each
every word every word is use
eating and there's one that is um
the the host friend
this is a really good episode he
basically like was friends with moby back
in the day and
back one day nineties one day he
was famous and gave only the cds
that he ended up using as like
wow mixes within porno ma haha yeah
it was our old slave song which
is also really crazy oh my god
and he but then mobi never never
never acknowledge
knowledge that the cds were lent by
that guy he just was like oh
i thought this was a cool music
that i found and i wanna just
lend to tumor credits which he made
music lent to me by well like
even he just wanted to say thank
you and then he would call them
asking for the cds all the time
and maybe just never would reply because
he one of the bad guys want
them back at this point because they're
because they're rare right
and then the host takes that guy
to movies hulu movies house and then
they have a conversation and this whole
thing oh my gods really jesus did
mobi know this was going to have
yes but he did he like he
knew who was coming over and stuff
he just maybe didn't know why he
did but he allowed it and used
to see mobi cleaning
like tending to his deck chairs on
his in his back deck whoa whoa
what i would like sometimes even when
he would hide when i would hide
on his deck
um but anyway really interesting stuff when
i told him i was like bingeing
it like obsessively and then i completely
i just really gotta listen okay back
in why did you call heavyweights heavy
weight like a heavy weight that you're
carrying okay okay
um and yeah because each person's kind
of like ryan why is this thing
like this why does my heart why
does my girl so bad i loved
that album yeah it's still good yeah
i don't remember anything of it at
all
yea we are now go it do
the west side i don't think that
was on that one and you know
what else somebody let somebody says moby
i always think of fatboy slim oh
yeah good well they're kind of noises
saying oh really ooh i gotta get
better when i'm
a little late
now of course scott you know my
famous character the guy who can't do
vibrato but tries to do anyway of
course oh ho say hey can you
see by the dawn's early
that's all these things the only things
the national anthem nuttall know we've talked
about this but you guys have the
sing the national anthem at a baseball
game no i have not we got
it come on hire the three of
us together as a trio i know
someone who knows someone in the a's
organization
the oakland a's oakland a's oakland athletics
and he said it would be entirely
possible that i could sing the national
anthem at an a's game you know
connection to the haze do you know
who cares i've been doing most of
the people singing don't have a connection
like green and yellow saying la dodgers
would what's going on anytime i go
there so
some jerk just that no one knows
this time was this old man and
his son they were dressed the same
sounds good no that was the oscars
with during the in memoriam andrea bocelli
i'm sorry
and co know but i mean look
no one knows us either but that's
exactly who god please so we'll do
it as yes we'll trade off mines
we'll do a little rap in the
middle it'll be great we'll do it
fergie style yeah no little story about
the national anthem
that's the route yeah no one anthem
put the national anthem sir francis scott
key he's the guy still
he saw all those bombs going up
in the sky
and it's a weird owl or our
national anthem isn't that yuck it really
fucking sucks the song yeah already says
a song parody what it's it's the
tune is an old drinking song for
various yeah i'm english i mean every
time you hear it makes you want
to drink right yeah makes me wish
i was drunk right because i'm out
of sports game
im cool
talks about peanuts getting all dehydrated yeah
why do we have to sing that
at the fuckin game that's the thing
it doesn't isn't doing it doesn't belong
long take it out of that ticket
out of football there's so much weird
like america raw rod patriot bullshit going
on jets flying over here's the thing
if you
added to whatever we're like we should
have to sing it before every episode
of this and then people will be
like this is america's podcast you mean
on mic because we do it off
my yeah well i'm sure people think
of this as america's podcast yeah what
else would it be what else would
be america's podcast or not this i
really don't know i don't think there's
anything more patriotic than what we do
ah lauren when you're right you're right
i mean let's just facts i can't
imagine something more patriotic than this but
yeah i mean they i don't think
they ever used to do then i
fell games and they wouldn't even air
it but then suddenly like they start
adding it in this jango istick sort
of like yeah
you know let's make football america's game
who cares who gives away every game
every type of game yeah now the
seventh inning stretch we should do that
for all sports all sports neat using
take me out to the ball game
no matter what the sport i'm like
when talkie when does baseball start again
it's probably any minute spring training is
happening right now
and we do it seven ninths into
whatever game is happy yes seven ninth
in exact football game is four quarters
we do this in the middle of
the fourth that's right that's right
ok okay you know i i we
talked about this i think but i
want my most recent time i went
to a dodgers game it was i
was invited to a special box you
know and i was like that's the
only way
some some at some points i was
thinking to be cooler to be in
the stands actually which i hadn't done
in a million years you know what
i only time i've ever done it
but i did that for a um
basketball game i got back is yeah
yeah and it was fun it's fun
because you just like really have a
conversation you can get around yeah
bathroom get some food although you can
eat it's all very easy yeah but
there is something about the baseball boxes
when i've seen them i don't think
i've ever been inside one but it
always seems like with the window and
everything that it just feels weird like
where you happen you do you also
have seats you can't go nine nine
y'all you have seen i did one
time i sat
that like right behind or just adjust
to the left of home plate um
because a friend had the this great
hookup with seeds and owen mean ever
raise your face right and you lie
to the net know i wanted to
i wanted it it was was gonna
be suicide by baseball
um but yeah what's the name of
that thing with owen meany a prayer
for forty i don't entirely know that
or simon birch that's okay that's the
movie version but three jim carey's in
simon birch say jim jason simon bird
he's jerry galleries and simon burns as
an adult or something he he's the
adult ah
ah simon's best friend wow
weird huh it's funny that they still
made that movie where it's like it
got so far away from the source
material and why not call it owen
meany just because it got so far
away i think so and there's i
don't know because we infor opinion for
a pound i guess we're gonna keep
doing this movie still i've never seen
it although i will say it was
released on stereo gts
laser disc format and scott hasn't seen
with paul with you know i'm not
you know i want to do these
with you i can only do the
one that i do know what we're
gonna run out next year then i
need you to do every episode oh
no no i'm gonna replace sean yes
no no no i can't hate him
i can't be sprague
yeah you just say sprig sprig way
um ok guys we have to take
a break okay so we'll be right
back
we're back i can't tell if i
am
like never going to sleep again or
if i'm going to fall asleep right
now because that coffee i hope really
ever again if i had to make
a choice it's really fucking up my
head man just out of ah people
so but i'm on the three meme
you mentioned that you had three cups
of coffee today yeah and it's really
not good i shouldn't have done it
i shouldn't but i was so sleepy
fyi yeah it was so sleepy i
always say don't coffee seems like a
fun idea it seems like a fun
idea i never ham or so or
something like you've never had it well
you've never had coffee in your life
i think just a sip once fifteen
years ago mo no job huh i
have seen i smell it every day
do you like the smell i do
like the smell of it it's nice
right i just i don't drink caffeine
and then i think if i did
maybe i'd like it maybe i should
do it interesting theory why not a
little
prep and mason yeah try it on
mike on our next episode oh you
know our next episode we're taping nine
a m oh that's right oh i
love to drink caffeine i'm not morning
time i'm not do it what if
we did the pepsi challenge with you
said you never had a soda you
never had a coder i've sold what
i used to drink it
all the time you never had a
cold i don't drink caffeine now i
stopped drinking coffee when i was nineteen
actually i haven't had caffeine beverage the
average age of of soldier and sip
here or there cocoa caffeine yeah i've
had a sip of coke you know
once every few whatever's but it's been
about nine
eighteen years since i've regularly drink so
caffeinated soda dear let me tell you
what the pepsi challenge was yes i
took it the but of course we
all did where did you do where
did you do it at home oh
no no no i did the official
one the official one modular oliver no
edgy on the pepsi challenge was a
gauntlet thrown
down by pepsi and they said essentially
coke is better than is not as
good as pepsi well that's right like
like coke is so popular and yeah
pepsi's popular too but everyone says oh
can i have a coke can i
have a coke can i have a
coke pepsi taste better yeah and we
aren't talking about your poodle yes pepsi
how do you remember
it's obviously because i'm listening back to
the episode all right so they're actually
sleeping in a low that's right you
listen to all of our episodes yesterday
french canadian um so ah they would
blindfold people yeah and they wouldn't they
would leave them to a bunker probably
fifteen miles away yeah it's covered with
spiders
so you wouldn't know where you were
yeah they would drive around in a
circle for a while so yeah notions
of direction yeah yeah then they'd spin
you around put you in this bunker
and then you had to put your
hand in some spaghetti yeah and then
someone would crouch behind you and they
would push you over yeah but as
the pepsi challenge just oh teen titans
or pepsi yes and then eventually you
would you would
blindfold or you would take sips of
pets not hard at all that's the
easiest test of the world you think
there's very similar know you would say
what you'd like betters year and okay
it doesn't matter you would know which
ones which it's not about
oh god oh you william from the
taste god damn it you haven't drank
at nineteen fucking years how do you
know what you tomorrow let's do it
tomorrow i will know alright you'll know
when i've had coached decades i've sipped
coke in recent history but it took
so strong now having not drinking for
three
yeah now legal coca-cola no i mean
like my day i like drink it
so much growing up that like you'll
know you'll just absolutely but i know
i know everybody happy if you got
you got pepsi r c cocotte you
die oh we gotta do this yeah
well you know them all i love
our schola
perpetual number three you you may be
number four do you think you could
tell the difference between diet coke and
pepsi between diet coke and diet pepsi
or diet coke and regular pepsi yeah
because the latter of course diet coke
and diet pepsi i definitely tell it
from a ladder know but couldn't you
you don't think you could tell like
if i was climbing up like pepsi
lauren
it's not about telling them apart it's
about which his daughter better but when
you're tasting them you're going that one's
coke that one's pepsi still saving you
that hand look i deplore it well
here's here's nobody who nobody who's a
fan of finding paw can i just
tell you don't know variance and i
love i love this because when i
did this oh no hear here i
tell you my
experience when i did this year magic
he's a veteran of pepsi challenges and
thank you for your service you're welcome
now these these commercials they should salute
people at bulk games that yeah these
commercials were all over national television okay
yeah i wanted to be on one
yeah you take the pepsi challenge thinking
they're probably filming
me while you take it yes even
though there's no cameras around yeah you're
like now in retrospect in hindsight it
was just something that you did a
long lands yeah yeah but i saw
i take it going like i got
to pick alright guy i got a
big pepsi in order to because that's
how you get in the commercial scene
yeah because hey like like yeah one
more so i take it you can
only
get the commercial choosing coke if you
look real dumb yeah yeah and then
they build it out to a music
bar and you have like a will
one of those like spindly pinwheel hats
on or something and we pin
so i take this and i go
okay curled via i obviously know the
difference between pepsi and coke yeah i'm
gonna pick the pepsi so i get
on every channel age of reason sure
yeah i'm eight years old you'll understand
what i really would be surprised if
we got it wrong so what do
i do they taste different i taste
them both i go oh yeah i
obviously know what this is and i
pick the p
pepsi turns out it was coke okay
aw now i'm really screwed a child
governor on it wrong your palate wasn't
only catering towards those flavors i think
throwing our in there really are she's
gonna throw it off so yeah she's
really gonna throw it off a lot
because our seas will pleasingly like
like a more like a pepsi puts
me in w rupee or in there
too no i don't like group just
as a palate cleanser rose root beer
yeah it tastes like licorice ginger beer
no lashings of ginger beer now should
we just do it as a total
total like an m and m's challenge
pepsi coke
that's it just so you we can
really tell let's see because honestly i
haven't had i haven't had pepsi in
many many years okay but i do
think i'll be able to because i'm
the one who has to buy this
get it oh okay that's good news
go get it you thought you had
no idea we hadn't discussed and i
don't have time
any time either but you're gonna do
better i'll i'll figure out some way
to do this because i because i
really and we have to try and
tell you what why don't we all
have to do it i'll all buy
soda yeah oh bite on the way
home okay that's good whoa are you
going to go to the foster era
what was it fosters reading the way
home to eat lunch okay that's
sucks but tomorrow's perfect time it was
a weekend too much perfect time to
do it so you'll buy the you're
so you're going to buy pepsi you're
going to buy coke are you gonna
do i'm going to try to find
our sql anything i heard another another
cola yeah and then we'll blindfold each
other simultaneously
and try to figure out where all
the like try to poor middle and
to
ah so our mouths each other's bubbles
it's really about it can the third
person tell can you tell from the
shit which ones yeah
thanks for spelling it
ah okay so that's gonna be episode
two hundred and two the palindromic two
o two can we make it to
three so it's not quite sold early
yeah i'm certainly recording at nine tomorrow
i think we should do that a
little bit later okay i'll allow it
okay it's all going to will get
tummy two o three hey wanting to
do to me i don't want to
get a two-week i just don't have
it
too late because i don't want to
be up all night
we're not drinking so much we have
thinking ships now i'm you're gonna jump
big gulps big guys i'm going to
take big gulps you know that the
big gulp the seven eleven big book
named after the like rather large gulps
that you would take when you would
drink a very loose outbreak yeah no
shit
ah i'm pretty excited about this and
i want to be and i'm not
even going to practice oh have you
practiced tonight
that would be so sly i should
have not instead of degree it would
be so sly little bit sly and
really cool of me what other animals
are sly besides foxes any i know
because why do they have that railways
wondering they have that right because what
what they sit around killing things they
sneaky around only like
feel like snakes are kind of sly
yeah they're always in these holes in
there but they have slither so that's
the sell for them they only get
one cell yeah yeah alright bears get
sleepy
lions get slutty it's like yes
frogs are slippery
seals are slutty
so those lines oh i just i
just lay on the bank yes
which animals are the sleaziest animals wow
i know everyone's got their theories like
which ones sleep around a lot yeah
they don't have the same partner i
always feel bad for animals when you
read these stories about like how spiders
made or whatever it's like oh so
then you know the spider puts out
a huge pheromone and then goes and
has it's way with the
male spider and then it lays a
millionaire eggs then the spider eats it
or something like aspose just sounds so
bad for the female spider it does
actually seems only for all female racers
so compassionate and you're such i know
we're allies were like allied cats female
cats like wow i'll give it to
me and then it's happening
yeah
stop doing that anger yes you do
while we've already talked about animal penises
but cats have barbed yes yeah yeah
yeah nothing about the snake yes why
do they why do they do it
and yet i don't know you with
everyday no more cats why would the
cats evolved to the point where the
female goes crazy like hey everybody
come and give me sex yeah and
then the male cat has the bar
penis so that she can't run away
it's like she's she's there she should
at least be able to don't need
the barbs dude yeah like like trim
the barbs trim the bar i just
don't feel like you can actually speak
to what the female cat is fee
feeling yeah we don't know that's the
thing we've never been able to interview
a cat that's you know suddenly say
oh she's there okay she's she's i
mean she's no longer it said something
that you thought sounds noise she made
sounded like the noise my mom used
to make yeah when my daddy oh
has a low time and i know
she wasn't enjoying that yea
shit my mom would call my dad
at work and just go ma into
the phone so they could go rushing
maybe
nasty that they were nesting yes oh
they were nested six kids nasty yeah
that's a lot as to mete you
tell them you're almost pregnant for like
her whole adult life me your mom
yeah yeah yeah and you you were
pregnant your entire adult life who feels
that way sometimes i gave birth to
show business ah
huh
goodbye
ah wow oh no paul he's doing
is mating call myself into to han
ho all these cats have arrived at
that once he wants it
ah what do you how do you
interpret the cats yowling know it's horny
it's a desperate call
it's it's you don't think it's confident
confidence yeah like in a bow about
an out now kind of way um
no i feel that it's well it's
powerful long head do what a damn
oh huh
huh
man i'm in heat bound bound by
air now wow wow this thing when
you're watching a nature documentary they always
say like the male wants to do
this and they don't know we've never
been able to talk to you know
there's this nature documentary docu series that
holly always wants to watch because it's
at the top of disney plus and
we've i put it on a few
times cause it's like
i think it might be a little
cute some of the warnings at the
top you know at the word says
like this is rated such and such
for whatever it's like violence and acts
of a sexual nature you know it's
like i'm like this is so aggressive
and then the episodes are like
always some animal being stocked and preyed
upon and violent and i just don't
want
i don't want her she she just
wants to see cute animals we like
surely to fuck a puppy bowl yeah
there's there's this book called hug hug
hug which is which is a it's
all about a monkey who i have
that i have that yeah yeah like
sees animals hugging like two elephants hugging
like oh hug i just acquired
that and he ripped a woman's face
off well that's the thing i'm hugging
you so like so like he goes
around the animal kingdom is like oh
huh ugh ah but but he wants
a hug and doesn't have one and
so this elephant takes him around to
look for where he's gonna get a
hug and then finally his mom finds
him is like bobo and he's like
mama
when he finally gets a hug and
then he hugs the elephant says hug
and then the entire animal kingdom is
there going hug and i'm thinking they're
all just going to murder each other
yeah if this were real life because
they're all in the same place yeah
they're all in the same place that
you don't like huh let me tell
you something yeah
the watering hole the warfarin place where
all the animals come and they sort
there's more truce yes much like our
watering holes in life in the human
kingdom but they go like hey you
can just have a drink here yea
that's my kelly we all agree we
all agree like come here for drinks
there's nowhere else to drink so
we all have to do it yes
so you know it's pretty nice it
is but it's sort of like but
if i see you here by yourself
on beer yeah if i'm lying and
your design dazzle yeah and you're by
yourself no other gazelles yeah i'm gonna
get you yeah huh yeah i know
we should
we should have watering holding a carl's
with other countries and there would be
no more war my god wow what
a beautiful image yeah it does seem
like we should just be doing war
ai now right yeah really good too
it was stupid in a video should
be big video games yeah and and
the heads of countries should have to
play the game and that's how you
decide
hi this is somebody else's bit i
think i think you will have to
elect a person who's good play they
have to shoot just like video you
know you gotta do stand-up with this
tonight
i miss you to new york ego
by five ten fifteen twenty times tonight
you ever seen one of those those
world war two like like i know
they've done this in dr hayward and
stuff where it's like on christmas day
everyone stops fighting and they all sing
like like both sides of the famous
christmas artistes
right during world war one it's just
doesn't make sense to me why don't
the other people go like
why don't we just not do it
at all they'd be really cool right
right why do we have war
honestly though whoa whoa are stupid and
be policy bid and love me nothing
and some strange border what's that that's
a culture club song that ended their
career really i think because that's like
their last song you got on the
radio yeah boo flank
i don't know if it wasn't i
gotta say that sadly it's so annoying
anytime i want to say these guys
are making enough karma chameleon do you
really want her here do you really
want to hurt me ah yes um
you have mistake number three i don't
know that one it's mistake number three
oh gee
e they have a pact not to
make three mistakes
and that is making sake number three
i know yeah what are the lyrics
now you're done
you are mistaking them for three goodbye
beach joe mistake quota and now boy
george is doing all the the theater
stuff yeah oh really yeah okay let's
hear yours like the moulin rouge you're
doing the christopher stats fun use the
lyrics to mistake number three i'm gonna
see if we can parse this yeah
this part da da da da da
da
da da da da da da na
the car commercial da da da do
do you can't stand you you can't
buy stand all the people stand them
on their own so true they will
fall to pieces of people so we
watched them grow what are you talking
about mistake number three yeah into strange
and pr
pretty faces i don't know clutching to
my lipstick traces watch them go okay
i have no idea but this is
bullshit white sox well that was almost
guys deserve to not be on the
radio anymore yeah
oh man she was overcome with emotion
i just lawrence having i feel really
bad that they didn't get to keep
like doing shit
because like they were really good and
i just feel like they like it
to do like oh really i never
heard you say shit about rank and
roger who from english beat yeah sure
so much about culture club what about
rankin roger yeah i'll die that one
english beat song that i got into
this last year and i really like
which one mirror in the bathroom it
for later
beta booty day
a down and food and yeah it
just came up on my spotify and
i was like this is for me
so you came up and you're like
yes ma'am i was like got me
figured out algo i gotta listen to
this enough to get it on rap
that whole album great really special beat
service i've honestly never even ventured past
the song because i just think yes
oh yeah i confess this good one
confers and coo
alright yeah i'm gonna have to check
that out later mirror on the bathroom
is also one of those earworms for
me yeah with the same amount of
single syllables yeah did did did did
did addicted yeah you have that yeah
i don't even yeah
i don't hear that the same way
you're lucky because it's a curse so
if i were to say like here's
an example lauren in the bathroom well
now i know i'm probably here to
florida oh i thought you'd hear lorin
in the bathroom oh you know what
the woman in the bathroom oh but
what if i were to say
mirror in the bedroom
mirror na bedroom
i know yeah there i i did
not put it together this they're the
same samples but it it does it
does it it matters how it comes
out like yeah staccato of the of
the syllables exactly determines whether or not
i'll go to mirror in the bathroom
or girlfriend in a coma
i'm an interesting person so if i
were to say mirror and a coma
you're in a quandary and does not
come you do yeah what's the meaning
of law marks do things with janey
were like
one of you will start to get
really annoyed by something like that like
if you're like i can't stop singing
a song oh yeah well no i've
stopped pretty early yeah for sure pretty
early on in our relationship we would
watch like thursday night tv at my
house and cool up along with neil
mahoney yeah you read it awesome shit
oh
and it would be like no it'd
be csci and e r and stuff
like that and so any song that
didn't have any theme song that didn't
have lyrics i would add lyrics for
zuma so when we would watch e
r it would be like it's sinjar
it's e
and at a certain point she's like
shut the fuck up
i don't know how the our theme
song went to di di di di
di let's hear it all i remember
is eric lasalle doing the yes the
big yes oh yeah i love that
so moving let's hear a little bit
cry i would cry every time first
we have a hurts i allow my
ideas blast
adds tom brady hurts ad first this
kid this is not skippable don't really
oh did ya ya should have the
ad-free youtube in this way this visa
is the only every generation ever get
it i have every delia it makes
me laugh every
this rocks
ah it's true it's like it's really
wrong this is like the worst massage
music yeah it's good i'm two dancers
come down from the ropes we have
to walk on your back we have
to take a break
we'll take you out with e r
by the e r gang
uh
and we're back and it's three church
time that's right scott it is we
do three cheers on this show and
you can't say that we don't feature
is a game that we play and
maybe you would like to send us
one to play a parlor game a
car game if you will not harm
good game not a card to gain
hours or so boring yes and there's
way way way the wages of sin
is death and um so we play
the game and so what you do
is you send it to us at
three dm usaid gmail dot com that's
email it's so easy to just email
someone these days like it used to
be remember the process of how
how you used to have to email
people yeah gp to get it approved
yeah i've sent it up to korea
during a dialogue yeah yeah i'm good
or have you become a computer mimi
mimi my name when you okay computer
i mean i'm going to start saying
that like ok boomer or like radio
to my own computer who's that
um this one this reacher this particular
three-tier was submitted by josh thank you
josh thanks josh and it's called taboo
word okay they're not gonna get us
they're not gonna again so taboo remember
remember they were supposedly lesbian zuo dated
each other law
la turn out their tattoo oh yes
two way i immediately accepted when you
said taboo well but you start thinking
it because she said but into my
head when and why did you start
singing it if i think because i
said taboo word because i conflated taboo
with touch yeah yeah so don't pin
this on me ice i'm just glad
i
was here to clear it up thank
you to sue because honestly if you
guys you guys talked in circles point
o one of our listeners percent of
our listeners would be like it's tattoo
i think there's me a lot more
do you think tattoo listens to show
i hope they do all the dishes
that just wasn't in my head went
through my head running through my head
do you think icona pop listens to
the show i think i don't care
i love it i think they do
though um this is taboo where this
is submitted by josh two players secretly
decide on a taboo word by texting
each other then all three daughters began
a scene prompted by the suggestion
nw of a common household item what
that part of it pan with broom
that is jazz and optional parties are
in the spirit okay but the two
players that know the taboo word have
to organically try to get the third
player to say it we're not allowed
to say it ourselves the third player
has to try to
avoid saying it
they say it the game is over
and we're gonna put a clock on
this lauren okay we're gonna put a
clock of how long should we do
it should we do it five minutes
minutes okay we're gonna do a clock
of five minutes zone hit lap show
oh you think a guy like me
would hit lap ah
not gonna do it
wow what's yeah what's shiplap shiplap is
like a little pieces of wood
putting wood on your on your wall
instead of in a certain pattern instead
of wallpaper a magazine yeah shiplap is
and there's just literally read yeah just
like i'm just pushing this into my
phone it's like um doing if you
wanna do a wall like a
beach house yeah yeah i knew it
had something to do with something nautical
so we have a ton in that
room over there wondering i know you
can't see it there's like a good
fellows where you get me to go
down there and yep
yeah why don't we good way to
murder so that is one of the
scariest scenes through like yeah go go
good don't tell further down there guy
just keep going just keep go okay
so who wants to be the two
and who wants to be the one
um i'll be the guinea pig okay
okay and so learn and i so
we text each
other well you can text me or
i contextual text you a taboo word
yeah just a word that that we're
trying to get him to say oh
okay okay yeah but we can't say
it ourselves okay
yeah because it's gonna be great
right and i'm going to start the
clock now
paul yeah do you need a common
household item
um yeah devlin yeah what do you
have dust pan you have a dustpan
yeah well actually look it's kinda cool
we're in the breakroom of the hardware
store right now i'd never really loved
being back here yeah yeah it's cool
yeah because you normally your customer normally
i'm just a customer you know we
recruited you today
yeah just usually come in and buy
stuff but today i kind of was
like we come in here a lot
we needed help thank you for joining
us do you need any snacks or
anything like that or what do you
guys have pillows kind of ruffles
that'll be mark ruffles
it's a little early for chips shaped
ruffles
i mean it's only eight thirty i
don't really want to eat roughly of
coffee we have whatever you need
i'm hungry though
okay how about some food what do
you think ruffles i'm telling you it's
early for ships it's a little early
for chip so my i'm more of
a breakfast how about a danish ah
so it's too fancy yeah guy anything
else i mean we're not a supermarket
hardware do you have in the whales
what's in the box with the one
hundred ne
nails what's in the box with the
danish show what are you brad pitt
what's in the box
there's also some bear cause yeah honey
why don't you bring something the next
time you'll work here yeah i'm kind
sweetheart forget it i'm sorry what's your
name bunny
money what's your favorite food yeah but
what do you like croissants in the
morning yeah what about hot buttered toast
sure
do you want some how about some
fried chicken i want something that i
can stick my finger through
yeah how about my ass
why oh wait you guys play back
hey watch eight time and was it
donor yeah yeah
okay so now you guys just text
each other oh you're going to guest
okay cause you can pick i picked
a word yeah you can pick the
word and send it to learn oh
the things you said although things she
said i do my head running through
my head running through my head that
was two minutes i think you fuckin
okay
two two isn't while i knew what
it was i was just media files
two three
thank you for loving it okay oh
you press a little harder yes
okay she said you don't have to
not only did i see it i
received it and i lost a household
item let's say scissors great i don't
get what that is i needed a
way it's just a thing i guess
it's so that you're not in danger
of overlapping with the words yeah if
you know that's what you're starting with
is oh it's a suggestion suggestion to
start the cia right here we go
okay and once you're done sewing those
up
um then i started the next human
centipede
it'll be ideal can you cut me
out of this one please don't we
sooner i'm just not enjoying it anymore
but we allowed you to be able
to talk that's gotta be applied oh
i know it's just my ass
i'm on the i'm on the good
end but i we we so that
guy's soles of his feet to your
hands yeah that's honestly i'm enjoying that
if you can keep that that's actually
confusing yeah why is it confusing just
the position he's been in yeah seems
like it would hurt
because he standing in the guy in
the front is like a willpower hooey
yeah anyway could you or no or
could you or not because you would
you with a spoon could you would
you ah with ah with ah okay
you're not helping trying to do a
green eggs and ham oh yeah wearing
always started dr seuss or something yes
is it your occupation people do kind
of think that i'm like the next
really
yeah i'm a doctor now i'm just
a really good rhymer like what i
can even think of one right then
but you know like what what if
you were to say radio what rhymes
with radio
um plato
okay look we
i'll be honest with you
yeah yeah what's up oh no when
he gets honest it's worded well i
just i'm a straight shooter we're not
going to cut you loose from the
human centipede but i yeah standards your
birthday oh okay we will be celebrating
your birthday here with all of the
centipede comes a little monkey very little
ghee carrie white i know yes oh
my gosh she has cupcakes too and
wow cake and cupcakes candle in every
single cupcake wow and then one candle
in the cake yep and because i've
really for my birthday the cakes great
but i really
i wish you'd gotten me like some
sort of ride
that would take me up into the
sky like a blimp or something like
that an airplane yeah an airplane could
yet be an airplane right think about
you and helicop don't even like the
decorations they're fine streamers are fine the
whole you know happy birthdays what else
what else to love sweetie the wrapping
paper you wraps the cake which is
like
attentional big god unless you like one
big guy tough guy i like how
you turned the house upside down and
boils widows due to delicious
house is it what does our relationship
by the way because you wiped my
memory oh we're mad scientists and you're
our human centipede yeah oh this is
just like watching you poop in the
meats human centipede kind of thing i
don't even think that do you like
to scientists use him he was a
normal person i don't think it's a
highbrow
i think it's only a tie bra
wow i use balloon right yeah okay
my turn won more tao i text
cheese time no i haven't gotten to
guess yet yeah i know oh sorry
i took off so that's right going
clockwise sorry sorry okay so i text
too
to paw the taboo word and i
receive it
um
okay yang
and what's a household item learn it
is a pair of tongues a pair
of time everyone has times these days
alright i'm pressing start
well now look at you wear nothing
but a pair of toms
yeah i have a pair on
i've two thongs disgusting it's better than
one it covers more yeah you're right
wow now look who it is who
is it mom tis or self
it's bonnie yeah i'm here hi bonnie
hi guys bony like it's so good
to wherever every being maybe just been
trying to get out of this complete
complete hole i'm in like i've just
been like emotional with my neck in
like problems oh my word tell us
just everything is going crazy like killing
example i lost all my papers what
kind of papers everything good bad important
money useless my receipts and star seats
l anything papers school papers lost them
i um like to do lists i
bought for phones instead of one and
now they all won't stop bringing oh
no you accidentally bought for full and
he set them off to all of
the same number yeah and they're all
ringing off the hook because i signed
myself up for all these calling large
biome i bought them from this kiosk
at the mall
all
what were you doing at the mall
shopping for what new tongues new tongues
new tongues no tongues you can buy
those anywhere you don't have to go
to the mall you do have to
go to the mall no you don't
you don't know they saw anywhere is
that all ya book did you buy
any food um do any food yeah
about a stay
take where did you get that at
the good the butcher
hey way to put your boot you're
sorry she's like i've lived here like
just long enough that your accents are
starting to get to me
but like no yeah the butcher
yeah yeah if you went to too
many places okay you can go one
place it's got a wild place what
like
supermarket yes alright we got ya we
fucking got you you know when i
got you because i was willing to
say no
thank goodness but shame it's gotcha and
that's how you play taboo and then
say put again as they're not gonna
get us farther than you said although
thank you to taboo
what did you do josh for sienna
josh yeah yes that's a classic and
any like essential three-tier write to us
at three numb usa at gmail dot
com and if you'd like to think
there's a voicemail call us at ah
well don't call us but you go
to the website hag claims eight dot
com and there you will be able
to leave us a voicemail
message i can't believe this we're living
in a world where this is possible
really cool website we're going website you
talk to it and then a recording
bird exact and then we hear it
exact nice and guess what if you
want to hear ad-free versions of this
podcast and also here are bonus episode
lips called three mediums then you go
to
dvd where my world dot com and
you sign up for the maximus tier
three memes are also available on some
sort of apple subscription or something no
one's explained to really although no it's
it's apple ah what does it call
maybe it's the lemon ata like if
you subscribe to ooh i don't know
but i'll tell you one
the thing i do know i know
this as hell cold hard fact will
you re-release all of our previous episodes
the ones that are behind the paywall
the ones that you can listen to
it cvb world we released them weekly
it's called three visiting on the twos
and that is every tuesday you'll you'll
hear an older episode
so don't be confused if they're like
like on one episode i'm saying i
don't have a baby and then another
one i'll i'm talking about my baby
because you've probably just heard them out
of order yeah and for until scott
had the baby we would so get
him to stay yeah once per episode
i don't have we would do a
baby kind of timestamps and we do
baby check yeah yeah yeah um but
we love you guys so
much and like everything you guys do
with why are you so statistics like
this was like listening to the show
or could be rolling her eyes everybody
you guys bring just like when you
press play on your phone and stuff
like it just does so much so
just keep doing that but you just
want pressing play on your phone yeah
i agree with lauren we do love
you we thank you for listening to
our cilia show and we hope
you will continue to listen to it
but yeah we're gonna keep doing it
and why wouldn't you continue this why
wouldn't we and why wouldn't we today
and i wouldn't who and if not
them then why not like it's a
waste of time for on our account
or on you know for you not
know this is time well spent for
everyone involved i would agree yeah i
and by the way hopefully you're getting
a massage
during listening i hope so because that's
i hope so that's very important i
don't know if we've said that in
or two hundred and one episodes but
us yeah this this podcast is made
for you to get a massage and
you have to multitask this podcast yes
it's about getting massages and if you
don't do that you're doing it wrong
yeah okay okay sweetie okay it's clearly
pie
a
alright well look we love you write
to us at three m usa gmail
dot com and lawrence taking your headphones
off feels like you're really thinking my
mom's smell all right yay goodbye