singing very fast watch how fast i
sin
straight up i choked
the best
yeah
faster than anyone i said faster to
what is the best with you you
didn't even hear me over sofa so
but some place yeah before each a
bleach featuring the flash the flash superman
batman aqua man and the flash you
know fleischer did the original superman cartoon
so you're not that far off
was a fleischer was leishman fishman is
in trouble from from ah northern exposure
remember that fleischmann don't ah joel fleischman
played by rod i think it's right
sure it's fleischer are you think of
charles fleischer was roger rabbit yes smallies
who are the body models for this
picture of you and reggie oh alright
well first of all shopper sean dixon
said hey i have a poster of
comedy bang bang in my house what
do you want do you want it
when we brought that over i'm like
what is he doing with that i
don't know it's like i'm probably national
ifc poe
post it was our third season where
reggie and scott are dressed like which
by the way if you ever have
a tv show and you think you'd
have some say on like what your
poster is going to be no they
helped they told me what it's going
to be this is the ad campaign
i actually really liked that you had
no say on that and that's really
funny
i mean given what it is it
has no connection to your show whatsoever
god for ten days or bottom of
a small svelte man with a unitard
from like a wrestling go sing let
ya know i'm like a ten percent
better body and just ten percent and
then the leg warmers like hot pink
leg warmers it's just funny that's what
you're wearing and you were like
sure yes it's okay like we don't
care if you think it's okay or
not no i honestly already printed so
i showed up they took a picture
of my head and then they had
the models there and there and i
was like what do you have met
the model yeah met them out and
they were like what's the concept i
said what's the concept and they're like
it's you and reggie working out and
the tagline is field the comedy burn
and it's just
that simple what does this have to
do with his burn have field the
comedy burn get it yes anyway so
that now i have this poster of
a couple of male models with me
and reggie's head voters it's got a
you should have that more than changsha
why does john have it i it's
in a frame i know yeah i
don't know what's going on with sean
he's in love with you obvious i
guess so
reggie is true or bunnies or these
models and not our heads that's so
he covers your head to be anything
it could be anything and he finds
the original models heads and he puts
them on paste them
and then you realize you've gone too
far like that you please take this
post please help me out of my
misery to go to therapy yeah yeah
anyway so i have a ton of
like my old posters around because we
closed our office because the pandemic and
all this and then the podcasts ah
your wolf close and so i have
a ton of these things around the
used to store well jackie johnson just
posted a
picture from serious exam of all the
art that you know the decorated shoe
the shoes from our fro yeah or
probably soccer shoes or she was digging
for mining she said i guess it's
at the bottom because i didn't get
to it huh i should've grabbed my
i know i wanna grab mine she
was i thought about it so many
times i mean i want mine so
if anyone out there
is that serious who wants to grab
it for us or if you have
any shoe just send it to us
send us a shoe if you look
here next time look into your house
if you see any shoe box it
up and send it to series yeah
no not wanting your shoes sim sends
someone else's look around your house and
find someone else's that doesn't live in
your house yeah one shoe
ooh one shoe please no baby shoes
never worn it's the saddest shortest story
oh the shortest story ever told shortest
turtle jesus webs that's the shortest story
okay well why the fuck was he
crying so much he is emotional guy
he had a bad life here yeah
i mean first of all these boarded
a terrible tie he
he knows that he's no internet no
toilet no tick tock tick tock you
can even do jesus dance
he would have been huge would you
why do they really what if you
want to have millions of followers instead
of just well yeah yeah
he he had that hanging over his
head the whole time like and you're
gonna die to redeem all of humanity
did he know that before was that
night before thing no i think he
knew apes i think you know and
then it just kinda like it caught
up to me so you think oh
shit that's tomorrow you think he knew
and it kind of informed everything yeah
i think yeah yeah i think he
started like let it slip towards the
end he's
like hey idiots i'm not going to
be here for very long yeah jeddah
together yeah when i say very like
him but by the way his day
started like you're gonna betray me and
you're gonna protect you don't know who
i knew all of it yeah you
know all of it anyway his life
expectancy he died thirty three
his life expectancy was probably thirty four
it's like it's not like it was
some great yeah he was elderly you
know what i mean it's like some
life expectancy well you with some great
tragedy was sick he was sick that's
the other thing is he was going
to die in three days anyway yeah
get a cold
and they were in cure back at
that time he called his fatal them
yeah yeah so you know come on
colas fatal line bible times sucked straight
up sucked yeah you don't have broz
you don't do you think the romans
didn't net browse ah they probably had
some sort of cloth that was draped
i bet i bet free experience and
probably let me just take ligula
this way it just draping a cloth
or regular didn't have bra caligula kahuku
da banana or that guy was a
freak watch caligula my friend's house once
and then build up yeah he lived
with his ya
he lived with his grandmother and his
grandmother came home in the middle know
oh and she came and she had
a conversation with us and she was
like blah blah blah she had a
really deep gravelly voice she was like
this and she's like bubble but anyway
so i wanted to ask the thing
and she would look at it she
would look at the screen this is
in the middle of the orgy scene
she would look at the screen and
when she would look at the screen
and there would be nothing going on
and then she would hope and she
would turn away and talk to us
and then suddenly there'd be like some
some yeah well hardcore sex happening over
there cutting away to during the orgy
they were like people's faces or malcolm
mcdowell's phase going oh haha or what
are you
yeah so it kept happening five times
we were crying laughing at it and
then she finally looks back and there
was like some oral sex going on
she goes oh my god she's eaten
this thing
okay
i'm sorry we have told the same
stories one hundred times and yet you're
sitting on oh my god she's eating
his band yeah i kept that in
the reserve that's crazy if anyone ever
mentions ancient rome i'll bring up the
power she ate his thing
it's like oh man died it was
so how old were you guys at
the time i was nineteen he was
twenty oh wow it's really fun and
i mean you know i was kinda
like should we be watching this in
your house while your grad knew he
had the kind of relationship where it
was like you know whatever whatever yeah
whatever it's one more thing yeah
oh my god just like oh my
god she's eating this thing
i don't think that's what she's doing
i've never seen that movie i never
have either i only saw that then
but i counted as having watched it
but like like in the middle of
the thing you know it's a weird
movie to watch them
when they come out well his grandmother's
doing areas but what year did that
come out in the seventies or it
wasn't it wasn't was it ah who's
the pennant bob or like maybe very
early eighties but yeah bob guccione it
produced it or wasn't it a thing
where they shot it and it wasn't
all that great and so they put
like hardcore porn in it in order
to like that's a fix
it's it's one you almost did that
between two ferns i think ah you
did want edit where you say sentimental
formed from caligula yeah let's see where
zach is just watching colliculus goes full
screen on this slow funny might have
improved the move that would have been
great uh
um yeah it was did you ever
watch movies you weren't supposed to watch
and then you had to turn it
off when your parents got home having
natalie i'm trying to think if there
was anything that was actually that i
think raised who's scared problem i think
i usually would do it really coward
we also didn't have cable oh well
you know what's weird here in l
a on my cowl nine or whatever
they would show
certain in syndication they would show certain
shows that had boobs in them benny
hill and i remember benny hill paul
hogan show i think crocodile dundee yet
to show he had a sketch show
or something like that before which is
good is very popular yeah yeah yeah
and so so my parents would go
away and we would turn on these
shows
and it's in black and white and
it's like well we're that desperate to
see boobs but then like suddenly my
parents would come home because they forgot
something or something like that and we'd
turn the tv off really quick and
then it got to be where my
my dad would like feel the team
to see if it was high
ah huh i and i probably have
told this story but i remember watching
kids my friends be oh yeah and
her older brother and the movie kids
yeah and it was so fucked up
and i just remembered no one caught
us nothing happened i just i was
haunted you know at a great argument
with a friend of mine about that
movie because i he was talking to
me
about it and i hadn't seen it
and i was like i don't eat
i don't want i'm i want to
know about this yeah horrible well and
i was like the age of them
at the time like i was yeah
and oh yeah i was eight and
yeah and yeah i think it's way
weirder to watch it what's the right
age yeah watch kids i would say
being the same age as that would
be the best way to go what
about one year in my mind
yeah so you can aspire i was
younger i was a little bit younger
but it won't be like seventeen but
i sort of think there's something gross
about watching it as an adult well
yeah and we're just kind of my
where i was coming from yeah it's
like i don't want to see that
and yeah like it's actually you know
it's like really rough but there's some
good performances and i'm like i don't
care i want to see it and
we were then we got we got
like genuinely we were genuinely argued
being and then it all came to
a head where he said
all i'm saying is it wouldn't kill
you if you saw it and then
we both started laughing
that's funny i've i must have watched
it when it came out when did
it come in the nineties right yeah
so i was twenty five that's that's
an okay age to watch i don't
remember a fine age to guess what
age should one watch kids well you're
getting older and it's about the time
you should be watching the movie kid
but yeah kojo this
century
i had a talk with my son
my boy today now knows what
vc ah it's only released on h
s yeah to this day um and
then we also watched wild things my
friends house that was pretty crazy oh
sure um very horny yeah it's very
horny film whole ne i recall that
i remember i recalled that dude you
make you hold as you see topping
slab
sheen this and that you do see
a penis although you see one in
gone girl is wellness gone good barely
seat and gone girl gone girl the
new laws on yeah you see it
a lot who's peanuts been my folks
i don't remember that pinos might have
to rewatch much do you watch the
spinoff yeah he's in the shower yeah
no i actually do kind of pause
yes it's way hitters in the shower
saying you pause yeah right where where
else would it be what he was
in a pool or something oh no
that's that kind of warps it a
little bit color of night with a
yeah bruce willis will you see his
unison schneider these guys gotta show their
dick he nuss p nah he na
sat right yeah penile show it the
ri
respect why lives and the only reason
i know that is because i believe
neil campbell wrote a joke about it
in the company paid tv show right
so yeah some of them
um i remember i saw kevin spacey
not oh my kevin hughes how kevin
spacey's venus zoo oh really congratulations ball
yes go here now this this forty
five years ago kevin bacon yeah kevin
big guns me not my own wow
he's the hometown boy kevin bateson wild
yes and wild things but he was
on ah instagram and he
i was putting on he did like
i love dr lewis instagram very well
i think he's so who term it's
very wholesome yeah but he was he
just like a montage of all the
the t-shirts he got from productions glennie
he was like going through a box
and he's like let's see what we
got so it's one i love any
small stems yeah yeah yeah yeah i
bet like some of them he threw
away yeah
talking about them but he would he
would like have a little you know
he will like this movie was like
some movie about a dog or something
like this great movie to watch with
your family is wrong i'm trying this
kind of free time and then to
make video speakers dealings
you find it can you like my
instagram hour if you do if you
film yourself wearing one t-shirt a day
and then you splice all together and
i made that one video per year
yeah it's really time to do that
space listen to go one to watch
so they put a wild things and
he said this we laughed all the
way through making this movie
a that's so funny yeah i thought
that was great i love that they
had fun and he sings with his
daughter anything single his wife it's all
very cute daughter who's in many commercial
with him yes about the electric right
yes and i knew that because i
follow him on instagram i was his
daughter and that was very nice man
when we did the tv show together
and i think i've told this tv
bb he did cbp
a big get so we met at
the season premiere and he was very
he's he's he's very he's kind of
a a very intense talkies for this
one of the hottest people i'm
earth possible
oh and i were he's very reserved
yes and you know i've spent six
hours on a couch with these people
have small talk and i was talking
about his band and music so are
you yeah must be hard it is
it actually was one of the more
difficult parts challenging but cool people you're
talking oh yeah yeah a lot of
interesting people and and but he was
just very very
quiet and very softspoken and then we
he's like do you want to rehearse
and so there's this bit ah kevin
town it's in the show it's very
funny and we rehearsed it and we
did one reading of any goes
funny stuff
it was like the most abusive that
that he was all day and i
was like we got it but then
turns it on for the camera he
keeps his energy low so he does
he doesn't have that kind of like
a lot of intense actors have that
thing where they barely raise their voices
above a whisper almost and it's because
they're film actors yeah yeah it's interesting
that is interesting i don't think
if so actually and i live here
cedric i don't think it's interesting i
don't think it's interest oh okay sorry
it's not your fault here cedric great
film make sure i'm getting it right
heart and soul do you remember that
movie with robert downey junior s where
he's a ghost yes no they're ghosts
they're ghosts he and they're trying to
be a little kid and love yeah
he's a little kid and there's this
bus accident where overcoming juniors little
initially he's a kid initially and then
oh my god we have so much
cause the ghosts and he can he
becomes a ghost and then he needed
to go so find him later in
their life because they're trying to kind
of tie up loose ends and he's
hoisted looking move on like their own
lucy yeah okay and so he helps
them go around to all the different
people
well it's a really sweet movie and
it goes around to all the different
people that they need to like connect
with they play the song resolves it
they play walk like a man if
that's your talking no heart and soul
oh no they actually nothing to getting
who are the goat it's being here
so i'd have to look is that
chopsticks that i'm saying ariz that heart
and soul that soul yeah and so
they go together like hard
heart and soul of the movie must
have been so upset when big stole
that song from them yeah but they
didn't like a movie that actually came
out later
um heart and soul so heart and
souls part of me oh good it's
shot charles grodin what now you know
no i'm just saying you can't just
pluralize it's how does such a low
rating did you get manjaro grow down
charles got on alfre woodard kira cedric
tom sizemore they die rest in power
king
arrested they die and nineteen fifty nine
when the bus they ride crashes the
four continuance goes cool are you this
amount of funny or die video sounds
like a great guy wow it's a
great movie he was born the moment
they die he was told they're like
that's why they're like immediately attached to
him yeah wow that's very cool it's
really cute
i got to see that you know
what you should put on scholars and
see if you haven't seen it as
oh would you do that episode twenty
my book for the last time i've
seen it oh my gosh last time
you seen that movie um i saw
it during the pandemic again i love
it and mike loves it too it's
a movie we loved as kids and
so we put it on
and we loved it i ever watched
the star trek movies recently yeah that
i hadn't seen since they were in
theaters and um the ah which by
the way i've not seen the final
one first ah here's the thing they
were all better than i really want
to see that but i was waiting
to do it an air order so
i was i was i was
trying to get plowed through deep space
nine voyager project can i stand it
before i saw that last one yeah
twenty souls yeah please say one less
thing i remember i saw it in
theater oh well my friend went about
some cool cheese eating thing
my god we my friend i went
to see that movie and we were
like eight or something and then we
came home and move the song walk
and walk like a man was like
a huge move song in the movie
and we spent the whole night calling
the old station trying to get them
to play it
it's adorable don't wait to hear it
and they wouldn't play it couldn't get
through couldn't get through to the old
east asia wow three it's a puppet
station did you just listen long enough
and they played it for sure probably
yeah um i so ah star trek
first contact is the one alfre woodard
is in fucking grade she does to
me i think guys
oh god in my i stopped it
i think generations in my rewatch of
everything so i still have two or
three to go to know you got
a bunch to go no generations was
the seventh movie i think yeah yeah
and then there's first contact insurrection
and i think i think if three
more okay not three and nothing more
interesting um alright well maybe i'll watch
these who knows should all leading up
to peikar be our picante
what's that what's picante yeah well so
this type of sauce type of hot
sauce okay i knew that that why
did you ask darling because i wanted
to know if you had an engravable
yes i mean will go my window
and they had picante but that's like
going to help me with my day
yep and the guy in that commercial
was the guy who starred in the
original house of cards for the bbc
with the grey poupon commercial yeah but
from the eighties yeah yeah he then
went on to star house a power
house of cards is so old my
grandmother hearts
alright have sick but i think the
commercials first gabbard
and we're back and um yeah we
are back sure and um
i was thinking the other day because
ah cool up sister isn't wasn't town
huh and for two nights ago duda
duda and she wasn't town she has
a ah a jazz a boy who
is ah now going very into junior
high strange and a very strange enchanted
boy
um and she was yeah we know
a lot about him this was ah
yes kai he of course was the
entrepreneur the entrepreneur was doing the science
the sneakerhead he i believe is no
longer interested in both sports cards or
sneakers i love that i love when
kids move on yeah now just focused
on basketball okay um and ah so
much so that
the baseball team really want and to
play this year because he's really good
and he was like nope i'm concentrating
on basketball so i get that he
is he's very focused very focused young
men anyway but this is cool up
sister's first time meeting our nebo baby
and ah ah she was i was
i was saying do you miss ah
your
her son being this age and she
goes yes because it goes so fast
and i was like it's feels like
it's taking no ever this is this
is the phrase that you'll hear over
and over again the days are long
but the years are short right wow
honestly wow these are preaching to and
that's shocking yeah it is really weird
it goes fast but it also feels
like every feels like the longest three
july yeah because it's like it's just
hours of yeah doing like nothing yeah
but um and here is so then
it led me to my theory which
is i think because
we all miss when people are babies
yeah everyone should when they wake up
be a baby and then they grow
to be an old man in a
single day and then they go to
sleep and they wake up babies lunch
everyone yeah oh i thought okay well
ah then i'll talk with the question
well you know what's great about it
it's a lot like that riddle of
like i mean who christ was god
let's get you know what's wrong with
this and i'm just realizing that what's
ah if everyone's baby who can take
care of each other you know well
no it's like the beach in old
where everyone's a baby for like you
know like half hour so we're all
like screaming our heads off and like
being ignored and like yeah meeting something
then you're
beginning and ending your day in a
diaper that sucks yeah i think we
should all be
wake up twenty five go to bed
fifty nine fifty add ten to that
i'm in ok
he said it he wants to why
do you want to die they don't
want to be young younger than twenty
five well i think you want to
be able to rent a car the
guy i want i want i want
so i want my brain to be
done developing that nice well here you
think your brain's done the mind still
got to go back to your twenty
five year old brain well i don't
know if you're going back to your
baby
the brain i would assume right i
think i think we should all have
the opportunity to have our our the
brains that we have now yeah um
in a baby body knows you feels
like one horrible because you can't you
you're you don't you can't do anything
though you can because you have your
brain is so you can be like
a rug rats you'd be like rugby
like a rug rats yeah getting up
doing all sorts of things telling ya
conversations and yeah yeah yeah but i
think i think i will miss because
she's so cute right now yeah but
it just like takes forever all day
for it does you know because she's
not doing anything you know and you
gotta constantly constantly attributing when she starts
crawling i mean you're gonna have all
these phases that are going to reignite
you know the excitement but what i'm
saying is is like i will miss
that cuteness i know you will yeah
you'll miss when she was a little
dumpling that she is right now yeah
because i have a friend who was
like oh my god i miss that
age because now it's just like she's
just constantly asking me for stuff and
i fixed my desk i have this
this
honest that's kind of where we're going
right now really getting into a lot
of like more more more more you
know maybe like how do you like
more more puffs more whatever rebuffs yeah
maybe hundred rebuff oh shit we had
these i bought these random sour cream
and onion puff setters who knows they
were some sort of simply vidyo random
i didn't think she was gonna like
it and she wanted to eat half
the i mean she just was like
more and more more more more and
more toughs but i do like the
chicken communicate a little bit so it's
it that's fun yeah she texted me
all the time she does yeah yeah
she's grabbed my phone trying to talk
to everyone oh wait i thought those
were from you
when i said loudly but i'm stopping
yes yes sounds exactly like yeah it's
ah um do you like do you
face time with ah relatives and stuff
we don't really like we're not a
big feast timing family but we have
done that from time to time but
people do say that that is it
doesn't count a scr
meantime apparently because they're engaging with a
person who disagree with yeah yeah um
we just don't do it very often
in my family but i'm i should
do it more because i want her
to know everyone's name she knows like
my dad's you know grandpa technicians go
to cheers and um yeah but so
sure she says
yes with pictures easy go to the
reverse cheers but i need to learn
everyone actually i had an idea that
i was going to get you're gonna
print out or put up on the
fridge pictures current pictures of everyone like
mugshot style yes that you can say
where hide behind it yeah yes well
because the pigment tall john's daughter was
saying holly's name from her
christmas card looks like we don't practice
people's names that way so yeah yeah
flash card yeah yeah yeah that's good
do you think the real quick just
the yeah the subject of the ah
cheers theme song which is you write
ah yeah do you think everyone knows
your name but you
no everyone else's name or do you
walk in there feeling bad because it's
like oh shit i don't know name
i never like god is not the
worst feeling yeah what do you do
when you're in that situation just play
it off for as long as possible
to you leave yeah yeah i have
done that i have oh hey you
it depends on it the thing that
fucking sucks is
i think it because of the business
that we're in sometimes you will see
somebody that you spend a significant amount
of time with yeah and you knew
their name and you had a good
relationship with them but so much how
much has happened yeah so much time
has passed it's like i know exactly
who you are but i can't remember
your name yeah and it feels terrible
yeah yeah you know
i know and you're so close with
them for like a year because you
can like work with someone for one
year absolutely every single day yeah and
really enjoy their company and yeah i
never get back to them yeah never
see them again yeah and it's it's
such a terrible feeling there are some
place there's sometimes where it's like i
know i met this person recently so
i can say i'm
i'm so sorry will you please tell
me your name like yeah you know
i'm in the situation now where i
do a show every other month yeah
at this venue and it's using just
enough time to forget to forget the
name every single but know the face
yeah yeah that is tricky and there's
some people where i think what happens
is
there's sort of an assumed we know
each other's name thing so no one
ever says it yeah and then you
never can say it or yeah they
like if if you're working at a
theater something where someone comes up to
give you some information and you don't
get their name cause they're getting the
information and then later like i wish
i had asked what their name is
that i can know that i know
and then honestly what used to help
me a lot
it was we had a mailing list
when i first started comedy yeah i
just got everyone's and i would email
them flyers for my not email the
mail them flyers for my shows no
snail-mail and so and we'd print them
all out you know and so i
knew every single person's name because i
was used to looking at them all
yeah yeah yeah yeah
um and i was talking to jenny
lewis from ah music about that because
i was on her mailing list i
was on her mailing list and so
that's how she knew my name for
so many years wow um and she
brought that up the last time i
saw her she's like oh remember our
mailing list and how you brought this
up so yeah yeah mailing lists are
a good way to go
yeah yeah well i mean i think
instagram can be very helpful with that
but then sometimes someone has a name
that's like of weird version of their
new and then you remember that yeah
speaking of being reunited with people you
haven't seen in a while last night
you have a son i had
turns out it's been a while last
night but i had a long dream
that we were
we were shooting the second season of
dag oh got there like the first
season was the year two thousand right
and then it's twenty twenty three eight
how gonna do a second see it
honestly could happen the way kumar now
with the reboots and all these things
i think that happens with popular show
now and it's it's i feel like
people just pull
out an old format and go tears
this was the best part was that
i forgot it had been so long
since i played this character i forgot
that my character had a prosthetic left-hand
which which one does he didn't say
oh i dream it was like in
the drinks if that's right i forgot
my character i remember during the dream
and i was like wow that's an
the hand the hand is not a
hand it is ah the hand of
a manahan the head of a ah
ear and nose hair trimmer yeah
that's grouse like my guy like it's
like inspector gadget e yeah like this
little tiny thing yeah and i was
like oh yeah that's right i forgot
i love it i had a dream
i'll tell this i didn't try to
dream i did you're committed i did
carl tart and lamar woods's gossip girl
podcast gossip gossip kings and so i
added dream that i always mix up
with
what's the other one gilmore girls gilmore
yes
and then they had that pog that
gilmore boys yes it was what it
was called yes it's just more guys
come on guys yea i did that
one right i mixed up the shows
whatever yeah i just had a podcast
and we'll get we'll get you an
okay sure thank you so much i
did the gilmore guys podcast and i
i had watched that show but fell
off of it
it and so i had not seen
this episode never seen any i found
out live was one of the it
was a live show to live upload
found out while i was on stage
and had to adjust some things in
my what my prepared box that it
was one of the most beloved episode
oh no you didn't like it i
hated it oh dear i absolutely am
naturally
for you yeah offense and i do
really you're famous and gilmore you're not
a young little girl
although neither are the host of the
show that day irony of it all
isn't it yeah it's ironic don't you
think don't you but yeah i really
hate it but i had to like
sort of hold back i didn't hold
back in my goal was the gossip
kings yeah because i just didn't understand
it but anyway so i of course
you're coming in watching one episode of
gossip girl it's
what are you going to pass my
memory of that show is doing that
like occasionally goofing on clips from it
for us we give oh goofed on
clips i remember your segment you remember
because i would die for goofy dog
clips with paul f thompkins it sounds
like a smash success it really was
it was the only segment that everyone
at emi ah whoa
my god yeah yeah for best segment
yeah they never did that category before
or some crazy yeah wow
i didn't think it makes it to
just open a ship in a bottle
i literally did not think that sounds
come out of my mouth you're supposed
to open those i don't know i
can do it again
yeah oh yeah i'm so high pitched
and perfect yeah it's cool yeah it
was perfect it was it was perfectly
lord we love to complain to go
whenever we want make it a drop
maybe probably definitely go over it a
little some kind of weird drop but
i do have to isolate yeah buttons
for drops here if we have buttons
oh my we need drag up buttons
for way way that would be so
funny
if like a billion episodes and we
start having drops and they're like a
saying like she's eating his thing and
you can't tell like are they saying
that live or is that an old
report and i
i want to plug my friend show
the smith sisters live on serious examine
my friends who are three sisters have
this show and it's so good if
you want like popcorn systems like chekhov
once wrote about yes why it's great
if you like pop culture or you
want to know what's going on but
you don't want to like keep tabs
anything they are so funny and they
tell you like the daily stuff it's
every single day on series x values
it's also on the app and it's
really fun and they have drops and
they're really funny and like their producer
just puts him in so you never
like they don't know it's coming right
and that's i love it um speaking
of chekhov yeah ah an oscar red
carpet moment that i did see was
you're talking to jessica chez stay and
just stay she said
says some point i'm doing like the
astor like what should people be looking
out for whatever what are you doing
next and she said i'm
i think this was the place she
goes i'm doing a play called the
the three sisters and it's like almost
nightly called three and it's not the
three system what i'm that that might
not be that was not the it's
not the batman it was that she
was like that's not the point the
point when you make a mistake that
she's saying like a play called as
if we don't know what the fuck
yes yeah yeah she's dumbing it down
for us she doesn't know what it
is i'm doing i don't know i'm
doing check offs i'm doing a play
called nine-member for christmas maybe you've heard
of the nightmare oh my god
i can finish my dream i'm doing
and i mean yeah just gotta finish
and i've managed to finish yeah but
can i finish okay so today this
was i'd already taped it but i
was dreaming about it so i was
like going to the taping and i
and i saw the host and it
was not carl and he turned around
it was harris whittles oh i was
like oh my god i'm so
so happy to see you and then
i realized i went oh in the
dream you realizing the dream i went
oh this is a dream oh that's
sad sucks yeah but paris laugh but
sometimes yeah he made fun of me
sometimes in a dream you can realize
it's a dream and then use that
to your advantage how like lucid dreaming
where yes let's go on a roller
co
after with them well you could just
ask him a question or something why
is it oh always his hell why
is
sorry purgatory paul ah her story
if
um one other thing i want to
write out
because we were talking about songs that
make us cry
oh where oh boo hoo in a
previous episode a long time ago oh
and i yeah we were talking about
that for years i remember yeah well
okay i wanted to say something because
we were talking about christmas ten years
ago on christmas um you're talking about
nightmares just a second ago because number
i remember christmas never sicker
i remember for easter never easter never
feast urge but um i turned on
i was like oh you know i
saw this on broadway but i was
like oh i'm gonna listen to the
soundtrack which i'd never listened to which
is the springsteen on broadway soundtrack oh
and i just turned it on in
the morning this is before co-op even
got ibos
you need to turn on i did
i didn't mean to yeah okay so
it wasn't yesterday didn't have to apologize
and song no okay so i turned
it on and the the third song
it's seven thirty in the morning and
i'm weeping my father's house oh yeah
and i did not expand i was
just like
oh yeah let's listen to a little
springsteen here in the morning and then
i'm just like yeah because he's he
he has a monologue in the middle
of it which is you to play
it i can play it if you
like out but it's making me think
of that song again tool ma fascia
was my father's eun joo and i'm
going to my father's she said
elton john fucking play
eric collapsing
alright here's a smooth i don't know
how long this is
the saw you on
i don't know if we're even gonna
get to eat we'll just skip to
the part would you know my name
if i show you which would you
know monet well because he was a
little bit oh shut up i hate
that little gnome
i can only skip to the monologue
part as always is a song about
stations too much this is a song
about his father who had a very
difficult relationship with contentious might say i'm
gonna skip i'm gonna skip ahead a
little and i stood on the porch
borge
yeah you're not the audience for this
or not plenty of huh yeah i've
never done him i did you fucked
him i covered it i covered the
song of his i covered ah thunder
road and only show i meant more
character onto ever done this character under
rule but i love that song it's
like a song that i never really
knew the words to under oath under
oath andrew
i think that's it you nailed it
there yeah and it's ah it's a
really it's a really lovely song i
really loved it anyway i would suggest
i got emotional listening to it by
the way it's on netflix or spotify
where you can watch road yet underwrote
is on netflix
i got a whole show that's why
they raised their prices yes no but
that that show is really good you
should watch because i it was not
what i expected it to be where
i was like oh we'll probably come
out and just like you know sing
acoustic versions of his songs whenever and
that's it but nowy was like him
telling the stories behind the songs and
everything is very very moving show check
it out
hi okay now you know i don't
know much about him really so i'd
be curious to see that i hope
i can see it before netflix suspense
my account again because there's there's this
learning it every day because you're sharing
them well i know i get a
text every day that says your account
has been suspended and you better rhino
i follow this link and click
like the lang give some money yeah
it's very similar to be good and
then i go check in my eight
courses turned back oh yeah and then
the next day another then another again
and i'm like alright i get i
get these calls and these messages on
my phone they say two point one
percent finance
yeah when you start in the middle
of the like the middle to wait
for the ease of dollars yeah like
today two point one billion do you
use your trucking me they're really little
though there's waste energy people are reliving
honestly we biden needs to get rid
of spam callers because he he was
in the process of getting rid of
they're too smart there's no way
fee there's no way to get rid
of any like back in the day
this stuff was manageable when like everything
was a landline yeah whatever now there's
it the the the horses out of
the bottle and i'm already just automated
computer worsening how to deal with back
in the day was those ah like
someone asking you if your refrigerator is
running friends as you like you get
that
thing in the mail that was just
like a circular right for what is
the who is and that was i
was like how is this legal that
this were sent this nobody wants this
correctly it's like fake discounts or what
is it i don't know what it
is just are you talking about junk
mail yeah oh yeah no they don't
post office to deliver rare yeah yeah
yeah but and there
doesn't list but it can like me
should not be like post web host
that's where you and i disagree like
junk mail i love it really yes
yeah because you like to go to
the trash can but yeah i love
the dragon would just be excused to
go probably circular know like when you
get the ones that are about the
fruits and stuff at the grocery store
sometimes
call it the circular filing cabinet
to but it's just the circular is
just about the fruits yeah circular is
just about fruits okay i might
or just about for new fruit discovered
worker
no whoops that was a strawberry apple
a postal worker told me how to
get off this list for his life
and i don't get something like didn't
say fucking do
ah man yeah to read come on
man i don't wait what is it
oh my god come on i thought
it was now i'm gonna say the
wrong thing i'm just not going to
say it but there's a way there's
a website to get off of the
junk mail w w w dot rick
roll dot com yeah i think it
is that and then you go there
and then you watch
a little thing i want you've watched
it enough times you get off we'd
be able
whoa let's go way to use the
rick roll is like gift was five
times in a row the whole song
man gorilla whoa alright we have to
take a break
i think that we're back i am
not so sure bomb around and i
see us all here i'm here i'm
here i'm really really here see she
sang out a parody of the nightmare
before christmas yes what's this what's this
what's this like
this i don't know why e r
what's this what's this i'm standing here
in piss my pants
i do know one thing and spits
alright this isn't the city you were
sending urine piss yeah cause i've never
seen i remember for christmas oh it's
good that's everyone yeah that's that's what
i'm want to check out but
hey you got a lot of kids
yeah yeah i see what your next
halloween or christmas so see really getting
to go into whichever way make it
a double feature with kids
oh wow yeah what's this what's this
example your kids
the kids are in my piss
ah paul you have a three-tier money
it's called it was submitted by robert
truths to troost first she spells robert
with two bees and the rain's really
coming down is it oh my gosh
i went whether i think he's a
robber and he put a t on
the
and throw stuff the scent green but
this is called off script okay one
player opens a weeki page or some
other article and starts reading it
i think he meant allowed three wrote
started reading it loud oh well see
how loud we can do it but
assertion loud at a certain point i
started let's start freestyling pretending they're still
just reading the contents of the art
oh that's fun the other two players
have to interrupt the reader the moment
they think the reader has gone off
script bonus rules bonus rules phone
bonus radio rules are are things that
we hate other players decide the article
subject for the reader to read players
get one guess if nobody guesses correctly
the reader wins the round two i
do random wikipedia so random
um yeah how do you do it
i don't know i just looked it
up i don't know either special random
special random okay i got one okay
and then you'll tell us okay there
and you'll start yell sir alright napoleon
bracey junior oh god you're okay
because i'm in pulling races yeah i
know all about i'll know exactly what
you got him napoleon bracey junior is
an american politician he serves as a
democratic member of the alabama house of
representatives where he represents mobile county alabama
in may two thousand and seventeen he
opposed the bill for the alabama memorial
preservation act
okay which would make ho god which
would make it harder to remove confederate
monuments in alabama he argued people that
sponsor bills like this don't care about
me and why should i care about
them because i can't okay
you've gotta
i think why one point
i think it's great when your voice
heard it differently no no he did
say that he did say people who
care about people that sponsor bills like
this don't care about me he did
it and that's the final word of
the article so wow well then i
miss i miss guest okay night just
do one right yeah yeah you know
i'm okay you do one thing
this is the wikipedia for smarties tablet
candy let's go tab like candy
okay i'm gonna try to ah what
a gif i can find out that
is a term i love that tablet
and the united states smarties are a
type of tablet candy produced by smarties
candy company formerly known as cd candy
inc since nineteen forty nine smarties are
produce
boost in factories in both union township
new jersey and newmarket ontario
the candies smiling so you're like oh
no i'm not and is distributed in
canada are marketed as a rockets to
avoid conf don't look at me it's
low because you can see my eyes
not moving the same way just a
bonus rule yeah bozo yankees don't have
to look forward to meeting canada are
marketed as rockets to avoid confusion with
sm
parties chocolate candy produced by nestle which
owns the trademark in canada rockets are
small disc shaped okay
why does you know
why did you go high i don't
know why you have to let it
go on even when we aren't because
it's like yeah because i wanna hear
hey when he says stupid shit okay
you want to this stupid shit okay
go the great molasses flood whoa also
known as the boston molasses disaster was
a disaster that occurred on january fifteenth
nineteen nineteen
i'm in the north end neighborhood of
boston massachusetts a large storage tank filled
with two point three million us gallons
of molasses weighing approximately thirteen thousand short
tons burst and the resultant wave of
molasses rushed through the streets rushed through
the street
eats and avenues storefronts and homes of
one thousand people killing twenty one and
injuring all the rich
the screams were heard for two towns
over
many of the gurgles of the people
who had inhaled the molasses were quote
chilling and scariest fuck okay i you
haven't started riffing yet as yeah let's
say long boring one
that was good okay scott
ah okay
i have to re random it because
i can't even pronounce this okay
randomizing here we go chandler c co
hagan
chandler c co hagan april twenty fourth
nineteen eighty nine to december nine nineteen
eighty five was an american architect who
designed around two hundred buildings in the
state of montana including the current montana
governor's residence he almost
ah yee oh he almost designed two
hundred and one
but he said ah too tired
yeah
okay cardboard say around two hundred buildings
or did make that it says around
two hundred building cardboard hundred and ninety
cardboard cardboard isn't a good cardboard i
wrote it
how do you randomize it you go
to ah you don't to do cardboard
you go to special colon random special
colon random yeah if you i think
if you search that or you know
i just did random yeah great okay
so how do i do okay so
boop i'm going to random okay because
i can't okay here we go
son's name william w hay
william when hey october twelve nineteen thirty
four to october twenty seven twenty twenty
two was an american geologist marine geologist
micropaleontology ist paleo oceanographer and paleo climatologist
as well as paleo doctor and paleo
piot pediatrician
ah
he is best known for his work
resulting in the discovery of many different
fish under the sea as well as
it's host within the hearts and minds
of the adults and children he worked
with
william when hay is best no
this discovery of something very much known
to man chocolate is yeah you discovered
something very much known to
it was the first person to turn
a cacao bean into a chocolate bar
thus resulting in them the mistakes created
the willy wonka universe
i so willy wonka was real this
is wild
unbeknownst to his family he did created
a new technology were exulting in the
making of skyscrapers
when his family found out they were
noticeably mad but allowed him to continue
his work as it was funding their
school payments as well as bills and
electricity academic career he received his b
s in biology and his m s
in misses
ah
anyway that's chances vs yoshi
an m s does alright this is
edie stewart steel jeanette eddie stewart steal
my october eighteen ninety july eight nineteen
eighty three was a british chemist she
submitted the first ph d thesis at
the university of st andrews and worked
there for the rest of her career
in several roles
including university this university assistant lecturer warden
of the women students residents secretary to
principal james irvine head butter face
and king lady
she was instrumental in creating soda pop
that everyone likes
she invented the rootbeer float before the
invention of rootbeer she also invented ice
cream by accident when she was trying
to
a new form of surgical lace
one of her students are arthur conan
doyle became the creator and destroyer of
sherlock
another of her students also created sherlock
holmes but after sir arthur conan doyle
these two students eventually met fell in
love and got married i guess due
to the ceremony it was eddie stewart
steel wikipedia pages don't have guessed it
was
she dressed up like a priest and
everybody thought it was so funny because
women were not priests in those days
they mostly were wives mothers and the
first ph d thesis submitters at the
university of st andrews eddie died of
complications due to a broken leg which
went off
all the way up to our brain
and the crack started at the foot
travel up the shin turned at the
knee
iphone yes pelvis stuff don't make any
comments and then every single rib thing
about being going from left to right
hit up the neck bones and then
skull
people could hear screams
she fell down and everyone came running
to help her but she waved them
off saying no no no everyone has
their time and this is my i
lived a good life i got to
do a thesis
and dress up like priests yeah that's
it i'll never forget any of you
and she looked at everyone's face for
a solid two minutes and then she
went back at the beginning and said
now tell me your names one by
one they did and she smiled and
said it's time for me to go
ah citation needed
and she flipped everyone saw her soul
rise up out of her body it
winked at everyone one by one and
then went up to heaven but then
came back down and said i missed
you and then winked at sir arthur
conan doyle
she is survived by her great grandchildren
who all look exactly like her and
according to some sound like her too
um and no more is known about
her accept that align exchange to heaven
alright so that was her wow so
that oh that yeah wow for sure
proud of all of our fun gaming
fun fun game fun game thanks robert
burt if you want to email us
to suggest a three tour or just
to tell us you love us you
can do so through to me i
say gmail dot com if you'd like
to call us and tell us you
love us or ask for some advice
or some shit call hag claims eight
that's the number eight imagine a hag
goal
ing around and killing eight people yeah
fun and if
it's an i tell you remember that
yeah and if you want to hear
ad-free episodes you can hear them at
stitcher premium or cb world and if
you want a three visit on the
twos on tuesdays we're re-releasing our previous
episodes that have been behind paywalls for
too many years we have been checking
reddit in the past week we have
not seen any votes in the poll
as to whether
oh yeah we were gonna be a
great reggie miller should be mad no
one has updated us either no one
is updated as yeah it's been we've
been checking radio silence for over a
week yeah so please do vote in
that poll and then up to yeah
and we love you just pick me
love you piss pigs we love you
lauren any last words any final words
really love you tom sorry i was
talking to me yeah alright bye
uh