sorry
our last episode season ever omega
simpsons season ever last time we're gonna
sit through the game
ah did you say it at all
or i said three canin you chose
like a boy to write trick that
was a loud as i could right
then that's like saying we're both going
to streak through the cafeteria and then
only i do well that was funny
though by the way you still put
your clothes back on no in the
house
spital cafeteria yes
nobody would last me begging you
yea yea
i lost my bag hang low
swing low sweet clause tea bag
finally orange women you know hey welcome
everybody to three dm my name is
paul my name is lauren my name
is scott and this is our final
episode isn't that wild final episode of
walls could be our final episode if
so they are not requested yeah make
many more yes and so
so and who does that who requests
that i think colin
how did people get a haul in
firth they call it first california because
it said well i guess it's an
impose cards that stuttering asshole
i was just a character what's in
real life he says that's a stammer
um yes gone for who doesn't oh
my god love actually he comes to
us and he says if you come
to a signal at night my strange
visitor yeah colin veitch strange oscar-nominated visitor
will you make more three two episodes
he needs it will you make more
freedom the clanking of chains yeah
he dresses up as a ghost for
some reason e digest facade cats the
rest
undigested potato he's making a reference to
a christmas carol little but i don't
i knew half of it i didn't
know the potato part so you knew
something was on digesting know i knew
that the good clanging of the chain
could be a blot of mustard
ah what does digested beef oh okay
what's a potato yes it's is it
a lie of potato xy of potato
of newt potatoes have eyes right okay
i'm gonna look up christmas carol potato
is look of christmas carol witch's brew
you may be and you redneck you
may
and yeah maybe you find me and
ryan and eddie yeah right you may
be an undigested bit of beef a
blot of mustard a crumb of cheese
crunchy a fragment of underdone potato rabbit
of outdoor dog but after their zero
easier as a punchline there's more of
gravy
e than gray about about you whatever
you are that's a burn for a
ghost ghost oh shit so i leave
some food a it's a convos holding
you covered in physical labor but the
ghost gets it the ghost knows what
the ghost knows to thank us just
just took it easy like on the
defensive now knows what he's talking about
oh my god it's almost time to
put
my halloween guys from paul that once
scared the hell out of me around
this time i really i was gonna
do it twitter i don't know if
it's gonna how how you doing guys
um paul's got me like these i
asked lord who are your halloween guys
and she told me yeah and i
got little figurines they're like they're like
funko pop adjacent but they're like little
statues with big heads and they're all
these horror characters or carrot sex work
there they're fours the whores and sluts
their famous sites working and i hope
i pushed them out and i look
good work and i um um um
there there's like ah who is it
there's like scarecrow who is i now
am more weight scarecrow from batman don't
know that mixing it up because it
looks like that is that one that
has the candy who's like little candyman
what the fuck are you not candy
bar you know that bag guy
who's like in a burlap sack and
has like a big lollipop no no
it's a scary movie but oh yard
this and it's a really witty yeah
yeah the strangers look up oh look
what am i supposed to look up
and it was a big law is
scary movie spy handy canned man burlap
sack lineup it's all gonna come back
zach lolly pop okay here we go
check is it from the movie tricks
from like trick or treat yeah fuckin
call and then there's like freddy krueger
and then there's lots scary movie as
a burlap sack head trick or treat
him so i saw someone dressed as
that walking down the street oh roundhill
just lesser but it wasn't tonawanda
and i was like near scary it's
really scary movers the kids me it's
a scary movie that's a killer shot
it's of that's a killer sort of
comedy too yeah it's kind of like
specify movie or like you know slapstick
be upi upi say swoopy for your
spaghetti monster to come out or it
wasn't long ago
two thousand and seven eighty yet it
was long ago i'm afraid curtis the
maniac will appear as the maniac i'm
scared til we hush now hush now
but those are my scariest decorations my
decorations tend to skew charming little cute
yeah yeah no they're still kind of
cute because they're like little heads were
doing look i love
love a little head i love it
a little head just a little small
amount to say there was there was
a comic that i knew and philly
so what do you remember when the
local news went from eleven pm to
ten pm all day that i whole
world chain wait eleven pm it used
to like ten when i was arriving
oh yeah i do between ten pm
and eleven pm simply don't understand okay
they moved the news fox eleven pm
to two what did you think he's
had a win from a leonardi eleven
pm and then it goes off am
the next day nineteen hour off to
sleep and they moved to do this
yeah yeah they moved wait so it
moved from
eleven like when i was a kid
local news was six and eleven and
we liked it that way and we
liked it we schedule our whole day
writer says like you're getting home from
work elevens like you should be asleep
dad yeah while you're watching the news
right now yeah because he finally has
a moment under age eleven too late
it's not too late when you consider
whipping the kids to bed
said then you have to wait for
your fucking wife to go to bed
and then it's like okay let's wow
my this is my domain my castle
it's the current day's events i could
watch the news i watched the fucking
news the other day for the first
time i watched live tv for the
first time in a long time now
and i watched something in a ten
pm and at eleven the news came
on
and i could not believe how far
it's fallen like the lead story was
coyote attacked a dog no backyard cause
they're doing news all damn day so
they just need whatever they can get
that and it was just like a
video that someone posted on twitter yeah
local news in chicago is a cross
i mean usually i mean back when
we were watching it was at least
someone got murdered somewhere yeah something like
that but now it's just like a
dog was attacked and then they did
all angles of it they want they
showed it they showed it and then
they like the the reporter went out
and talked to the woman like did
all you know all this just for
like they talked to the coyote yeah
i'm sorry you should interview
oh no sorry dude again um i'm
no one to interrupt you for i
appreciate that so what are you going
to say there is
because if not i have something i
was going to talk about so there
was a slow the local fox affiliate
their slogan was ah when they made
the move from they were the first
ones to do it i remember locally
they moved from eleven to ten and
their slogan was
does an hour of news an hour
ahead
more like you felt like you were
getting the jump you got ahead of
everyone yes but there was there was
a comedian vase very nice guy but
his he had a joke that was
about that that was dependent on his
speech pattern and is the only way
it worked he's like yeah a thick
accent just like
hey you know i'm watching the fox
news and they say they're going they're
gonna go earlier and there's they say
ah an hour news an hour ahead
and i'm thinking doesn't sound bad our
news and then we're here
so that you would be getting head
for an hour oh i got a
i chuckled a turtle which it works
if the phrase was an hour of
your an hour news hour ah
an hour news an hour of head
that what i mean would you like
an hour of head and wow work
would you watch an hour of news
if that meant you would get an
hour ahead
just can't have this
you can't yeah i can't unless i
bring it up if it comes out
of your brain it's okay huh not
in control of the phil foster say
it's disgusting by the way you are
the one who started when you said
a little head you're the one who's
you reacted as fast as i'm sure
but begged me to tell that story
don't forget it's on tape please please
weasels like i said ah and then
please break it down with one hour
talk about it please don't include me
just make it about that head-to-head is
for men and we i know but
but you were looking at him now
about him and i didn't want to
be a part of it okay
hey
why can i have some fun you
can do whatever you want ours too
much okay yeah what's that what's the
limit is high school that the doing
it i'm just kidding
so now you're in
ah
wait wait i you have something but
i also have something okay while i
have nothing i have one of our
most revered segments oh well i guess
weren't starbucks to reality recap yeah real
well because i sorted easy but this
is kind of
more this is lawrence topics notice as
high as reality reality work yeah it's
um what you had before we said
yeah because you were talking about that
coyote eating and talking that made me
think about how we might not have
been watching show now
two coyote easy one dog calling up
hour long
perfect for a blow job ah perfect
to watch but you're getting perfect for
a single blow job
ah where y bear too short for
a blow job i've always said that
or we're addicted positively addicted to the
show alone which has been pitched to
many times by mandzukic marry a lot
of people i know people have to
pitch you shows they're just telling me
oh you gotta watch this you gotta
watch this and it's come up enough
times then um some of their friends
mentioned
this is about going to lengthen our
kids like oh sloan it's called alone
a o and e and then these
people are survival and they go in
by themselves to get loans yes and
it's really hard because grandma oshie eating
with you
wow am i helping get this low
know they they go zit good boy
he'll say bag so we started with
season six because the internet so that
was like one of the most exciting
seasons don't you want to stay and
work up to it because now nothing
will match season six no we just
watched we're watching past that now basically
see season
six it's on hulu um but people
are surviving alone in the arctic and
for as long as they can and
you are they're all in different ways
like forty five minutes home before they
tap out know i mean these people
go a long time some people don't
last long because they're not naked they're
clothed and alone they are clothing alone
how clothed warm
no winter clothes but like underneath g
strings yeah they have g strings underneath
and tidied tassels
and it's so that's mandatory so you
only see that when there many women
there plus um but it's really great
and one person wins at the end
but they don't know if they're being
so it's a group of people they're
all in separate places they have no
idea what's going on with anyone else
and you're just trying to go as
long as we know
oh so do when the when the
second last person drops out do they
tell the first person like oh hey
that person dropped out or do they
just see how do they never tell
that they go no they don't make
them go too long they just go
right when that person leaves they go
over to germany i think it'd be
funny like someone drops out three days
in and then another twenty seven days
and honestly might be a key
couple days later because one of the
things that happens is they bring out
a member of their family to surprise
them and say like you won oh
and so i always surprised even though
there's multiple seasons while i've only seen
the ending of one season so i
don't know um but the surprise would
be you don't know that they're coming
because you don't know that you won
right so like you're hoping
and every day that that would happen
to you but it's alright it's probably
not going to so you just have
to keep working shooting beavers so fucking
nowhere on season nine being working shooting
beavers another inch obese canada somewhere in
season nine you think easy versus the
the balloon verse oh but the point
but the best part of the show
i just need to say one blown
he verts
that's what they would call
the world of the show is being
movie loading verse is a b movie
about baloney
i started watching that reason with the
first star theories that are bologna purse
but um will go way way way
so there
they're all people who are like really
good at doing this like they've they're
either like oh cheer up survival or
they've lived like this in different parts
of their life or whatever where they
have to hunt and so they only
have a few tools they have like
and wait and they can do it
they can do it and they have
chosen arrows sometimes they aren't but there
isn't there come on you can't it
can't be come on word yes when
it comes to the lord the truck
isn't there last episode you're trying to
squeeze me yeah yep get it all
out there um so anyhoo
it's kinda great that because like so
they're eating like this fucking stuff right
like oh don't kill kill this guy
kills like when you keep a mole
rat or something like something really gross
yeah yeah almost kevin slide now i'm
doing intentional it's a tiny cabin okay
kills a tiny kevin smith and he
cooks it up and he's like
he's like one of the most impressive
guys he makes this amazing like shelter
and he's like doing he's like he
looks like the guy from stranger things
who like takes in eleven i don't
really haven't seen that show beyond for
season one but you know what i'm
talking about yeah he's now in grammar
think your kinda looks like him he's
like just seems really like tough and
he's got it all together and he
eats this fucking like muskrat whatever and
then he's
literally two hours later like oh like
and it happens like it started to
become our catchphrase for the show is
oh my god like anytime someone eats
like this is so because you like
this because it's all good this is
so good and then an hour later
he's like dying of like food like
serious book parasites in his stomach so
he eats beaver for an hour and
what happens
yeah wow scott wow how dare yeah
well um no he so every single
person who eats something basically you you
start to think that this was gonna
happen every time because it happens a
lot they it doesn't always mean they
go home but like they feel so
ill that they're like dealing with this
and just watching them throw up for
like a long time she's crazy so
why are they getting so sick as
it been
cause there's sometimes there's stuff in there
like you can't guarantee that it's like
a clean animal like it's like they're
doing their best but they're not on
a farm yeah yeah these animals are
they're eating live stuff so and a
lot of times it goes well but
like they're eating squirrels and sugars can
they bring food if they want no
you're like here's my question for you
and how good you last not like
one yeah yeah yeah i think i
would be one outbreak and ten candy
bars i'd eat them all would be
my ten things that i'd bradford fucking
right i would i'm on one minute
i i can see myself actually bursting
into tears and being in being asked
to go home
oh and asking to you have to
tap out you have to call on
your walkie talkie yeah yeah and we'll
call you and they tell you to
go like as soon as the chopper
starts walking away i met tony jefferson
i don't have a tent to build
hence they have a tarp and had
to build their share tarp they make
it out of like clothes you know
they're amazing
and you didn't mention the tarp yeah
i'm staying i would do that twenty
one days they're all chopping wood and
making like log cabins and stuff it's
like amazing but um this season nine
the the season six was they have
to stay as long as they can
and they went five hundred thousand dollars
so yeah you mentioned that yeah it's
really good money eight months season nine
they
have oh it's for money tech a
day thing a hundred days who they
have to reach that point a person
to sixty guys i won't say but
the people who were there were not
lasting wow wow wow a hundred days
i can't do it how much should
do it i shared some really cool
to me okay bye wow
he called my bluff ah right well
lauren what's going on ah that's what
i'm rashi feel like scott you guys
miss me connected us and now we
have nothing exactly i everywhere did you
make me the fuck who got ah
it's new high struck myself why wish
him you too
you say not to you didn't say
that i always say not to drink
yourself yeah it seems like that's a
lot of work for everyone else except
you sorry but i did it but
do i have to say not to
do everything else that i know when
you do
okay let's see one don't don't be
gigantic oh good catch weight yeah it's
your next port of call gigantic
so does your reality ten are you
done with vanderpump yet we are i
am i am i noticed you sent
me out to say a video and
it seemed to be from the season
yes we we needed to season ten
we made it of course too first
we made it to a major milestone
that's a bitcoin yeah
which was not quite the way scott
delivered it in now not a great
discussion was i correct though that later
they would they they would make more
out of it in the know it's
always the same so it's the exact
same thing yeah they don't they didn't
like auto tune that is something coy
and no he he just goes that's
bitcoin
yeah i saw horrible i saw it
i didn't know what you were i
didn't know what that means because with
scott does he goes that's a bit
coy yeah he makes so much more
like the child catcher
so i'm wrong bad is that what
you're saying yeah you're wrong and bad
so we have we have finally we
know what scammed of all is thank
god because it's the only thing i
know so were you shocked when scanned
of all happened well obviously we were
going into it looking for signs of
what it would be right right which
they then had to edit where
you write or episodes of the show
where are you right i had two
possibilities and one of them was right
it was not specifically that person oh
so you're not doing that protecting anyone
knew it had to be mandible the
names i knew santa always involved probably
because of the name scandal that was
that was my first clue i was
like it can't be that easy yeah
and then it turned out it was
due your eyes but i um i
did call that he had an affair
that was like an off-camera affair did
you think i thought it would be
producers something i thought it was i
thought it was maybe somebody that we
had knots that somebody was not involved
in the show right right oh but
i knew there was something i knew
well i mean i thought it was
either that or that he fucked over
his business partner oh i remember somebody
they will never do that made a
thing that was like comparing it if
you don't watch the show it's like
if um obama was secretly having an
affair with joe biden that's how close
likewise like billy like if bill clinton
had an
affair with an intern or so oh
my god that would be insane
any journey was a great friend of
hillary clinton what if they were best
friends but anyway that that is bad
as the edible that is ah so
we are you're happy we're not completely
done we're halfway through congratulation reunion episode
and then the learns onto the third
then you'll be all caught wanting to
do yeah watch other tv
shows really yeah we really put the
time in we would call it good
job and we would say back to
work i watched a tv show that
i won't promote and i'll tell you
what it was later but i was
really enjoying it and then the ending
of the season was in the middle
of a climactic moment where which is
how the show had been working at
the end of every episode like oh
big thing happens then you want to
get clutching yeah
and just ended and i'm like i'm
never do you're not gonna you're not
gonna get another season or it's going
to be two years till i get
to see what happens next tv shows
enough enough with the trying to tease
of future me like some sort of
ending then i will want more yeah
i like still like just give me
some sort of like and then this
habit i think like early
the on in vanderpump there was either
like at the end of the second
or third season it definitely ended like
a series finale or there like it
doesn't look good for us and then
they've all worked yeah but like the
way they're reminiscing or whatever every third
day show does that now where it's
like they end the season with
not resolving the story they've been telling
yeah it's like resolve this one story
maybe give a hint or something like
right yeah have something like oh there's
more but this guy could go to
but but it's it's better when it's
more like justified seasons where it just
ends the story you're telling and then
like the next season you can pick
up on a new story i've never
seen justified oh it's so good in
this new
i'm seeing the new one yeah anyone's
grave what happened to shiver are you
alright you got a shiver like okay
we need to take a break because
i've got a shiver it's got a
blanket
okay we're back ah why did you
put a wallet in my mouth i
just i really want to make sure
that you weren't going to bite off
your tongue so i was not going
to either tickle in my ear is
there any issue let me take two
because i want to see time fly
fuck
so good
goddamn flooring or i learned texting because
i wasn't wouldn't be threesome is lauren
wasn't texting oh that's not true that's
not true at all i'm always extremely
present
yeah who cares who cares welcome back
to the show god welcome back we
i've just been looking at pictures of
sam from trick or treat that's his
name so that's his name oh guy
yeah well now when i put him
out i'll say hi sam i may
have mentioned this on the show before
but this is one of those nonmusical
earworm
terms that you get sometimes is a
friend of mine said out of nowhere
my friend buddy fitzpatrick and i think
i was told this on the show
before but it's all it's spooky season
is upon us it's utility spooky spooky
seasons pretty spooky just cute spooky is
that without it i think so yeah
i've never heard spooky it's a very
internet slang it's very internet it's giving
internet
if you're talking about josh the stagger
um yeah you might say that's spooky
it's creepy spoof it's just oops that
they can be pasta it's just boobies
begin it's a spooky spaghetti i understand
it's creepy but one time i started
buddy said out of nowhere ladies and
gentlemen mr freddie krueger
huh
because introducing
that was it it was like a
british accent whoa where what's the situation
minister ready
honestly that's what i was doing i
was on alone because i sometimes sometimes
they do like a little funny thing
to the camera i'm like all i'd
be doing is being like boise
happy to be doing
gentle i just don't i just show
you wouldn't be allowed to sing i
was reading a markey wow lady i
was reading a mark mcgrath interview wow
about big brother and of course you
know because of the copyright so so
paul you wouldn't be able to say
two minutes later you would even make
up your own coma hawk you can
make up your own songs you it's
true my will too i think
they may just come in in case
it has the same melodies and other
one that may just come in and
go don't know singing speaking of making
up your own songs yeah you have
a new birthday song
yes
so because we've all been waiting we
were sitting there waiting right i've opened
a chain restaurant yeah the first order
of business make our own birthdays yeah
you don't know the menu or any
thing like this it's sort of a
thing that people do a lot almost
like being like no one wants to
hear your dreams people like to go
like the happy birthday song is not
a good song it's links everyone's just
singing low notes don't you feel
like it's like a thing that people
are constantly saying no yes yeah yeah
one one of my favorite things about
happy by the way i like happy
birthday as long as it's not directed
at me okay it's always uncomfortable and
weird it's offensive because everybody that whoever
you want just don't say it to
me yeah exactly i don't want a
house we don't like happy birthday directed
at me but everyone's like ha be
huh but i like what is better
than when people start to high ah
that's the bad people
everybody's trying to get up there happy
guy yeah yeah it's great you need
to have one professional singer at every
party oh so here's the song
you know brian jordan alvarez okay this
has been ruining my life because it's
in my head so much it's him
but i love it well it's really
funny but i'm saying it so you
want a song will not as as
of this recording there have been so
many covers of it it has of
course the the song called sitting by
his character t j mac you know
that name is so funny
and i just wanna you know what
in case nobody's heard it
i just want to play it for
everybody here plug in plug it in
plug it in plug in every plug
you do see him see me through
yoshito sunbeam cne dijo placido iranian or
syrian you say
a wonderful thing to do because you'll
see ea seemingly yup we'll see those
londinium your head seating is the opposite
or hanging from my barbell sigue is
full big to go one thing to
say
something like i see the face duties
but you all seem nice actually glue
because it looks is kind of like
a knob is kind of like something
as it actually does c d
see the movie
the beagle placido
he has a snapchat filter
huh i love a good song that
please show me one thing currently and
i think maybe you posted today that
was like some somebody staring off into
space like he's been yeah for years
we don't know what the last thing
he saw was and then it was
just like hey time
and then my whole morning was just
that yeah i'm singing my god shop
so much he thinks it's the best
it's incredible it's hilarious it's incredible i've
heard it once i go mad when
things get in my head i go
mad absolutely mad do you go figure
your head
things speed songs matt has send us
math has send us and send us
many song new ah plays matt he
turned us many song you you made
a a request for oh no sounds
right oh my god people didn't so
i was looking for a seamless transition
into species songs
this is it guess what we don't
have access to these what you need
to request access to them so i
just want the accent i've just texted
him hey give us access to these
songs come on dude
producer it's it's it's a dropbox that
apparently they changed every day because i
was getting box or something so thanks
he sent me so ah yeah and
you're flying blind here yeah yeah if
we can't access dropbox i don't know
woman and what do i mean we're
look i don't want to give away
our location by
but mars were in a blimp on
mars but i will give away what
day it is it's a sunday afternoon
yeah matt better be by his computer
on sunday
flip at finding easy pass you might
be a mess you might be umass
if he has not been
for us now am i wrong or
did matt have some news let me
see yeah lawrence topics matt has news
i wow think i saw this in
a special lauren she got a man
bazooka doesn't take although he got engaged
i didn't engage this this was august
fourteenth i need to put a like
on it and i need to comment
on it right now ah mats engage
xd yeah yeah to us no to
the three light and see it so
he's engaged three of us yeah there's
ah he loves the uno solo show
i don't know that's the combination of
the three and he bought the will
of god yes he went to the
mall he got a composite made those
look like can you imagine how beautiful
we would be if we there was
a combination three of us yeah
we were at my gym today with
our daughter and one of our friends
was remarking there has never been like
a more clear combination of two people
wow with her like yeah you know
it's just like very very young a
lot of dry a lot of kids
is like oh you look so much
like your mom or that you look
so much like your dad it's just
a very like huh
yeah like maya hawke yeah exactly he's
more oomph no okay wrong she's more
oprah ah i didn't have ethan hawke
keep going we made it up
oh my gosh i'm gonna keep clicking
on this and and hope no we
made that one up that one was
fake nope didn't happen you fell false
stupid idiot
we got you you fool
yeah scott what's going on buddy okay
hey buddy okay i'm alright so you
went to my gym you run around
in little ball pit or what's going
on
yeah i don't even bring her anytime
yeah it just ain't the name of
the places my gym yeah okay i
know it should be our gym it's
a little gym for the baby yeah
who's the mai in this situation my
hawk it's my hawks gym my my
edgy my achieve it's mario's but um
it's me so you have a youtube
yeah
friends who signed up at the same
time as you intentionally always this a
coincidence you say well we all wish
that there were some friends that we
tested it out because you can take
two classes before sign up so we
tested it out at the same time
and then we went around telling other
friends hey tested out and so now
there's a big group of like five
of us say five couples and me
go there okay yeah yeah you just
like it's my gym yeah oh it's
you just gotta work up i guess
so mad he's fucking kids yeah just
like goofing around while you're on the
rowing machine hey it's dangerous like that
dow yeah yeah um yeah great so
yeah we went two days in a
row because we missed a couple of
weeks so we did
makeup class we've been two days in
a row she gets very excited yeah
yeah and it's like you now when
we go to the car i think
she knows we're going to my gym
because that's the only place we ever
go sometimes you go into the vet
yep you mentioned you have to make
it up such yeah scared everyone know
we have to amy lands expression wales
we have to start going to the
dentist now we talked to the des
artists don't get out to go actually
have a great dentist for you okay
um i've heard negative stories from other
places so i'll send the information if
you're because you have one good sort
of balance it out well so you
win please spite all these terribles no
no i went to i went to
the place that had a lot of
positive stories from people but they had
also like the group that i'm in
also recommended like this other place
that some people were saying hit or
miss with certain people and then my
friend went ahead to this other place
and had a horrible experience with her
child where they like pinning him down
and like wouldn't stop screaming and stuff
and her they was very traumatizing them
and i the place that i took
holly was delightful she had a great
time she talks about it all the
time really she wants to go back
she like thinks it's great
like it was like they have a
tv on the ceiling playing bluey as
so when the kids laying back that's
good and the parent holds the child
when i could just put a tv
on my own ceiling and play blues
but are you gonna clean your tv
week
um and then the dentist and his
wife it's like a husband wife and
they're like say kiss and make out
your singing songs the whole time and
like oh he's cleaning your teeth i
have a really funny video of it
but she's just kind of like haw
and i'm like she got a toy
at the end choose so happy oh
wow so yeah she she did not
like the first time we brushed your
teeth yeah and then
i showed her that i would do
it with my own brush and would
go brush fresh fresh fresh fresh fresh
and then she would smile and so
now she likes to she gets very
excited when it comes out and shavasana
she brushes her teeth yeah but so
i'm trying we're trying to do that
with dennis my mom is telling me
the other day that that i just
hated any dentist or doctor yeah or
anything but i i was wondering this
paul do you feel this way
i'm on the spot because we're we're
the same age this is the reason
i direct it might be the same
it might be the same thing i'm
only here what it is but i
feel a lot of literature when we
were kids and a lot of tv
shows like they had a lot of
stuff about the dentist and the doctor
like getting shots and getting cavities drilled
yeah and instilled like a fear of
these
most places yeah when really you're just
going to get like you know your
teeth cleaned or stuff that doesn't really
hurt all that much most of the
time yeah but i mean but then
as a kid you do get cavities
and then it fucking sucks yeah and
you know that i've never i actually
never had a cavity until i was
twenty seven or something budget for you
but
so why was i so afraid where
i was like my mom would have
to bribe me well some fifty thousand
dollars sharing tools in your mouth and
all that stuff it's kind of like
it's kind of creepy it sucks yeah
i don't like things i don't like
going yeah yeah ah but i um
i i remember we had a we
had a dent
just as a kid who did not
i remember him drilling my tube drill
baby drill and it hurt so much
because i don't think he gave anesthetic
oh i think maybe he was going
to and then maybe i fought against
having a needle put in my mouth
i don't know but i do remember
or maybe he did and it didn't
take i mean all i can remember
is the fucking
ng
crazy pain yeah of having my tooth
drilled into it's horrible it was insane
my mom had to get a root
canal and she was pregnant with me
so she couldn't have any oh no
never
she couldn't wait no became nine meg
it was essentially fuckin yeah rough yeah
that's rough yeah yeah wow how how
far along i don't know it's just
i guess just a story i've heard
that just was a way to make
you feel bad yeah yeah yeah and
it's works yeah every time you see
your mommy i'm so shy you
nah you're just like them like i
was like so so but holly liked
it so much she she talks about
it all the time she's always like
dentist and like we have like saucers
that we that they recommended that's the
thing is are they like the disposable
one yeah it's like a plastic so
they say that we have to start
doing this now i know which also
extremely like as a kid that coopers
like well you have to do it
because i won't be able to do
it and i'm like yeah i don't
know if i feel like if it
i just show her me doing it
once she'll go oh the den and
i don't know honestly i mean you
don't have to go to the dentist
but i just felt that it was
a really sounds like thanks here to
tour a lot of negative you don't
have to go to the dentist but
you can't say he will just have
like i mean this advice moms group
and like the stories of the dentist
can be
so horrible but like this one is
all positive and my experience really positive
so that's all i can say ok
here you go um it's because it
seemed early to me but then yes
we didn't take her till she was
too but because you just got this
new york times article the old gray
lady um it said it said ah
four months after they get their first
teeth
and emmys hat yeah well or by
layer um eye exam at a year
we haven't really but what you know
those videos of like the baby having
the glasses put on for the first
time yeah and then they always hearing
aid and they always smile yeah i
would love to see one where it's
like you're blue ugly like oh my
god
rip them off
i don't want to see this stupid
world yeah but it feels like a
lot of the stuff is happening a
lot earlier than i ever knew it
to maybe they always are recommending things
that early but people just didn't do
it i'm like when i was a
kid you didn't go to the dentist
till you were i lease in school
i feel like i feel like i
was going we were talking about that
with my mom and my mom you
know just all the stuff we're doing
and she's like yeah we never did
any of that and and you slept
in the crib with blankets yeah you
were on your tummy you know all
the and she goes and you're so
alive yeah i'm like yeah but the
stats weren't great out of luck yeah
she goes yeah you're right your dad's
the one of the guys he was
in vietnam with their baby died while
he was in vietnam
and he couldn't go back and all
this stuff so it's like yeah mom
babies fall vietnam i know well they
were that important ways that time also
president yeltsin president nixon
what if david bowie in that song
had done it president nixon impersonation lucasville
oh president nixon you think that's david
boies president nixon impression yeah probably why
what do you think david bowie's president
nixon brushing movie i'd like to do
an impression right now this is the
american president r-truth duke
it's like oh so blue group whoa
whoa whoa whoa fixing for all you
know how he says a duel the
song andy warhol he's like it's overhaul
war hole oh i guess i didn't
know that oh yes and i guess
i didn't know that during the intro
kruger
ladies and gentlemen mr freddie christa already
crew guys is playing up piano only
with his knives once again freddy krueger
duty is easier to play piano with
knives than it is with fingers yes
i would cheat code why wouldn't it
be yeah i mean i'm a sinner
yeah will also play
get in those cracks because most of
the really good notes are right in
between those key yeah if we are
able to get that because our fingers
are too fast yeah if you play
with forks you can play so many
more notes at the same time i
use a spoon because you'll want to
get every drop yeah obviously
oh man that is tagline that has
written something new link for the ono
songs yay and i click on it
and here they are are we ready
i'd love to hear here we go
this is by cole map stone coal
map stone i don't know what these
is are i don't know why
a
sweet god that was really good
so you're saying i'm saying yes i
said he wanted people to add music
to it yeah okay so it could
replace the current oh no no no
by the shangri laws oh okay got
it alright this is by ah sir
john this is too long johnny to
k aka john i don't know as
come
comments
uh that
back then no
uh wow
now imagine that being played over a
a toddler dropping ice cream cone yeah
yeah we have another one oh yeah
we have ah probably a few probably
five more
huh this is submitted by joe okay
this is by joe just ooh ooh
me
a honestly they'll be very funny on
video it's kind of flat
yes
that just made chatting look he kept
in a little bit of studio chatter
to chat yeah um a k now
this ah this is submitted by philip
elliott
oh
a shortly like that i like a
little higher pitched yeah yeah this is
submitted by loren loren you did oh
did i learn pro tools what
ever wow
uh that's
it's really unsettling i feel like you're
in the bathroom or something bad that
was exactly the phrase that was in
my mind unsettling and unconventional take my
lauren
this is submitted by zach
a
that's my favorite so far faced by
people you know or know hey i
have some more last one submitted by
matthew brown here we go
a yup you're white stocking so into
heeled shoes matthew brown by the way
because you're in like the marie antoinette
moment oh there you're the ranch for
that moment it's got
you're wearing white stockings on your heel
shoes
you know you're going like this
i like this and you have your
powdered wig yeah did you ever see
the great powdered wig it's a powdered
wig and you're wearing your white sockets
with your heel shoes and these are
what we call the marie-antoinette moments
hey all of those were great shows
are grand thank you so much good
job everyone happy brown by the way
parents medical a composed spoof for me
although some people are just hobbyists some
people yeah no that was ah a
premier national someday i would say anyway
yeah so we
little bit of this little bit of
that little better this was that was
delay how's your life those things so
much you everybody i'm paul do you
have a new song to to for
people to work on in-between seasons here
it's a good question um what's used
to i mean beyond that what i
hear a lot is you've got a
friend in me with any two creatures
together
either yeah yeah for years that song
that's kind of a new song um
just drop by she my living working
depending at them with a d day
then maybe they can do for you
what did they do to d v
d lee day-to-day do you do to
dude where do we go
oh yeah
guys
thanks
you know we heard that one i
have heard that one right i haven't
heard it it's cute so i guess
it's okay song when i put it
on holly's like e
scenes like phobic yeah yeah just she
screamed to music because she likes certain
she'll dance and she's really like shaking
her booty it's kind of funny thing
well thanks so much for those we're
gonna take a break and when we
come back the final three-tier of the
season and maybe ever yeah oh yeah
oh no oh no no no lord
don't go backwards oh no oh no
no no no no no no
oh no
we'll be right back
and we're back and very quickly here's
another song that people can work on
okay if they want to this is
to replace randy newman singing you've got
a friend in me not to replace
randy newman we love that randy's show
so i don't have that power i
don't have that power
but if i did let me be
using gone there would be a lot
of people that short people song what
about it was so good because from
nineteen so many wow i'm just wondering
what is obviously a joke but i'm
like yes why like i just am
curious why he's just like ah i
think it's a satirical take on like
we keep
finding new reasons to hate people oh
okay yes a satirical take on bigotry
in that it's ah just a random
thing it's it doesn't make any sense
to hate people for these for these
reasons yeah and he's saying what if
you just hated short people for being
short yes and he's right it didn't
it made people hate short people yeah
well he describe
leaves them with like beady eyes and
my yeah
they gotta turn a little voice is
going to be vp
bird
alright alright i think they have tiny
little cars that go turn low voice
going pee pee ah loving breaker it's
alright so this this is a song
that would replace you've got a friend
in me yes and you people would
put it retroactively into toy story as
well
i mean i i would like that
yeah but i'm not i'm not asking
me to go that far that's hard
to do but there was that kid
who edited toys twenty three three yeah
to make it look like the toys
died and showed it to himself that
kid day when anyone do you know
it's so funny you know you know
where the
the part in the middle of toy
story three where they're in the trash
compactor whenever they're about to burn up
a kid they rented it from blockbuster
whatever and then they watched it one
night and then the mom didn't have
time she's like well we'll all watch
it tomorrow so they edited it where
it just fades out right as they're
about to burn up
and it says direct reddit because to
credits directed by and then they filmed
her watching this and you hear the
mom say like was the end why
would they do that and they keep
bringing it up and they keep filming
and just like that was a weird
movie that they also diary what we
know stray have you seen this thing
that i posted
it's like girls asking their boyfriends how
often they think about the roman empire
somebody else i saw soils both so
funny to me because like all the
guys are like once a week
every day every day and now every
other day it makes me scared because
it's like you have i've been thinking
about the roman empire and i'm not
aware of it i have to ask
my dad i bet you he'll say
every day or the guy i just
feel like he's going to be everything
guys just saying yeah to seem to
seem none like they're not know like
they think about their like i thought
about yesterday i
i haven't thought about it and have
you you you don't think so because
maybe you have i mean maybe think
every time i think about jesus and
how much i love him and how
he died yeah and some stuff i
also think of aqueducts a lot charter
yeah of course and
i think i do think about rendering
unto caesar what is caesar's yeah of
course i like how he would dress
up like a beggar
well yeah a year yeah i do
that to me too yeah i dress
up like caesar dressing up his bag
yep i have a little crown yeah
and i put makeup over a stand
by the freeway
i call it single layer
so do sing the song alright so
this will be an original song that
people can use so it's it's like
if you have two babies that are
friends if you have a baby and
a dog that are friends it's like
always stadion an aunt if you have
if you have like an idea crazy
dog and a cat that yeah although
there are videos of kids saying hello
to bugs which is really funny to
mask yeah yeah
it's really it's adorable so sweet hi
so if you're having a little one
and two hats that are friends
fuck two hats next to each other
sentient hats know they don't have to
be sent in pixar hats sentient the
secret life of hats see what they
get up to when we're not around
well that's what we don't know and
we'll never know unless you turn on
camera on him what if we did
a parody of cats called hats and
it was all about the different types
of hats like a cowboy hat and
a beanie
oh i think we'd be baseball cap
uses terrible is what we did this
yes i think we'd be worse than
cats would it be like ted producers
are wearing a hat and they're representing
the hat or is it big hats
that move around on stage well that's
lives ville yeah yes welcome to lids
villains feel they were all big hatters
just to one-half that he fell into
know
they were all big hats they're all
big hat yeah i'm sorry what there
was a store last fill or lids
is what i'm using loop
so let's go backwards and that made
sense you and he said yeah like
yeah that was a joke like that's
leadville it's like oh yeah welcome to
lids ville where everything's hat forget it's
lids ville leadville was a student marty
croft joint to people that would talk
to charles nelson reilly that brought me
what oh hi ng h r puffin
and it was a cat goes into
a magic store there's a big giant
hat and a closet and he falls
into it and he gets transported to
lids feel right when you were gonna
say which is a world of people
of beings that are hats
so it's been like this idea has
been done with arms and legs do
you have eyes googly eyes how close
were you to finishing your screen pie
had written like ninety nine pages it
was really rough the last page ain't
one it's called capstone capstone yeah it
was called no cap
yeah and there were no giant hats
there were and i think you're safe
okay but
it's still derivative every character keeps managing
bear no giant hats anywhere about a
murder on a train yeah by the
way there are no giant hats last
train can i say that i will
those ah kenneth brown ah hercule poirot
movies yeah you're a you're happy to
take them over i will yeah
if he had starred similarly similarly moustaches
down now they're not gonna they're not
good but i will watch madonna have
you watched the new one because i
haven't seen it yet no one genius
thing was it looks like a horror
movie and then suddenly he shows up
with totally mustang and you're like oh
shit it's oh can you sing the
song that you're dancing yes you're okay
hey
i like you aid you lack be
weird just the bestest friends that ever
could be it's the people that say
we're not even the same species but
as a alike receive pcs well there
you go so let's put that through
the hander yeah
yeah so you're sponsored by reeses p
doesn't matter that you some people say
we're not the same speed yes yep
i'm not answering whether we are or
not i'm trying to say i like
reeses peace lauren exactly yeah it doesn't
matter what species i am i like
reeses peace so is the song yeah
exclusively then not for two human babies
know it could be because the people
who say they're not the same species
they're just insane people can't believe you
are talking about reeses pieces yes i
was on um your show yes steve
hawkins and my whole life i've been
bothered by the reeses pieces people but
right now i'm actually going what am
i what am i so upset about
that's cute it is cute you know
what do i care yeah well that's
cool are you up in some
it's so hard to lie low hard
why do i care life is so
hard we should all just get along
with each other not be annoyed by
anything there's so many worse things than
saying receive oh it's really bad even
though it's really clear that reese's it's
like nails are too fucking chore whereas
re and pcs are not tuned and
you have to be
ah a yeah to get that okay
but when you think about robert blake
shooting his wife is reeses pieces that
bad yes so honestly like those are
really different scenarios in which both things
are really bad if robert blake were
to shoot you for saying that i
would quit huh come on what about
out open humor who was like i
created the bob why i do it
well but sucks but if he said
reeses pieces i would buy like that's
kind of heute
thank you that's all of it yes
yeah my opinions are all over the
place um should we play game yeah
this game is called celebrity hunt we
haven't played it in a while i
have played in a while now the
way it works yeah is one person
will say a celebrities name we all
say hunt together because we're on the
hunt and the first question is first
person is forced
to say yes yeah yeah yeah knifepoint
yeah none of us want to do
it no no no okay we love
playing the game but nobody wants to
be the first person to start it's
really a tough position to be in
yeah but then the next person has
to say a celebrity that starts with
the last letter of the previous celebrity's
name that's right and it's a celebrity
not a fictional character is that true
that's true okay that is true i
don't think we've ever come across that
issue can we do can we do
fictional character oh why bitch why fish
oh shut up you can't actual counties
damage mister freddie krueger lee hello bitch
mister freddy krueger
so he's doing that much one movie
said hello bitch hello bitch he started
it that's really funny friends already a
little to be useful to follow them
i would like to count the the
b words don't trust the b in
a apartment twenty i would love to
count them in each movie and see
you
you know how they count the f
words of all time or just freddy
krueger just freddy krueger okay i would
love to see like stats on okay
and nightmare elm street he said at
once into three times you think that's
not look up bubble already i bet
it is let's see how many times
has freddie krueger first lifetime and then
individual times
xs has it's like ready baseball games
kruger looking up to a baseball game
bitch and i sit there with a
score card yeah oh here's this one
i will say here's a supercut of
him calling
but i want i want to hear
this
yeah
jesus i've been guarded by gay for
a long time ditch me just say
bitch
ah this fitch
twitter
why the problem
let me handle this his voice is
too deep
by the way his makeup
let me say wow did you make
it gets worse and worse with each
passing movie like they spent less time
on it that's it yeah alright i
liked it i would say if you're
making if you're making a supercut also
like let's balance the sound levels try
yeah please try bitch come on i
wanna just play for my friends thought
of being like loud quiet loud quiet
like by the end it look
ks like tommy lee jones' two-face levels
of makeup or just like slap something
on for five really familiar with that
at this time it's so time but
you know the story that they had
this elaborate makeup plan for tommy lee
jones like it was going to look
awesome yeah and then like on the
day he was like oh no you're
putting that shit on my face why
did and so they just
slaps like a plastic thing on his
face that took forty five minutes to
glue on that's wild they're like no
this is going to take four hours
he's like absolutely not it is it's
crazy he also let people spend like
half like six hours in the makeup
chair work for like two hours yeah
i'm like get like five hours taking
it off or whatever if you're a
klingon
on yeah and then you have to
go there and then all you get
are randy oh aura for rongi and
all you get to say is i
like goldbergs lock up yeah frankie are
like space choose please that's not okay
whatever you just said i'm just saying
it's not okay no it's not frankie
or not okay right
but the the depiction i mean the
eviction of the iraqi are not okay
um wait can we just go into
the safety of celebrity hon please celebrity
hunt so somebody will say a celebrity
than the next person has to say
the name of the celebrity that begins
with the last letter of the previously
named let's celebrity only have a second
well we drone the word hunt that's
right is there a rhythm to it
i don't remember no yeah keep moving
okay just let's just move gotta go
go go because there were there to
catch you don't get the ball go
there for five minutes before you throw
back that sounds fun do you wanna
play that sounds fun
yeah where one person holds the ball
for five minutes sounds so relaxing let's
do it alright ah who would like
to start i'm gonna start okay alright
and then which way we're going scott
clockwise clockwise yeah or the egg comes
out to pushing
anne hathaway hot yanni hoz adele du
z
the demons l ha and lorenzo lamas
huh sylvester stallone huh was eric ah
fuckin salts huh and zayn billy hi
can you really go backwards oh come
on yeah zero and x you can
you can john directly okay i'm just
saying right now that's really hard yeah
okay okay st billy okay yeah e
what's her name who plays ah maggie
on not maggie ah lian sampson yeah
yeah yeah yeah we can't do this
come on you're out huh and you
have to be out let's just keep
going right fine yeah
yasmin bleeds yeah guys harry anderson hud's
natalie wood hot ah doritos know what
the thrills yeah your rule is you
can never get out it's danny dirty
but you also don't do anyways sos
go
to any degree does
huh samantha morton whose high hunt she
was in broken arrow um niall horan
hot one direction um
nevada nevada nevada
anyway so no no no the hand
cream soap she's a mano name nevi
nebbiolo i don't get ya
you have to hear out here's a
professional wrestler out here you didn't even
know you're oh yeah hey she's one
of the bloggers i use our piece
to this gaze out let's you come
right out you can come back okay
i'll come out come you can come
back but not right now and i'll
come back now i turn where should
i go from no no no wage
it's just yeah h
yeah
ah herman's hermits of all of them
shannon mature huh
who's the door from raw housewives with
ah are are ah richard roundtree hush
elijah wood hut don rickles hon susan
sarandon hards nolan comma christopher
um ah robin williams hi guys stephanie
powers hunt soupy sanders oh my god
sail oh so close so weird to
hear you say that it didn't seem
right
that's how i lost between soupy sales
and colonel sanders exactly i would love
to see that were like syllable sales
to see the instead of making su
p made chicken he makes chicken and
instead of soup yeah which he did
make every day okay let's start over
so he's a wild day we're gonna
go freely is running counter i guess
are you talking about your diarrhea
my area's hard and publish yeah
alright here we go ready i'll start
evan dando huh ah oh i was
supposed to be me next oh going
the other way oh okay good yeah
good this deobandi that's what yeah that's
why i did it but i'm just
saying that so it's clear orlando bloom
huh and ah madison cawthorne
just
ah
therapy them oh yeah you ever been
ah okay ah
normal huh
oh karen j celebrity i don't purse
it but he's famous oh um um
lauren holly hud's eve santa lol raul
hides
tierra masu oh my fuck i'm just
saying you've desserts and things d we
shouldn't do this right before lunch time
so i always have tear me see
what i'm on your
what's wrong it's chairman
okay you're out again
ah and um okay right well you
dug up danny de vito can't oliver
says hudson hunt um neil de grasse
tyson hunch ah nick multi hunt evan
rachel wood huh
hans die yan von furstenberg behind gregory
hines huns stanley and lee hans um
ah grr right
huh
tina turner hides robin wright penn huh
um ah and they may and natalie
imbruglia hards anthony anderson high twenty ends
we always run in
to this um nicholas j heinz yvonne
orji hon signs guy she's from insecure
yeah man huh and ah is the
iggy azalea hides ah
ah anna paquin huh
orange sorry not a neil's a lot
of neil armstrong hines gragg
greg greg greg greg greg greg greg
coma clark berlanti greg best buddy let
me use somebody's somebody yeah yeah slip
answer the sure slippery but greg berlin
ah um i le fischer heinz rita
radner huh
robert redford high and diane keaton ha
and na na na na na na
na na na na na na na
nia long huh odds
gina gershon huh
nia vardalos signed sam shepherd hans de
game judi dench huns helen hunt huh
that's weird yeah oh yeah yeah you
won because you said hello john's yeah
no way there's no way out
out of us no way out there's
no way kind of gone forever and
if you'd like since three-tier right to
three each no right to three m
usa at gmail dot com and if
you'd like to call us leave us
a voicemail ask us for advice give
us a conversational prompt or just compliment
us you can call us at hag
claims eight
it's great it's great and um paul
dave live shows coming up man do
i ever yeah ah wonder people hearing
this thursday thursday tonight the neighborhood listen
live we're doing a dynasty typewriter it's
going to be in-person and live streamed
seven thirty pm pacific
ic me nicole parker brett morris and
our special guest metro johari it's gonna
be a lot of fun i can't
wait we're going to be doing for
the first time we're gonna be doing
the show in costume whoa created to
look like what my character like are
you going to be sam from trick
or we're all gonna be sam from
one trick or treat from trick r
treat
and only getting people killed over your
face exactly and at the end of
the night we take your bags everyone
is like has guessed which one is
which yeah yeah and if you guessed
correctly you win the bags have been
on our heads for wow hour plus
free covert free gold everyway
so that's so that's this thursday then
october ninth wow let me tell you
something official thing is happening that's like
a monday i think so i do
you know the days ah because some
i know something's happening on the seven
okay oh there he goes that's how
you figured it out
um he figured it up now um
um it out super ego and wild
horses are once again joining forces we're
going to do a show that we
were going to do right before lockdown
yeah and it is an improvised murder
mystery and it's called whom has done
this going to be real
the exciting this will also be live
in person and live streamed to the
world yes you can get all the
details at paul f tompkins dot com
slash live including variety opiate in brooklyn
late shows still some tickets left but
they're going quickly nice um you know
i'm doing much a random shows lately
you just have to follow
my instagram to see what they are
because i don't know if type of
meal dome piece um but i will
say my friend or marine is on
tour on the east coast this fall
and she's got a show coming up
in philly which i wanted to promote
it's in october you have to go
to her page to find out what
the heck that is but she's really
funny and you should go see her
she's doing new york dates
a couple other towns but i know
philly is coming up soon okay it
was one where you were you were
targeting that one specific yeah yeah yeah
it's coming up it's coming coming up
going oh yeah yeah i've nothing oh
come on what about all your other
podcasts well i started was adam scott
and i started the springsteen show right
so you can listen to that where
it's called use springing springsteen on my
beam what was the face you made
when you said that title do you
like it or you don't like ah
half and half did you guys have
i mean you have to vote on
these right you have to yeah unfortunately
we each have one vote in the
nose that true and we're always tied
you know what i'll just say because
i looked it up yards at union
hall nine twenty
one she's philadelphia city winery ten twelve
city winery and she's says maryland and
october thirteenth and city winery in boston
on october eighteen the whole city winery
many cities why didn't she do it
in new york city winery yeah i
mean hall and city winery hey can
you call arden
until her to switch yeah anyway just
promoting my friend that's very nice and
something i'm not doing that oh no
you know although i do want to
promote arden marine this in general just
generally i saw hurry and what women
want the other day really yeah so
yeah i i haven't seen that since
i've known her so oh okay oh
sure yeah
don't you yeah watch the whole thing
just for her one line yeah i'd
love to what does that mean she
she one of the people who's like
thinking something that he can hear yeah
i think so i go find our
oscar
well that's the that's gonna do it
for us for this episode of threesome
can you or the season two hopefully
it's not the series finale it better
not be and if it is um
well i'll miss amazon at least a
plug for army marine yeah i know
it's not random but
yeah we finally fulfilled our purpose yeah
yeah but i was done promoting my
own things to the point now where
i must promote others yeah must promote
others map so you understand the rules
if you want the show to continue
you have to send physical postcards to
call an anderson yeah he loves them
by the way who wouldn't i would
love to get a bunch of physical
postgame my god not really
ah no no no no no no
no no no no oh no oh
yeah you fred dough with different everybody's
there's that we get along he above
friend and everyone else kid go to
hell
that's what i say go to hell
hell hell everybody go to hell hell
hell if you're not my real goal
to hill hill hill lateral light you
go to hill nice
a okay we'll see you next time
hi
uh