anyway m g o um so not
it's a historical figure i don't feel
like i guessed and i have one
right now that i've been mulling over
i have one too okay mother goose
did we ever decide if it was
real people or not well i don't
know it's my first i think it
could know it could be fictional characters
well here's the thing one clue that
was very interesting was
we asked if the person was involved
in a war and he kind of
waited little she was on that yeah
spineless i'm not very good at um
historical figures yeah no no no no
yeah yeah you're not very good at
historical figures yeah yeah yeah no no
go ahead go ahead you like being
friends with them totally yeah yeah go
ahead yeah
okay i'll talk to you later alright
love you but hey mikhail gorbachev q
hey it was a business i guess
it was a telemarketer mikhail gorbachev um
no what if i said mikhail gorbachev
then i don't know i know it's
not me
mikhail gorbachev what that was the best
answer we had i swear ah sorry
guys do you give up in no
one more when you work well hey
we need more shock wave i'll cook
while huh question is this person did
yeah oh yeah this person historical figure
yes is this person american now
no sir is this person british i
know because this person mahatma gandhi yeah
i feel sad
oh
ah gandhi oh ma begun no three
to mahatma gandhi got it finally i
would say to him if i met
him it only took a week sorry
guys sorry i yeah sorry news entertainment
weekly they wanted to get a subscription
before they stop
i'm going weekly they're just like right
you want to get our last few
really oh wait they're going what are
they going monthly going monthly did you
not know this i hadn't known zero
this is very true little young wagner
why on earth would they be weekly
in a day and age with the
internet right ah they are going monthly
but they're still calling it entertainment weekly
it's very confusing anyway welcome to
entertainment entertainment seen the news i'm freedom
paul f stockman
i'm lapping flappy flappy give me that
love love it
yeah maybe not
nice i like laughing taffy okay great
song i like toasty chair just saying
like bread and butter
hi guys what's cracking hi great cheese
crack aleck with his crack a whacking
with all of you that was an
on again so did you feel bad
when you had to leave or did
you not care i like this i
like the mining questioning how did you
feel about us yeah were you worried
like well i've been here awhile i
why do you keep sl
lightly taking your glasses because they're
my headphones are making them crush my
skull and so i was like like
trying to take them above the headphones
and every day i have been yeah
ever since the tv show took classes
every day well you know what why
i said it like that because i
don't know okay because like i was
like i feel like i don't know
that answer
or yet i yeah all the time
i'm supposed to yeah okay i feel
like your default has been glasses lately
it had yes so what happens is
default has been glasses i was i
was thinking your default has been glasses
i would say your de apostrophe fault
default i was on the show i
was on the tv show grace the
tv shows around the thing we all
we all know guys the tv show
now like there have been many many
programs but none of them still only
wine but yeah like how many men
behave done please use the city um
it's and so for five years so
for the last three seasons of it
we worked every trees and freezing
yes and you worked every day we
worked every day and never never ever
even got like christmas vacations off we
got the weekends up but so i
couldn't go to i couldn't go to
doctors and stuff so i went for
three years without going to a dentist
or a doctor oh i remember this
time members about you arrive for this
i have a problem
with it yeah because a you're the
boss be your springsteen you go to
saturday bed they make hours for the
status quo but you know like i
want to sleep in yeah when you're
doing like bartleby the scrivener i would
rather not i don't think i would
prefer not to burden the screener like
an
actual thing or is it just a
reference people or is it a kauffman
you can't use to be a thing
and now it's just just everything just
if you register
so anyway i was on the show
and i would i would be looking
at my phone and i noticed i
would have it my my my arm
extended all the way out we're taking
a selfie each ah to to be
able to read it we had two
different interpretation millennials think a selfie
gen x called the old man
but i i've never thought of myself
as a glasses person necessarily but i
got them and they were like yeah
you should wear these everyday i was
like that with black chicks
ah robert de niro oh robert
um you know my prescription is so
bad
how bad is ah she gestured to
us like aren't you gonna follow this
up bad is that i feel but
i can't really wear my glasses when
i go out in the world because
a they magnify my face in a
weird way and b i can't see
peripherally and so it's very stressful i
got more tired when do you wear
it then just run home
like when i go to like when
i'm done for the day when nothing's
going to sneak up on yeah and
you're approved for oh yeah on wow
when i'm are you are you like
a blind person where you know the
steps of how to get around yeah
and i really do i can do
a lot i can actually remember where
i put something and then grab it
like but i can't see she's she's
moving this out staring blankly
as if she's portraying a blind person
in a movie yeah and grab something
like ideal food to someone watching me
i might look like i know what
i'm doing but i'm actually going i
think my glasses over there then i
like doom and then they are wow
it's really that much yeah but just
a blur yeah so you're you had
to be like damn you can't see
us right now basically i have contacts
oh i didn't know that ticks down
wow would i ever do anything like
if i was i wouldn't see your
prescription movie says right now your prescription
is bad enough but for the context
you can see peripherally is that okay
because they cover the
paul they cover the balls oh i
can't get contracts because because i need
different prescriptions for far away and close
so okay grover
grover cleveland the numbers the cleveland show
over cleveland the muppet from the cleveland
show from the cleveland show the president
of the united states
our american debt
i don't know what grover has to
do with he did a very funny
and memorable ah demonstration of near and
far oh yes santo near back in
eau claire
let's listen to a six minute clip
of this now grover i understand you
wrote a clip
you look to me like you do
a grover i couldn't even tell you
what he sounds like i was honestly
trying to be johnny carson version
this he's very grover sounds like huh
no that's yoda like an amped up
yoda doing my duty huh oh fozzie
bear that's what i'm doing yes that's
fuzzy bay wow waka waka huh that's
good i'm kermit the role i'm this
is pigs come to the fr
gugu play yahoo
yeah hi ho hi ho cuba the
full goo
wait so if you can do a
yoda you can do a miss piggy
hey if you could doing yoga you
could do miss piggy is that true
though oh do you ride hello there
hello there hello yeah sitting down my
i hate it i know i the
way you can do here backwards it's
annoying it's
very annoying it's syntax like yeah you
know when you in other languages syntax
is different yeah but then he's he's
nine hundred years old he should have
grasped he's the only one show of
the jedi down solely didn't like eventually
yeah everyone else so if you can
do if you can do yoda yeah
how far away is
is it from miss piggies is this
is not the hello me yeah i
guess it's kind of the same right
yeah hi me oh my
what is behind me you guys are
looking at a tv spot behind groupon
ad starring tiffany
she lie greg why why why oh
i was snowy i wanna hear grover's
voice this is yours here our team
grover serves a burger oh oh okay
so that's franco's to o grove on
a second kevin was happening did you
request this no i said playing near
and far went twenty mi
if i'm to blame he's typing something
what is happening right now we're just
watching grover here's the clip that'll explain
your notion
or you don't know what it is
so give a tutorial on the grover
voice oh grover you are spell grover
you about very good yeah how how
does he keep this up in fact
i guess that's what it sounds like
it's like alex frank sounds like myself
so when he was directing butterfinger no
i think i'm sold remember when the
lewis brothers
i see
i didn't know what that reverence was
and i was alone when i was
why are you imagining frank oz saying
why because tom sawyer yeah thanks you've
ruined paul and he okay prophylactic when
i was a kid i had no
idea what he was talking about right
i saw that when because he said
prophylactic and yoda and yoda so no
i didn't know what kind of was
either okay
what do you think economy is now
i think it's boo same stone i
think it's too loose
with a big empty hall see this
loose blue with a big zoo how
would you describe me to tell you
why them
it's
we're
yeah florida and i are very full
of beans you guys are very loosely
were very very loose like really today
yeah very silly
so when you were a kid you
you you saw the blues brothers repeatedly
this rated r movie now i saw
it in the theater you did yes
yes yes yes okay theater my dad
with whom see in the theater with
my daddy with your daddy and and
he was a blues brothers fan or
he was a blues fan know he
was a fan of brother i wanted
to see this film i requested to
see this okay and he
took me to see this movie
three my vocal work i wanted to
see this i want you to see
this film i requested to see this
film he took me to see this
film and curtin
so and how did he feel about
it because as i recall that movie
has curse words and did he care
about the question less indoors which i'm
again not a big fan of ah
who knows what that guy felt about
anything ah yes so the note didn't
talk about it afterwards didn't was there
wasn't choice cism prophylactic one thing that
my debt
ah just like oh um the one
thing my dad and i kind of
had a bond over was comedy oh
okay and we used to watch together
the um when sctv was on late
night on fridays right at like twelve
thirty those ninety minute episodes we walk
sales together in the kitchen yeah and
we would laugh
and make pasta for ethanol no concurrently
and who who got on the air
first
s l was on there so it
was only then they were like let's
try canadian style yeah well a lot
of people came from second city dashboards
can be yeah snell became so popular
like a lot of the initial cast
came from us from the second city
up in canada and so then they
were like well let's make our own
show and then em
vc picked it up for those nine
eventually yeah but well yeah but they
did episodes and they did like half
hour shows in the seventy s that
i remember watching on p b s
yeah oh yeah the public broadcasting severe
network spherion know people for free she
has had monty python on it whoa
yeah wow i've always seen like
too many python sketches which one's fucking
fucking cheese shah know if the spanish
inquisition one is merriman horses maybe you
marry your sound effects oh you saw
the money the holy grail why didn't
i see that i saw clip okay
okay fine i want to make it
clear i don't know what lashing out
at about
simply understand yourself simply you understand yourself
he said oh da she doesn't understand
yourself
what do you write them an urgent
message on that banana spells writing in
a marker on this banana like it
was a fervency so what's the other
one you saw it that's it that's
how i remember i don't even know
i guess it was a movie then
so do you think that you should
watch any or were you like this
never really cared
but this is a bunch of dudes
year into female como women's comedy first
of all i mean i'm funny screaming
again
go ahead and scream it
this time you convinced me okay yeah
that was the one um no i
just never really cared it looked dusty
it looked um uninviting good tape you
were yeah like it looks like you
know like like the quality of the
film it was like you i pristina
things and ten adp not
not necessarily i just think as a
kid no one was saying like this
is so funny got to see that
nobody was saying that point you know
like yeah i feel people who love
money python like my older brother loveday
there's always some story right yeah i
didn't like and because i wasn't a
dude i wasn't seeking it out do
you always funny is that i when
i found it there was not
discovered it well you're the person in
the ancient tomb who on buried and
occurs
and i'm crashing generating machine is always
talking about dead parents i mean um
i don't remember talking about it with
the only friend that i remember was
a friend in high school who shared
an affinity for it and we ended
up being a comedy act together oh
right that's right you're gonna do oac
but we were very influenced by my
python his name was rick roman
interesting he's dead now i'm sorry wheel
did you do know then you're alright
i thought i had to leave
finally the first reason to say i'm
sorry
the first anytime anyone does the first
verse sorry it always means oh interesting
i know lynch a great podcast i
don't need your grip zero
no called um could you call earning
a podcast serial like c r e
ellenton horatio sanz did i was on
an episode oh ah the serial podcast
um no but it was about i
was like a parody of that i
guess ok i was in his basement
for a reason i saw his army
hi there yeah i was like what
the fuck is going on here was
the name of his studio basement studio
he called it something i never was
good here with the bro bro bro
bro robert okay that's very ill zigzag
says bro bro um muss because the
title
ziggy says roby
as well but early contender for sure
for the podcast listened to was called
to live and die in la have
you listened to this i've heard of
it i've not heard it really good
and there's twelve episodes plus a bonus
one that was about people who've died
in law or live one story because
they didn't switch off they did both
get yourself a man who to upi
is about this woman who was
i'm twenty five and she was an
aspiring actress in l a last year
she went missing she lived last year
she lives in hollywood she's just like
going to acting classes she lived in
hollywood i'm just saying it was right
at our doorstep to understand you could
walk past her on the street yeah
tackling i know it's something else alone
it's good to live and live it
die
it was such pride my man could
live and die it's a bunch of
people with corpses
there's still with them
that's the one requirement man they can't
live anymore so wait so this woman
would pass you on the street no
i'm just saying she did pass me
on the street possible wanted to pass
me on the streets all she wanted
so she's our warmup knows she couldn't
pass her because she wanted to pass
me on the street she did pass
me on the street and curtin um
she died so um stop laughing but
no the podcast is so interesting because
it's one went missing she was having
a relationship with this other guy from
her acting class
who was engaged to someone else so
they were having an affair your scolari
hit no no this is his name
was shit and demand wilson spots chris
spots spots or crispy yohannes z oh
god it's worse than my thing yeah
but you'll find out more about his
name if you listen but me in
the spotlight yeah that's what i always
said i'm ready to play they both
met in this acting class and then
he was cheating on his fiance with
her whenever it's hot and then she
goes missing it's pretty odd so basically
the police are on the hunt you
know they're on the case but they
don't really get that thorough with it
and this journalist who's making the podcast
goes out of his way
way to like work with a private
investigator to try to solve the mystery
and he called it he does yeah
and it's spots um well no i'm
not telling you what this what the
dude takes many twists and turns but
it's spot i'm not going to tell
you what happens is this guy truly
neil strauss thing i don't know what
that is is he did he nor
laura dope
play dough did he killer who is
neil's house was the guy who um
wrote that book the game about oh
yeah this reason oh the thing that
idea oh the game yeah yeah yeah
but no anyway
every day there was a show i
was told about ah an argument that
happened in a text thread where people
were bagging on neil strauss the author
of the game and then someone thought
that it was the the movie the
game like why are we so bad
at writing the game
yeah i liked that movie wow neil
strauss's a murderer that's so not not
that's not right but anyway investigators listen
do you like stuff like that i
don't typically i barely like listening to
you talk about well i'm not as
interesting as the honestly i feel like
serial turned me off
to those kinds of but here's the
two things that i've listened to in
that vein yeah serial which was so
disappointing i know that was such a
bummer this one's not just pointing early
where it's like when they kind of
realised they weren't gonna wrap it up
and they're like i think also on
the third episode they were asking for
donations i know um and then the
other one was you must away with
this people
donate to us if they like yeah
i'll take please donate time you donated
to serial donate an equal amount yes
yes and that sounds fair doesn't it
presence yes and present so an equal
amount plus a present and that way
one of us will murder one of
the other people who would you murder
out of the three of us if
i had to kill one of you
and fuck and marry yeah i'd fuck
marry myself and i'll kill you
i tell myself oh i can kill
both of you i couldn't just kill
one of us god hooper and then
fucking yell fucking psycho oh well i
don't typically like true crime i don't
like i say big crime
i like ok gone you are you
serious you must remember this know who
i've listened to that what's that it's
it's hard to describe it's it's ah
this person who does these deep kind
of deep dives on different historical events
um are they all los angeles i'm
not sure but they're the one i
listened to on a road trip was
about the the manson family murders and
the the host has ah ah ah
ah ah sort of peculiar way of
speaking she over enunciate as i've sometimes
and then sometimes not like there are
certain things that she says to crisply
and clearly like no one says that
word that very often sounds like it's
take fourteen yes but then she also
kept saying unfortunately
ah she she does a ah d's
for tea thing always drives me crazy
that's for teasing i don't know
i don't know why it bothers me
so much no i don't mean really
bothers me and there was a give
an example there was there was a
motorcycle gang that came up in the
story again and again whose name was
the straight satans oh god and she
kept straight saying straight satans and it
was driving me if you're gonna see
straight here
gonna say yeah exactly and whatever exactly
but yeah people say important it drives
oh yeah important important yeah important crazy
were taken down other podcasters i love
it ivanka trump is important joshua yes
she didn't have so much other good
showing she's so it's a one flaw
i know i don't like
i don't like true crime i like
funny fake crimes like like funny fake
crime like bajirao man steals a trampoline
and used it to get away in
focus crime
he jumps on a trampoline to get
out and he steals trampling then he
uses it to get away from everyone
he liked bounces away i'm in between
i likely ms but with a laugh
track like
what's going on with your wrist someone
calling me my phone tells me oh
my thought my my watch oh yeah
well my fan call is that from
the apple company or did you go
with nah see saying i gotta fly
cheeky love the band
why shuffle what do you mean you
guys started to get you guys aren't
bad you're not watching people you're not
watched people i only had one for
a while in fact i think i've
been given like three or four i
tried to go on for a bit
i got a very small delicate watch
and loved it but
eventually it was like it's we're not
a man am i going to look
at my wrist already i'll never gonna
look at it second of all if
you say you're not gonna look at
it every day i'm not gonna i'm
not going to wear it everywhere every
day but i'm also not going to
be someone who's like what time is
it one of those she just stuck
out her arm like the most like
she was a scarecrow or what time
is it the most awkward way of
looking at a risk
stephanie allen has a really great like
big watch chunky well yeah that's like
but it's like big like i don't
even like gleba believe practically let me
pray cooldown remaining wild horses let me
guess who's a watch and who's not
oh yeah you'll get it and play
fuck marry kill okay erin not marry
yeah fuck
mary mary yeah so you'd fuck marry
yeah i mean a good marriage he
kill the other threads i held
fuck mary look mary holland
maybe blush let's play fuck marry holland
to stop it looks like this how
did i ruin this
when you fuck who you marry and
and you holly you it ruined me
okay i say aaron no watch you're
gonna guess them all you're going to
go one by one i'm gonna go
one by one you're correct marry she's
the wildcard oh yeah
i'm gonna say she's just sometimes exactly
oh and then stephanie obviously watch all
the time because of that big chunky
wash she looks cool and it's and
it's it looks cool i'm sure it's
cool it's so cool on her yeah
she she's peering out from inside of
it but i feel like i could
never pull it off it's a big
bowl
lol you know look i don't know
i don't see you as a watch
person i think that like the day
you wear watches like you start walking
ooh you know why because time is
meaningless to me yeah ah janie is
not a watch person geez na was
early in our relationship i bought her
it took me two watches to realize
oh you know what i bought a
watch gift is so intense yeah i
bought i love watches i definitely watch
it took me two purses to figure
out you should never buy a purse
for two that's such a hard choice
i was like oh here's a purse
you'll enjoy it i got the the
most oh we can't even imagine what
worries you would have pegged we know
this style even though
i want to see it you want
to like i mean wanna see twenty
years ago i know you described no
idea but it was just oh i
couldn't even tell you no idea you
were like cute but that's the thing
as i look at the purse i
bought yeah and i look at the
per she bought i'm like hey your
what's the fuck i do a lot
if you're in high school everybody complaining
about
come on there are such persons are
jealous much
sick sick yeah you did it when
she was in high school no i
know i'm saying sick um that if
you had not even close not even
close for years thirty record it's not
even close no wait one year later
when she was a college crowd knows
like
five years our she was five years
after her freshman year yeah thank you
ah
so five years after she started high
school is not bad that's a long
that's half a decade that's sick
what is says you are forty nine
come on alright let's take a break
alright bye
alright hello okay bye great hello hi
hi welcome back guys can i share
a thought with you yeah yeah i
was gonna i was gonna put it
on the text thread i was like
no i'm going to tell these guys
in person and love automatic the text
thread i gotta say that's a whole
other show that could be a show
is actually show you guys if you
could always have the text thread you
guys if you would lose your you
remember though
when you were on a text thread
of eight of us who all went
away together yeah and the month probably
that everyone was just doing stickers my
god i know it was it was
so psychedelic i lie love no hate
to say yeah yeah like anyone with
texting thing who just be covered with
five stickers of varying just like pulsating
worms
try to put on down disturb so
that i wasn't getting an update every
time that i check back in and
there will be times where i will
go i will be like in a
meeting for a half hour and i
will look at my phone and there
will be eighty three ten yeah from
all of you yeah and they're all
garbage meaning yes garbage yeah
anyway tell me that i look
really good girl fun fun communication um
fun communications with friends ah i don't
remember what made me think this but
i realized ah that well
i'm shy to say ah don't be
shy hello he's peeking up from miami
up in between my fingers i kid
lucky when hit in the corner pull
back back um that we're going to
know each other when we're old wow
i realized today that i've known you
guys a lot longer than i even
realized how long i think i may
know in twenty third teens so twenty
twelve maybe maybe not the year we
make contact
i feel like maybe yeah maybe yeah
something like that something like seven years
but like six or seven because i
was actually thinking about that well oh
shit that wilco or um what's it
called jeff tweedy party oh yeah the
jeff tweedy party we went to a
private concert but jeff tweedy did at
he taught a toy
puta thinking that twenty twenty five um
it was the singer sylvester invited yeah
well yeah what did he say your
sister must be dead sylvester saying get
real is that right shelvin look it
up semester the cat had a song
no no a singer named sylvester what
is sylvester's
biggest hit his absolute biggest hit and
please tell us in mind forum do
not get on like i don't think
i've ever heard of siri what is
sylvester's biggest hit
it's serious girl duet with usher is
by r kelly
that's not at all you have like
an art kelly filter where you're always
looking for r kelly news
do you try to get another million
what do you typically use siri for
i've never used it what ah
ever ever use it for paul what
are use what for theory do you
want to use it for a lot
is dictation in the car ah like
on a text yes so i don't
touch my phone overmuch i used alexa
because we got an echo died like
two months ago so i've used that
occasion hope this makes people's alexis come
to life if they're listening without headphones
alexa know but too many people their
series go off while they're filming show
alexa play the national anthem loud
i like sex attorney tom volume up
fifty percent i realized i kind of
only use siri to ask how tall
actors are
and like all during and are you
asked are you asking because you want
to see how your body would be
next to there like i always want
to guess we i guess that is
part of it but like i like
how when i'm like wait you were
if you were at a premiere with
them yeah how's the sylvester yeah this
is you make me feel oh you
make me feel the epilogue oh right
i guess this is where they look
at me feel mighty real that's yeah
hell the people to die during the
making of the song he was a
disco singer the the
the upbeat version of this is is
a great song so how taller actors
these days i mean they're all five
eight what are you i'm five ten
no serious how tall are actors
siri how tall is lauren lacoste
let's find out siri how tall is
loren lapis
i found this on the web oh
what she bagley know wikipedia is the
first hit siri how tall is paul
f tompkins
i found this on the west finding
a way on the way here you
fucking cunt okay wait yes siri i
can type i found your entire biography
on some weird you wrote away all
of it jay listen this is you
right buyers john hi benjamin franklin this
is a biography of joy baba ki
okay i made a lotta guys this
is on a website called the hotline
dot com yet like i don't even
know if it ever says you're high
i have your whole career history line
okay furthermore he has made guest or
more you have so much on there
there's a furthermore couldn't collusion is the
voice of mr peanut butter with siri
look up lore pictures of lawrence feet
i hope so okay okay wait his
height and body measurements oh god are
you all
tomkins is very tall handsome and has
an attractive personality whoa biased he stands
at five feet nine inches with a
masculine body structure what i'm you can
tell has a wonderful body measurement
however his measurement can't be ascertained at
the moment oh his weight and shoe
slash feet size are also not available
oh they're not availed do you want
to put them out there right hey
look i know i didn't have triple
e for shoe that's right i got
a wide foot tripoli trippy wow more
like triple x more like a little
a little
oh okay
siri how tall is
siri how tall is scott otterman i
found this on the web here's what
i found she changed it up here's
what i found i want to find
you on a weird theory what is
scott ottomans net worth cheeses okay here
i am on famous retail
eighteen the estimating cup and tones
those things aren't right though they don't
have i yeah they're not wrong i
always said one hundred and fifty dollars
oh yeah that's about right this one's
core is just watching my pocket right
now i want to find a funny
one about you a funny one okay
this is fun fun with sirah scott
ackerman epic fails
how many epic tales do i have
on the web
gotta be a lot oh my lord
so now lauren is just like scrolling
through her photos show my money information
cradle dot com what
one to find the weirdest website about
you i'm on the tigris euphrates dot
nest not aquaman height he stands at
a height of one point nine one
meters
one point nine one meters
yeah good congrats man hey yeah that
means this is from europe um that's
big weight how big hello how much
is a meter to foot yeah so
they think you're like a little too
few feet tall
scott aquaman deadpool deadpool is a fictional
character appearing in american compost just about
dead
it says people were maybe losing interest
like deadpool right we got deadpool in
there to jazz this up this is
something my virginia whose very refrain
oh my god anyway moving on eventually
we'll be older we'll still newish yeah
that'll be cool we'll have lots of
memories yeah i hope so i guess
so what do you think we won't
mail i'm just i hope that i
have all my memories sick my fear
are you guys gonna stay in la
are you gonna move away well when
i'm like eighty i'm planning a move
away
well some people so much is gonna
happen yeah but some people are like
i have my dream is that i
eventually retired move back to chicago or
whatever i want to have multiple properties
in different cities where i can go
to at any point i mean that
would look yeah that's okay don't just
happen to be a studio apartment
i was only a fancy p editor
you're paying rent too and you're not
there eleven months out of the year
if i don't know i wouldn't advise
that as your financial damage taken out
on every bee ah right still i
don't know if you don't want to
be a landlord i know not at
all forget it i'll just die here
yeah we have next to us is
is itself a great look into both
you've already lived here because only one
thing remaining where are the property next
door to us is a rental property
with three units and for when we
moved in over there's a fence between
the properties and over the fence was
growing this hysteria butte butte we love
you
oh but also afforded some privacy lot
more acres private schools part of both
yeah tris privacy trees nature's privacy there's
this the landlords wait what who's was
that who siri whose siri was that
shit this is why i don't have
series because it just goes off the
most i think it was yours paul
actually mindsets
to do that really yeah i don't
have a hey siri i just i
really hey siri
hey siri oh you know what it
was it was my watch there we
go there we go it it very
randomly wakes up and starts talking to
me not based on anything that i've
said so if you know that why
are you denying that it could be
you because it's so fervently because it
doesn't scout y happens frequently enough
but i honestly didn't think you don't
think we should be able to change
series named whatever we want yeah yeah
wow what would you change syria to
jonathan like that jonathan hey jonathan or
you're gonna say you have so syria
they cut down down right so the
landlord didn't tell anybody who's gonna do
this
had this entire thing removed huh
and now we can see more but
see directly like the fuck which yeah
i know what you can see into
yeah is it like sweepstakes homes oh
so rude yes so why don't you
plan something by the way the city
will plant trees if you maybe there's
more to the story i doubt it
the santa we asked paul let's hope
we're asking you like like each other
paul was there more to the story
i'm glad you all florin as a
matter of fact there is oh do
you wanna hear it awesome oh no
so we're very upset about this and
i told janey i will call murder
first we talked to the neighbors said
yeah we didn't know he's gonna do
that we thought he was just going
to trim it and then he'd just
remove
the whole thing and um i said
i'll call the landlord to find out
before we do anything i'll find out
if he has plans to do anything
sure knowing he doesn't write and he
does not think he's gonna be lifted
guy who you want to not have
to trim it for a very long
time yeah well because the the property
one of the properties opened up while
we were law
living there whenever our neighbors moved away
and we were an friend of ours
was looking for a place and so
we went looked at it with our
friend and it sucked and he was
so proud of himself saying like i
really fixed it up and it looked
like garbage so guys suck i know
that this guy is not going to
yeah he's not going to do anything
as no pride in ownership this guy
no ass
and so i call him up and
janie said was janie was listening to
me on the phone later she tells
people i thought yeah i thought paul
was gonna go off philly on this
guy and tell him you're gonna do
how many times do you go philly
on people and she's like they're listening
just love ism oh she does love
she loves this
i am a big this is very
this is such a cliche but i'm
a big let me talk to the
manager guy right you so i can
be rude to that person and not
be rude to the first person i
write but the but the other who
probably has a boss above them you
don't want to talk to their boss
you don't want to talk to the
someone to talk to the owner of
the company that's
i wanted to always talk to the
hale settle for the lowest person's bought
immediate boss i want i want a
recent thing i want to talk to
a person that i can that i
can feel okay about yelling at right
because they're paid to get yelled at
right which is not yelled about recently
in somebody
wow there was something it was like
i made this guy admit that their
that their policy was faulting that they
did not they did not accurately warn
people that there would be a charge
on this or that or whatever and
i was like all i'm asking for
you is to say that ah the
way that
it's worded is bad and doesn't it
doesn't indicate that you're going to do
this if it wasn't you just like
fine okay yes he held out for
ah dye my beard be fired for
relaying time and eventually he was like
yes it's true it's not it's not
worded well and we should change that
why not sure he was like oh
this fucking asshole that's like just changes
you have to deal with people like
this yeah do you have people on
the phone by the way who recognize
you your name or whatever when you're
like complaining about if no that's not
that they've admitted yeah well i've i
that's why i feel like i can't
even complain about things anymore because
like ah it i get a lot
of people on the phone going wait
is this the scott document and i'm
not famous or anything but it's like
there i think people in those jobs
or podcast listeners maybe you're right yeah
so i can't even come i don't
even have the joy of complaining to
people anymore is that fun
ah but sometimes it what do you
think feels worse after it's done after
i know yeah being pushy well yeah
but it's like you have to sometimes
because people are trying to rip you
off all the time no
and there's a certain amount of ripping
off that i'll put up with ram
and there's certain things that cost doing
business the causes of the success of
the voices go back to straight back
to the tree tree got so i
call this so i called the guy
up and i knew exactly how it
was going to go this guy is
just complaining about his life and how
how what's his life like with these
neighbors they may i had to do
this because they weren't taking care of
it and the city comes down on
me and the city made me do
it and you know all they have
nothing better to do than just harass
people you know all the shit and
it's like you know i wanted to
take more down but then i ran
out of money and i already spent
yeah i'm cleaned out of money i
put all my money in the pr
property it's all the usual stuff yeah
whatever this guy actually owe a huge
hearing you should look for reminding me
have somebody to live and die anyway
but since it's so fun is when
somebody's like interrogating people and you hear
them like makeup things or just get
away from the po yeah turk have
their excuse yeah it's like little white
lies yeah they're like dan
yes this guy was like i put
a nickel in him and he just
went oh yeah and then i was
just saying ah i would let him
i let him go for awhile and
say so my question was do you
plan to do anything else are you
gonna put anything else there in place
of it and and then you would
talk more about what problems he has
what he would like to do if
he could but he can't do it
right and i said well i think
we're gonna go ahead
and we're gonna put up a fence
um and he's like yeah sure you
know i don't blame you you know
the privacy i mean you know it
doesn't bother me but i don't live
there you know horse lovers and then
he said then he said ah you
know i'm you know maybe we could
you know split the cost of that
you know depending on region yeah it's
like i'm never going to see a
dime from yeah never wait and it's
like you but that is
one of those things where it's like
it's it's worth it to not try
to hassle this guy for money so
i can just get this done and
do whatever you want with it yes
but you're reminding me of like landlords
i've had where they i might what
i really hate is when somebody comes
at you with aggression before you come
at them with i mean like i
hate when like i i had an
a landlord
come after me for like ah some
damage my apartment this was like when
i first moved to l a and
what did you do to it you
filthy monster pistol
he was like oh really aggressive with
like you owe me two hundred dollars
he was very like crazy and fine
like i don't like yeah i admit
that i did that and i had
a guy like that too like i'm
you have to wait for me to
deny yes they skip a step yeah
to say because they've already had the
conversation in the yeah obviously yeah i
remember when it's a special breed of
person
i remember when klopp was like six
years ah ah it was like six
years after her freshman year um and
she was here you count all the
time
it's a weirder way to do it
you know
she was moving out of a place
and her landlord was being unreasonable about
something and and so i got the
job of like calling them and trying
to fix it you know and the
thing that i did which totally made
her discombobulated from the start and like
an uneasy and like what
i was like oh by the um
i said ah i so i got
her on the phone i said by
the way i'm tape recording this call
if that's all right wow she said
oh yeah sure and then it just
made her like oh nice it made
her be nice and it made her
her ah are all singer be nice
just be nice just be
nice i talk to you be nice
for the tape recording be nice for
the people who listen to this guy
yeah that's but yeah it really worked
on the regard we wanted yeah yeah
i had one landlord out here where
she was like really delighted that i
was on orange is the new black
and she really she thought that was
like i said i'm living in a
prisoner as delighted as those people in
the subway that time yeah
subway sandwiches yeah um she was like
yeah that's what i meant yeah she
went on and on about it when
i like you know when she put
it together whatever when you were applying
for the no like i had already
lived there i yeah i don't know
i don't know she just like realised
later or something yeah and so she
was really excited and so then i'm
like anytime i saw her she was
really nice and we had like
nice interactions over texts whenever there were
many techs about and then when i
moved out i left behind a broken
outlet cover that like had gotten like
cracked and fell off behind those things
are literally two dollars i mean it'll
steep i'm saying
cost about two dollars including the work
it takes to install a new one
okay sorry yeah oh and she charged
me like over two hundred dollars for
damages in the place just like the
play there was like on the ads
she took a picture of it it
was like cracked i was like took
a picture and normally i'm really good
at doing like filling every hole but
for whatever reason i didn't have
time and i wasn't doing writing on
toothpaste and she was at my friend
was moving into the apartment i also
was like it doesn't really matter my
friend is moving yeah like he doesn't
care if there's a nail hole right
here like this needs to be how
do you know i just know yeah
again from opposite irish in the same
building like it was a hole like
this is convenient for everyone kind of
thing right right and she overcharged me
so much
then i just paid it because i
was like i don't want to deal
with someone who's insane yeah but she
thinks you're a rich tv actress as
well that's just i mean i was
like i was living in your apartment
way you know what i get
i'm not a big centric million i
we have this the ar guy was
when i got the job on best
we ever had to move to new
york and we had only been in
this apartment for six months was like
a little house that we were renting
this dude was always around because he
used to live there with his wife
who he didn't we didn't find out
was his ex wife until much later
but he like when we're meeting him
to you know discuss renting the apartment
he talked about his wife as if
they were still together and then when
we found out they were divorced it
was like that was weird but he
um he would come around to ten
the grounds because there was like there's
like a little backyard with a lot
of greenery and he was just there
all the time and janie hated i
mean i wasn't crazy about it either
but janie don't like it because he
would it would be scary like she
would just be she'd be alone in
the house and then all of a
sudden like see somebody in the backyard
yeah him
and ah but he ah he at
one point
i can't remember what the argument was
but he was pleading with us about
something please balls please bear me when
we had moved in there was some
wicker furniture on the little patio that
we got rid of we thought the
old tenants had left it behind oh
but it was his he provided that
for us we did not realize though
oh but in his and his email
like say trying to say how much
he had done for us
this raises my head all the time
consider the settee ah consider the settee
consomme course it seems you so much
ah please consider the settee yeah did
i tell you about the dude speaking
of like dudes who'd like hang around
round and hang who own places hang
around due to own places so cool
up and i rented a place for
july fourth i think three years ago
out by by the ocean and had
a bunch of our friends there which
went and ah which one would we
show pacific yes hey and i pointed
to it
and um it was like christian adi
tj's old place like we didn't know
that we had hardly gone yeah we
got there and then suddenly less ed
hardy the name of it because by
it from he was an old tattoo
artist at heart he was an old
tattoo are saying the song is ed
hardy was an old tattoo his from
the
fifties do the dance so he had
the license to town tonight they licensed
his tattoos for ed hardy stuff and
then christian audigier bought the company i
see and i only know this because
coop used to be the the merch
rep really yes for anyhow wow yeah
shoe traveled up and down the coast
it's getting stores to buy ed hardy
wow smell there was a time when
that was really it was she quit
before it got that popular and she
could make some money oh yeah but
so we're at this place get back
into route this place in the coming
back around again and the air bnb
thing like listed the caretaker guy
as like a special feature of like
like talk to fred it'll be fun
or whatever you know and we're like
oh no we never watch doctor fred
but he certainly popped by quite a
lot and then um tal john and
i are out by the pool like
a couple hours up until john
yeah just three of us just getting
weird
and it's ten years after her freshman
year of and tall john medium scott
and short cool right
yeah my midi really talk to say
okay i guess am so tajo higher
in the pool this guy just pops
by how long would you say is
like okay for a guy to pop
by and like talk to you zero
yes yeah please where does he live
these he lives probably on the property
in a guest house so i would
say five minutes max
at three hours he talked to us
in the i got away and here
here you get in the pool no
he just sat there down would have
been a message and in my mind
he's like crouching next to it talking
to us while we're you know if
i stripped down my boxer brief weird
and the other part of it that
was really weird was he was like
um by the way the tv show
limitless based on the mood of the
bread
early cooper movie was was out at
the time he was like yes so
i created ah limitless and so yeah
that's going pretty well for me and
then we passed and we pulled on
the thread and were like oh that's
so cool so you wrote the original
movies like um well i
i wrote a script that they ripped
off and turned into lists so so
things are not going well so but
yeah but i'm feeling really think eventually
i'm gonna sue so that'll be really
good because it's on the air now
and it'll be like hey i'm doing
five episodes good news my idea guy
ripped off so i get to those
all be rich alright let's take a
break
we're back we're buck daddy we're gonna
make ah a point about my landlord
yeah because i the way i told
the clerk i made it sound as
though she liked that i was on
a tv show and then she overcharged
me she also that's exactly what it
sounds like you're really she turned on
me two other times so i knew
nah
not to fight this situation wait how
does she turn on well one time
i was late with my rent by
a day i'd never been late so
whereas the sixth or the second it
was this the first i think my
check hadn't come yet or the second
maybe but i totally spaced on it
for some reason and then she like
got so mean and she made me
send it same day even though i'm
like i knew she didn't like i
knew first of all i'm
trustworthy i'm always on time or earlier
with my rent and secondly i knew
it wasn't like she's gonna go under
if she doesn't get it now you
know i mean i didn't own the
place or was she she did but
she was very not understanding like any
problem that i had right um and
then we also had something regarding something
i was trying to get fixed my
point is when i got the bill
from
i was like i'm not going to
fight this even though it makes no
sense because i know that she's logical
when she is on her high horse
i wonder if i heard the other
side of the story like if i
was listening to the story being told
by her i would be on her
side about if she's like she was
late with the rent yeah yeah play
with a rad she leaves this cracked
plug thing i mean look i get
everywhere that i'm bad and everywhere that
i'm good and it's fun listen your
bag huh
i was lazy but when i was
leaving and i was late wind my
way you're lazy when you were leaving
my point is i didn't go around
filling every hole and taking off that
plate and replacing me i would never
do that by the way like i
don't think i've ever left an apartment
in the shape that i got it
in i was just like fuck it
i'll just know the deposit i remember
i was always on my foot
pause that and it pisses me off
when i don't get it because i
do every little thing the one place
that i'd left where when i was
all alone and my roommate moved out
and i just got a christmas tree
by myself and i'd just like had
a christmas tree and i just lived
alone and i just like left the
tree and i gotta say the part
that's with all the pine needles everywhere
see how old are you
ah to i was like six years
after freshmen year so i would do
it i don't know why i never
yeah i would i would do that
like christmas tree is nice i feel
like guys can i make a huge
generals yeah let's go there dampness is
fun i feel like that but i
also feel like they're more likely to
go no but i know a lot
of really messy girl
oils i don't know that's not true
i'm saying like i also know a
lot of guys like to go like
mel leave it but there's probably a
lot of guys who are like fuck
this i'm gonna make sure everything is
alright yeah that's true i feel like
i yeah it's just personal person i'm
just gonna every oscar there's a felix
i guess i'm just always thinking of
all the like improv guys departments that
i've been in for rehearsals oh my
god yeah my course like oh same
names no
i say it's time for a three
cheer send us your three cheers by
the way hashtag three cheers t h
r e a t u r e
s three ch three years and here's
a three-tier that r e a t
u r yes yes three teachers this
comes from chris lee creature double feature
aha
haha this comes from chris bleak on
twitter now this is something we had
name this is something we played on
bang bang nine years ago back in
the day maybe once or twice but
it's a little game called fortunately unfortunately
have all your players sit in a
circle or establish a clear are we
sitting in a circle or a triangle
or in a circle around a triangle
around triangle great our bodies make it
round a bar is mac around beautiful
song then proceed to tell a story
with each person saying one sentence at
a time here's the catch each sentence
must start with either ginny
good work can seem so straightforward i
was so into it or unfortunately always
alternating yep
so lauren start us off with just
a sentence it doesn't have to be
the first one doesn't have to be
fortunately or unfortunately i was just ah
i don't think it was say anything
yes anything okay anything you want like
anything that goes into your crazy little
head
from the twisted mind of lower leg
guests fortunately pitch perfect was on tv
unfortunately it was at the very end
and the credits started rolling fortunately the
credits led me to a name of
the woman that i ended up marrying
unfortunately she wasn't in on getting married
to me i married her while she
was asleep fortunately when she woke
up she asked me to marry her
not realizing we were already married unfortunately
she died the minute that the period
of her sentence came out where she
said will you marry me mr oh
that's great that you said yes the
period at the end of that fortunately
the because her sentence didn't make any
sense i was arrested
well that's fortunate
where are we
you're done unfortunately unfortunately i remained arrested
for a while after that fortunately when
i got out eighty years later
i found an apple on the street
that someone had discarded it only had
one bite in it unfortunately it had
two worms in it and they bit
me back fortunately i now have warm
powers
unfortunately no one cares because what can
a worm do except slither around which
is what i do every day
ah unfortunately which one you did i
did unfortunately forced i thought that was
positive for ya the science-y has recently
included slither lanes so i have my
own way to
unfortunately a car drove into one of
the slither lanes and cut me in
half but i didn't become two of
me i was still just one guy
cut in half fortunately people love the
half foot is still alive and i'm
on the cover of people magazine as
the
sexiest slithery are alive unfortunately it's my
bottom half
fortunately there's a lot of people that
are into that if you know anybody
unfortunately not the one that i really
want to be into it
fortunately anna kendrick is still responding to
me on twitter a lot
unfortunately she doesn't realize it's me she
thinks it's someone else someone better fortunately
i'm in pitch perfect for unfortunately it's
only going to be played on one
channel lifetime
fortunately it's the only channel i have
so i get to see the movie
as much as i want unfortunately i
don't even have a tv all i
have is a cable box fortunately i'm
going to go to my neighbor's apartment
and watch it
unfortunately that's the end of it
oh great game thank ye breaking a
feature it's a three rates feature great
creature creature all right jack reacher oh
we should play jeff creature feature right
we good play jack we should play
jack reacher next time what's that you
don't know jack reacher you don't know
how to
play jack reacher no i'm saying like
tom cruise play jack reacher yeah he
knows how to play jacket each region
reaching
right right thing jack reacher or decree
to reach you're crazy huh was a
creature of the saint apparently in the
jack reacher novels he's very tall he's
very tall and his his knuckles are
often described as being as pigs walnuts
why so
just is a twitter like some guy
who's posting passages from these books they're
fucking hilarious but i don't know if
there's supposed to be funny or not
i don't think my oh wait britney
spears when you're just that as big
as walnuts made me think of this
post she just did a time britney
spears and i'm big as walnuts
i don't think i'll find she doesn't
her story but do they mean big
as paulie walnuts yeah paulina wallner
ah what if someone said that to
paulie walnuts every supremacy probably want a
walnut what if every soprano scene with
him starts right after someone has just
said that and he's like shut the
fuck anyway tony you think i've heard
that one
don't know don't know rewatch the sopranos
and anytime he comes on screen imagine
that someone just said that to him
this guy focusing probably want more so
britney spears was ah clapping back at
the paparazzi because she claims she believes
there's a conspiracy that they edit the
photos and whatever so
they made her look like she had
gained weight but and she was showing
her body and she was like a
maschine as a needle which saying yeah
that was a needle she said needle
but as you can see i'm skinny
as a needle
cool i just loved it yeah it
was just strange oh me too alright
well wait we're done it's a girl
with new hair what am i gonna
do i just
you too this show just become you
looking up things on twitter that just
playing them i don't care what the
show has become ah you have a
problem with it i do have a
problem with it lower or someone who
care lorne michaels don't call me with
my given name
yeah with my chamber
alright we'll see you next time bye
uh